-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

Where -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
Iguazu -X- -X- B-LOC
? -X- -X- O

Iguazu -X- -X- B-LOC
Falls -X- -X- I-LOC

Widely -X- -X- O
considered -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
spectacular -X- -X- O
waterfalls -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Iguazu -X- -X- B-LOC
Falls -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
border -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Argentina -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
Brazil -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
certainly -X- -X- O
must -X- -X- O
see -X- -X- O
attraction -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
centre -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
falls -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
locally -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
‘ -X- -X- O
Garganta -X- -X- O
Del -X- -X- O
Diablo -X- -X- O
’ -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Devil -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
Throat -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
huge -X- -X- O
volume -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
water -X- -X- O
sends -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
constant -X- -X- O
mist -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
spray -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
air -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

With -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
sun -X- -X- O
shinning -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
spray -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
creating -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
rainbow -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
foreground -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
perfect -X- -X- O
place -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
trademark -X- -X- O
Iguazu -X- -X- B-LOC
Falls -X- -X- I-LOC
photograph -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

However -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
save -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
shots -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rest -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
falls -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
total -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
around -X- -X- O
270 -X- -X- O
cascades -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
spread -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
over -X- -X- O
nearly -X- -X- O
2 -X- -X- O
miles -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Iguazu -X- -X- B-LOC
River -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Iguazu -X- -X- B-LOC
Falls -X- -X- I-LOC
are -X- -X- O
easily -X- -X- O
accessible -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
dependent -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
restrictions -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
budget -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
either -X- -X- O
bus -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
plane -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
nearest -X- -X- O
towns -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
site -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
Puerto -X- -X- B-LOC
Iguazu -X- -X- I-LOC
in -X- -X- O
Argentina -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
12 -X- -X- O
miles -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
falls -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Foz -X- -X- B-LOC
do -X- -X- I-LOC
Iguaçu -X- -X- I-LOC
in -X- -X- O
Brazil -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
equally -X- -X- O
close -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Both -X- -X- O
towns -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
airports -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
regularly -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
larger -X- -X- O
cities -X- -X- O
such -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
Sao -X- -X- B-LOC
Paulo -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Rio -X- -X- B-LOC
de -X- -X- I-LOC
Janeiro -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
Buenos -X- -X- B-LOC
Aires -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
bus -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
obviously -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
cheaper -X- -X- O
option -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
travelling -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
Buenos -X- -X- B-LOC
Aires -X- -X- I-LOC
the -X- -X- O
trip -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
full -X- -X- O
20 -X- -X- O
hours -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
although -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
buses -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
very -X- -X- O
comfortable -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
spacious -X- -X- O
reclining -X- -X- O
seats -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
bus -X- -X- O
trip -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
Sao -X- -X- B-LOC
Paulo -X- -X- I-LOC
is -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
similar -X- -X- O
affair -X- -X- O
taking -X- -X- O
around -X- -X- O
18 -X- -X- O
hours -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Foz -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Brazilian -X- -X- O
side -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
larger -X- -X- O
town -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
however -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
geared -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
cater -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
visitors -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Waterfalls -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
National -X- -X- O
Parks -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
offer -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
range -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
accommodation -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
budgets -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

For -X- -X- O
those -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
larger -X- -X- O
appetite -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
scenery -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
larger -X- -X- O
budget -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
hotel -X- -X- O
complexes -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
closer -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
action -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
views -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
parts -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
falls -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

RP -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
Is -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
wrong -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
remove -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
contact -X- -X- O
because -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
really -X- -X- O
really -X- -X- O
stupid -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
read -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
answers -X- -X- O
lol -X- -X- O
:( -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
gon -X- -X- O
na -X- -X- O
say -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
now -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
commit -X- -X- O
suicide -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
something -X- -X- O
haha -X- -X- O

LOL -X- -X- O
Callum -X- -X- B-PER

no -X- -X- O
no -X- -X- O
no -X- -X- O
no -X- -X- O
no -X- -X- O
no -X- -X- O

it -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
definitely -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

no -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
lol -X- -X- O

i -X- -X- O
emailed -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
saaaaaam -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

how -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

it -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
me -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
!? -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
mostly -X- -X- O
joking -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
talk -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
suicide -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
really -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
stupid -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
stupid -X- -X- O
situations -X- -X- O
D: -X- -X- O

i -X- -X- O
guz -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
lol -X- -X- O

whoooooo -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

sorry -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
i -X- -X- O
ca -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
help -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
stupidity -X- -X- O
=( -X- -X- O

EDIT -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
love -X- -X- O
how -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
says -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
callum -X- -X- B-PER
but -X- -X- O
does -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
deny -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
me -X- -X- O
.... -X- -X- O
i -X- -X- O
think -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
talking -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O

EDIT -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
now -X- -X- O
i -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
curious -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O

EDIT -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
How -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O

lol -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
really -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
worse -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
me -X- -X- O

and -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
gpa -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
mine -X- -X- O
.... -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
question -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
McDonald -X- -X- B-ORG
's -X- -X- I-ORG
Monopoly -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

Please -X- -X- O
HELP -X- -X- O
!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

TEN -X- -X- O
POINTS -X- -X- O
!!!!!!!!!!? -X- -X- O

Ok -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Mcdonald -X- -X- B-ORG
's -X- -X- I-ORG
has -X- -X- O
Monopoly -X- -X- O
going -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
now -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

& -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
wan -X- -X- O
na -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O
has -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
game -X- -X- O
pieces -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

And -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O
has -X- -X- O
EXTRA -X- -X- O
game -X- -X- O
pieces -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Because -X- -X- O
Large -X- -X- O
Fries -X- -X- O
give -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
FOUR -X- -X- O
PIECES -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
drinks -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
got -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
included -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

So -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
somebody -X- -X- O
please -X- -X- O
list -X- -X- O
ALL -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
includes -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
game -X- -X- O
pieces -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
number -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
game -X- -X- O
pieces -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
THAT -X- -X- O
FOOD -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

PLEASE -X- -X- O
!!!!!! -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
person -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
explains -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
helps -X- -X- O
me -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
question -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
REWARDED -X- -X- O
WITH -X- -X- O
TEN -X- -X- O
POINTS -X- -X- O
!!!!!!! -X- -X- O

PLEASE -X- -X- O
HELP -X- -X- O
!!!!!!!!!!! -X- -X- O

THANK -X- -X- O
YOU -X- -X- O
!!!!!!!!!!!!! -X- -X- O
:D -X- -X- O

scroll -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
website -X- -X- O
shows -X- -X- O
each -X- -X- O
thing -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
buy -X- -X- O
(: -X- -X- O

http://www.playatmcd.com/en-us/Main/Gameboard -X- -X- O

4 -X- -X- O
Peels -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
20 -X- -X- O
piece -X- -X- O
Chicken -X- -X- O
McNuggets -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
Large -X- -X- O
fries -X- -X- O

2 -X- -X- O
Peels -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
Big -X- -X- O
Mac -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
10 -X- -X- O
piece -X- -X- O
Chicken -X- -X- O
McNuggets -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
Medium -X- -X- O
Fountain -X- -X- O
Drink -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
McCAFE -X- -X- O
Drink -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
Filet -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
O -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
Fish -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
Hash -X- -X- O
Browns -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
Egg -X- -X- O
McMuffin -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Sausage -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
Fruit -X- -X- O
& -X- -X- O
Maple -X- -X- O
Oatmeal -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

Pubs -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Philadelphia -X- -X- B-PER
? -X- -X- O

Hey -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
trying -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
restaurant -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Philly -X- -X- B-PER
to -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
husband -X- -X- O
tomorrow -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
birthday -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
pretty -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
love -X- -X- O
American -X- -X- O
Food -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
drinks -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
occasion -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
laid -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
kind -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
guy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O
;) -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
somewhere -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
going -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
awesome -X- -X- O
burgers -X- -X- O
/ -X- -X- O
american -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
atmosphere -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
preferably -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tavern -X- -X- O
/ -X- -X- O
pub -X- -X- O
style -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
nice -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
service -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
around -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O
=) -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
looking -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
suggestions -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
anyone -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
knows -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
philly -X- -X- B-PER
area -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
to's -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
moved -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
town -X- -X- O
outside -X- -X- O
Philly -X- -X- B-PER
a -X- -X- O
couple -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
months -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
expert -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
little -X- -X- O
help -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O
=) -X- -X- O

Thank -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
feed -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Oh -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
asked -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
question -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
perfect -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Go -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
local -X- -X- O
market -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
drug -X- -X- O
store -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
buy -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
month -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
copy -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Philadelphia -X- -X- B-ORG
Magazine -X- -X- I-ORG
" -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
very -X- -X- O
subject -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
bars -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
lists -X- -X- O
places -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
over -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
suburbs -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Wishing -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
husband -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
happy -X- -X- O
birthday -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
're -X- -X- O
looking -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
burger -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
fries -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
too -X- -X- O
die -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
drinks -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Chickie -X- -X- B-LOC
& -X- -X- I-LOC
Pete -X- -X- I-LOC
's -X- -X- I-LOC
! -X- -X- O

Oh -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
gosh -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
make -X- -X- O
sure -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
order -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
crab -X- -X- O
fries -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
wo -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
regret -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
:) -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

Better -X- -X- O
Steakhouse -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Philadelphia -X- -X- B-LOC
? -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
taking -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
wife -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
year -X- -X- O
wedding -X- -X- O
anniversary -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
agree -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
steak -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
staying -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
hotel -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Center -X- -X- B-LOC
City -X- -X- I-LOC
Philadelphia -X- -X- B-LOC
so -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
wanted -X- -X- O
something -X- -X- O
close -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
spent -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
afternoon -X- -X- O
looking -X- -X- O
around -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
menu -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
menu -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
looked -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
photo -X- -X- O
galleries -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
inside -X- -X- O
look -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
decor -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
restaurants -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
narrowed -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
three -X- -X- O
establishments -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
never -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
these -X- -X- O
places -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
suggestions -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
advice -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
welcome -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
narrowed -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Butcher -X- -X- B-ORG
and -X- -X- I-ORG
Singer -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
Davio -X- -X- B-ORG
's -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Del -X- -X- B-ORG
Frisco -X- -X- I-ORG
s -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Thanks -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
advance -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
advice -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sidenote -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
familiar -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Capital -X- -X- B-ORG
Grille -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
Barclay -X- -X- B-ORG
Prime -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- B-ORG
Palm -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- B-ORG
Prime -X- -X- I-ORG
Rib -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
Morton -X- -X- B-ORG
s -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
Ruth -X- -X- B-ORG
Chris -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
etc -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
weighed -X- -X- O
those -X- -X- O
options -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
found -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
three -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
chosen -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
wife -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
own -X- -X- O
taste -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Please -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
reviews -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
three -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
mentioned -X- -X- O
earlier -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Many -X- -X- O
thanks -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
familiar -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
Morton -X- -X- B-ORG
's -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
Ruth -X- -X- B-ORG
Chris -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
never -X- -X- O
eaten -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ones -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
listed -X- -X- O
nor -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
anyone -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
has -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
hope -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
answer -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Anyway -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
lovely -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
anniversary -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

Was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
San -X- -X- B-LOC
Francisco -X- -X- I-LOC
Bay -X- -X- I-LOC
Area -X- -X- I-LOC
mostly -X- -X- O
Caucasian -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
early -X- -X- O
1970s -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

No -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

There -X- -X- O
has -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
large -X- -X- O
Asian -X- -X- O
presence -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
SF -X- -X- B-LOC
Bay -X- -X- I-LOC
Area -X- -X- I-LOC
for -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
long -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
-- -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Chinatown -X- -X- B-LOC
here -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
largest -X- -X- O
population -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
chinese -X- -X- O
outside -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
China -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
lots -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Japanese -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
'd -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
displaced -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
WWII -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
whole -X- -X- O
Western -X- -X- B-LOC
Addition -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
large -X- -X- O
portion -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- B-LOC
Haight -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
black -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- B-LOC
Mission -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
basically -X- -X- O
latin -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
american -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

As -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
southeast -X- -X- O
asians -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
philipinos -X- -X- O
came -X- -X- O
over -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
added -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
cultures -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

So -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Bay -X- -X- B-LOC
Area -X- -X- I-LOC
has -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
fairly -X- -X- O
mixed -X- -X- O
ethnically -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
long -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
-- -X- -X- O
caucasians -X- -X- O
may -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
seemed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
large -X- -X- O
populous -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
because -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
tourists -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
caucasian -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
hippies -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
caucasians -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
photographers -X- -X- O
took -X- -X- O
pictures -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
ethicities -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
well -X- -X- O
represented -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
politics -X- -X- O
yet -X- -X- O
-- -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
rather -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
breaking -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
color -X- -X- O
barrier -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
70's -X- -X- O
due -X- -X- O
largely -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
open -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
minded -X- -X- O
hippy -X- -X- O
generation -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Marin -X- -X- B-LOC
County -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
predominantly -X- -X- O
caucasian -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
expanding -X- -X- O
outer -X- -X- O
east -X- -X- O
bay -X- -X- O
areas -X- -X- O
started -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
white -X- -X- O
suburbs -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
long -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
Civil -X- -X- O
Rights -X- -X- O
laws -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
discrimination -X- -X- O
started -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
impact -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

You -X- -X- O
never -X- -X- O
saw -X- -X- O
black -X- -X- O
MUNI -X- -X- O
drivers -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Asian -X- -X- O
police -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Latino -X- -X- O
politicians -X- -X- O
until -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
evolution -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Many -X- -X- O
illegals -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
counted -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
population -X- -X- O
until -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
mid-80s -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
big -X- -X- O
percent -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Chinese -X- -X- O
migration -X- -X- O
until -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
mid -X- -X- O
90s -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
fewer -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
running -X- -X- O
across -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mexican -X- -X- O
border -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
fewer -X- -X- O
social -X- -X- O
benefits -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
immigrants -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
counted -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Only -X- -X- O
Caucasians -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
political -X- -X- O
power -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
corporate -X- -X- O
presence -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
owned -X- -X- O
businesses -X- -X- O
except -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Mom -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Pop -X- -X- O
stores -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
neighborhoods -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

San -X- -X- B-LOC
Francisco -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
settled -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
19th -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
20th -X- -X- O
century -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
mainly -X- -X- O
European -X- -X- O
immigrants -X- -X- O
except -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
Asian -X- -X- O
workers -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
manual -X- -X- O
laborers -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

There -X- -X- O
has -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Mexican -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
American -X- -X- O
cultural -X- -X- O
influence -X- -X- O
since -X- -X- O
Calif -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
owned -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Mexico -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
larger -X- -X- O
black -X- -X- O
population -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
70s -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
now -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
power -X- -X- O
until -X- -X- O
Willie -X- -X- B-PER
Brown -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
elected -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

San -X- -X- B-LOC
Francisco -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
progressive -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
welcoming -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
tolerant -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
kinds -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
historically -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
counties -X- -X- O
outside -X- -X- O
San -X- -X- B-LOC
Francisco -X- -X- I-LOC
were -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
white -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
San -X- -X- B-LOC
Francisco -X- -X- I-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
70s -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

EDIT -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
My -X- -X- O
memory -X- -X- O
may -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
might -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
accurate -X- -X- O
answer -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
someone -X- -X- O
else -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
remembers -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

My -X- -X- O
dad -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
does -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
understand -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

Ugh -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
dad -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
stupid -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
does -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
understand -X- -X- O
anything -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
5 -X- -X- O
sisters -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
including -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
mom -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
guy -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
house -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
six -X- -X- O
females -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Now -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
youngest -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
got -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
period -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
now -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
ours -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
thinks -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
thing -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
ohh -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
must -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
happy -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
finally -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
yours -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
wish -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
mine -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
even -X- -X- O
joking -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
think -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
living -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
house -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
girls -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
making -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
crazy -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

Yep -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
females -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
getting -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
dads -X- -X- O
.. -X- -X- O

Do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
blame -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
please -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
feels -X- -X- O
lonely -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
wants -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
show -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
attention -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
look -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
please -X- -X- O
forgive -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
sympathy -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
miss -X- -X- O
something -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
sorry -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
dad -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

Vietnamese -X- -X- O
girl -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Mayko -X- -X- B-PER
? -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
thought -X- -X- O
Mayko -X- -X- B-PER
or -X- -X- O
Meiko -X- -X- B-PER
is -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Japanese -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Canadian -X- -X- O
Regenesis -X- -X- O
actress -X- -X- O
Mayko -X- -X- B-PER
Nguyen -X- -X- I-PER
has -X- -X- O
Japanese -X- -X- O
connection -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
fake -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

Right -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
proven -X- -X- O
source -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

And -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
last -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Nguyen -X- -X- B-PER
is -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
typical -X- -X- O
Vietnamese -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
anyone -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

Certainly -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Nguyen -X- -X- B-PER
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
names -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Mayko -X- -X- B-PER
is -X- -X- O
relating -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Japanese -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
baby -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
born -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
must -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
named -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
according -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
fathers -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
principle -X- -X- O
except -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
number -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
cases -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
example -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
babies -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
orphans -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
father -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

E.g -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Full -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
father -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Nguyen -X- -X- B-PER
Thanh -X- -X- I-PER
Luan -X- -X- I-PER
" -X- -X- O
===> -X- -X- O
Full -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
son -X- -X- O
/ -X- -X- O
daughter -X- -X- O
certainly -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Nguyen -X- -X- B-PER
.......... -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
instance -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Nguyen -X- -X- B-PER
Thi -X- -X- I-PER
Thuy -X- -X- I-PER
Lan -X- -X- I-PER
" -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

But -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
babies -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
born -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
American -X- -X- B-LOC
so -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
named -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
way -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
still -X- -X- O
remain -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
order -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
recall -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
origination -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
pretty -X- -X- O
sure -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Mayko -X- -X- B-PER
is -X- -X- O
Japanese -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

She -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Canadian -X- -X- O
born -X- -X- O
Vietnamese -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
'm -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
sure -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

Modern -X- -X- O
m -X- -X- O
16 -X- -X- O
vs -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
m -X- -X- O
16 -X- -X- O
version -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
playing -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
video -X- -X- O
game -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
has -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
m -X- -X- O
16 -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
model -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
game -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
3 -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
shot -X- -X- O
burst -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

My -X- -X- O
brother -X- -X- O
said -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
full -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
auto -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
semiautomatic -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

My -X- -X- O
questions -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
.. -X- -X- O

1 -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
difference -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
modern -X- -X- O
m16 -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
m -X- -X- O
16 -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

2 -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
m -X- -X- O
16's -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
3 -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
shot -X- -X- O
burst -X- -X- O
function -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

To -X- -X- O
save -X- -X- O
money -X- -X- O
Robert -X- -X- B-PER
McNamara -X- -X- I-PER
ordered -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ammunition -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
new -X- -X- O
M -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
16s -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
sent -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
SEA -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
early -X- -X- O
60s -X- -X- O
use -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
older -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
dirtier -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
gunpowder -X- -X- O
meant -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
use -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
M -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
14 -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
ordered -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
receiver -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
think -X- -X- O
chrome -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
coating -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
helped -X- -X- O
keep -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
gun -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
jamming -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Than -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
troops -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
issued -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weapon -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
told -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
self -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
cleaning -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

As -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
result -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
problem -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weapon -X- -X- O
jamming -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Once -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
troops -X- -X- O
started -X- -X- O
cleaning -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weapon -X- -X- O
properly -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
even -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
dirtier -X- -X- O
powder -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
era -X- -X- O
M -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
16 -X- -X- O
turned -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
weapon -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
purpose -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
screw -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
kind -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
things -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
happen -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
bean -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
counters -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
McNamara -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
nothing -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bean -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
counter -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
instead -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
soldiers -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
charge -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Today -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
weapons -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
kind -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
problem -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
reliable -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

1 -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
modern -X- -X- O
m -X- -X- O
16 -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
alright -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
m -X- -X- O
16 -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
clog -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
never -X- -X- O
work -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

2 -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
All -X- -X- O
M -X- -X- O
16's -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
either -X- -X- O
automatic -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
semi -X- -X- O
automatic -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

No -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
uses -X- -X- O
3 -X- -X- O
burst -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

you -X- -X- O
play -X- -X- O
too -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
cod -X- -X- O
;P -X- -X- O

modern -X- -X- O
m -X- -X- O
16 -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
Chicago -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
restaurant -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
dine -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
budget -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

Downtown -X- -X- B-LOC
Chicago -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Loop -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
North -X- -X- B-LOC

Take -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
red -X- -X- O
line -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Clark -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
turn -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Walk -X- -X- O
2 -X- -X- O
blocks -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
turn -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
again -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Walk -X- -X- O
2 -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
blocks -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
cross -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
street -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

You -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
place -X- -X- O
called -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
BIG -X- -X- O
BOWL -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

THAI -X- -X- O
FOOD -X- -X- O
AND -X- -X- O
ASIAN -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

BEST -X- -X- O
PLACE -X- -X- O
EVER -X- -X- O
!!!!!!!!!!!! -X- -X- O

McDonald -X- -X- B-LOC
s -X- -X- I-LOC

Not -X- -X- O
necessarily -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
restaurant -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
order -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
lunch -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
less -X- -X- O
expensive -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
dinner -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

You -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
order -X- -X- O
appetizers -X- -X- O
rather -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
full -X- -X- O
meal -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
dinner -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

But -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
way -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
use -X- -X- O
coupons -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Check -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
http://www.restaurant.com -X- -X- O
lots -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
restaurants -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
look -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
menu -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
check -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
prices -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Yo -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
may -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
try -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
small -X- -X- O
neighborhood -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
restaurants -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
support -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
run -X- -X- O
places -X- -X- O
rather -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
large -X- -X- O
corporate -X- -X- O
chains -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Not -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
anything -X- -X- O
wrong -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
because -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
employ -X- -X- O
local -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
live -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
shop -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

New -X- -X- B-LOC
Zealand -X- -X- I-LOC
skilled -X- -X- O
migrant -X- -X- O
visa -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
apply -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
skilled -X- -X- O
migrant -X- -X- O
worker -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
visa -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
accepted -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
work -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
same -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
skills -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
application -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
work -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
ca -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
something -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
own -X- -X- O
field -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
posted -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
question -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
NZ -X- -X- B-LOC
visa -X- -X- O
site -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
ca -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
info -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
does -X- -X- O
anyone -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
.??? -X- -X- O

Watch -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
poles -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
coming -X- -X- O
..... -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
little -X- -X- O
butterfly -X- -X- O

That -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
preferable -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
does -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
matter -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
something -X- -X- O
similar -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
depends -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
conditions -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
skilled -X- -X- O
migrant -X- -X- O
visa -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Your -X- -X- O
visa -X- -X- O
should -X- -X- O
say -X- -X- O
whether -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
restricted -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
work -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
specific -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
visa -X- -X- O
does -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
restrict -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
taking -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
work -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
New -X- -X- B-LOC
Zealand -X- -X- I-LOC
then -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
work -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
matters -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
received -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
offer -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
employment -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
currently -X- -X- O
working -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
New -X- -X- B-LOC
Zealand -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
job -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
application -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
skilled -X- -X- O
migrant -X- -X- O
visa -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

What -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
places -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
eat -X- -X- O
brunch -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

My -X- -X- O
bday -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
Saturday -X- -X- O
:) -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
wan -X- -X- O
na -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
breakfast -X- -X- O
/ -X- -X- O
lunch -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
fam -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
gon -X- -X- O
na -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
dinner -X- -X- O
party -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
cousin -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
having -X- -X- O
Having -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
bridal -X- -X- O
shower -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
brunch -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
places -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
denny -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
ihop -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Oh -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
btw -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
live -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
los -X- -X- B-LOC
angeles -X- -X- I-LOC
look -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
places -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
lb -X- -X- B-LOC
area -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
torrance -X- -X- B-LOC
etc -X- -X- O
thanx -X- -X- O
^_^ -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
strongly -X- -X- O
suggest -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- B-LOC
Breakfast -X- -X- I-LOC
Club -X- -X- I-LOC
" -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Chicago -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

You -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
definately -X- -X- O
plan -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
meal -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
reasonable -X- -X- O
prices -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
hurry -X- -X- O
though -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Just -X- -X- O
relax -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
enjoy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
fabulous -X- -X- O
French -X- -X- O
toast -X- -X- O
too -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- B-LOC
Breakfast -X- -X- I-LOC
Club -X- -X- I-LOC
& -X- -X- I-LOC
Grill -X- -X- I-LOC
is -X- -X- O
conveniently -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
blocks -X- -X- O
off -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- B-LOC
Kennedy -X- -X- I-LOC
Expressway -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

There -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
plenty -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
parking -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
street -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
private -X- -X- O
lot -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
'd -X- -X- O
rather -X- -X- O
dine -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
home -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
simply -X- -X- O
call -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
order -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
service -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Plenty -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
parking -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weekends -X- -X- O
.. -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
week -X- -X- O
please -X- -X- O
park -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
little -X- -X- O
lot -X- -X- O
across -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
street -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Directions -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- B-LOC
Kennedy -X- -X- I-LOC
: -X- -X- O
Take -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Ogden -X- -X- O
Exit -X- -X- O
off -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- B-LOC
Kennedy -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Go -X- -X- O
three -X- -X- O
lights -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
onto -X- -X- O
Ogden -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Continue -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
blocks -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Hubbard -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
another -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
're -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
corner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Hubbard -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Noble -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- B-LOC
Breakfast -X- -X- I-LOC
Club -X- -X- I-LOC
& -X- -X- I-LOC
Grill -X- -X- I-LOC

1381 -X- -X- O
W. -X- -X- O
Hubbard -X- -X- O

Chicago -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
IL -X- -X- B-LOC
60622 -X- -X- O

312-666-2372 -X- -X- O
Tel -X- -X- O

Email -X- -X- O
Us -X- -X- O

Hours -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Operation -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O

Monday -X- -X- O
thru -X- -X- O
Friday -X- -X- O

6:30 -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
8:00 -X- -X- O
pm -X- -X- O

Saturday -X- -X- O
& -X- -X- O
Sunday -X- -X- O

7:00 -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
5:00 -X- -X- O
pm -X- -X- O

Happy -X- -X- O
Hour -X- -X- O

Monday -X- -X- O
thru -X- -X- O
Friday -X- -X- O

4:00 -X- -X- O
pm -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
6:00 -X- -X- O
pm -X- -X- O

$ -X- -X- O
4 -X- -X- O
appetizers -X- -X- O

$ -X- -X- O
4 -X- -X- O
wine -X- -X- O

$ -X- -X- O
3 -X- -X- O
Coronas -X- -X- O
& -X- -X- O
Heineken -X- -X- O

Unless -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
plan -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
late -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bridal -X- -X- O
shower -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
might -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
post -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
again -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
L.A. -X- -X- B-LOC
section -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

What -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
goal -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
North -X- -X- B-LOC
Vietnam -X- -X- I-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Tet -X- -X- O
offensive -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
Johnson -X- -X- B-PER
deployed -X- -X- O
troops -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
1964 -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
advised -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
half -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
million -X- -X- O
troops -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
ten -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
pacify -X- -X- O
South -X- -X- B-LOC
Vietnam -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
refused -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
believe -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
ordered -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
win -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
three -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
next -X- -X- O
election -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
1968 -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
give -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
number -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
troops -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
requested -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

This -X- -X- O
left -X- -X- O
Westmoreland -X- -X- B-PER
with -X- -X- O
few -X- -X- O
options -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
adapted -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Search -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Destroy -X- -X- O
strategy -X- -X- O
instead -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Clear -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Defend -X- -X- O
strategy -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
long -X- -X- O
run -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
preferred -X- -X- O
method -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
pacifying -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
insurgency -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Thing -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
ARVN -X- -X- B-ORG
was -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
having -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
big -X- -X- O
problem -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Local -X- -X- B-ORG
VC -X- -X- I-ORG
( -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
guerilla -X- -X- O
movement -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
challenged -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Main -X- -X- B-ORG
Force -X- -X- I-ORG
VC -X- -X- I-ORG
( -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
light -X- -X- O
infantry -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
North -X- -X- B-ORG
Vietnamese -X- -X- I-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
( -X- -X- O
NVA -X- -X- B-ORG
) -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Americans -X- -X- O
swept -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
Search -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Destroy -X- -X- O
operations -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Communists -X- -X- O
quickly -X- -X- O
leaned -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
stand -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
US -X- -X- B-LOC
firepower -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
these -X- -X- O
regular -X- -X- O
troops -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
forced -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
flee -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
country -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
sanctuary -X- -X- O
across -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
borders -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Laos -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
Cambodia -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

All -X- -X- O
those -X- -X- O
sunny -X- -X- O
reports -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
progress -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
were -X- -X- O
correct -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Communists -X- -X- O
WERE -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
defeated -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

However -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Johnson -X- -X- B-PER
would -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
let -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
cross -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
borders -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
clean -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Communist -X- -X- O
bases -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
warned -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
building -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
huge -X- -X- O
Army -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
eventually -X- -X- O
launch -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
attack -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
ignored -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
advisers -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Communists -X- -X- O
agreed -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
defeat -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Americans -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

However -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
hoped -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Tet -X- -X- O
Offensive -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
sneak -X- -X- O
past -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Americans -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
attack -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ARVN -X- -X- B-ORG
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
urban -X- -X- O
areas -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
deployed -X- -X- O
doing -X- -X- O
successful -X- -X- O
Clear -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Defend -X- -X- O
operations -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Communists -X- -X- O
thought -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
defeat -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ARVN -X- -X- B-ORG
, -X- -X- O
cause -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
fall -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
South -X- -X- O
Vietnamese -X- -X- O
government -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
rally -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Communist -X- -X- O
cause -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
leave -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Americans -X- -X- O
stranded -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sea -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
angry -X- -X- O
peasants -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

THAT -X- -X- O
WAS -X- -X- O
THE -X- -X- O
PLAN -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

What -X- -X- O
happened -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Americans -X- -X- O
detected -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
attempt -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
infiltrate -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
urban -X- -X- O
areas -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
already -X- -X- O
redeploying -X- -X- O
troops -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rural -X- -X- O
areas -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
ARVN -X- -X- B-ORG
rushed -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
holiday -X- -X- O
leave -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
counterattacked -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Within -X- -X- O
24 -X- -X- O
hours -X- -X- O
every -X- -X- O
Communist -X- -X- O
assault -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
defeated -X- -X- O
except -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ancient -X- -X- O
capital -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Hue -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
government -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
NOT -X- -X- O
fall -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

And -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
South -X- -X- O
Vietnamese -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
give -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ultimate -X- -X- O
choice -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
rallied -X- -X- O
… -X- -X- O

TO -X- -X- O
THE -X- -X- O
SOUTH -X- -X- O
VIETNAMESE -X- -X- O
GOVERNMENT -X- -X- O
…. -X- -X- O

Tet -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
huge -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
political -X- -X- O
disaster -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Communists -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
chased -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
Laos -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
Cambodia -X- -X- B-LOC
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ARVN -X- -X- B-ORG
in -X- -X- O
hot -X- -X- O
pursuit -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
rejected -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
attempt -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
topple -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
government -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
intents -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
purposes -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
US -X- -X- B-LOC
military -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ARVN -X- -X- B-ORG
) -X- -X- O
handed -X- -X- O
Johnson -X- -X- B-PER
the -X- -X- O
victory -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
ordered -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
achieve -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
frame -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
ordered -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

All -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
complete -X- -X- O
victory -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
allow -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
Laos -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
Cambodia -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
finish -X- -X- O
off -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
shattered -X- -X- O
Communist -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

But -X- -X- O
Johnson -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
obtuse -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
n’t -X- -X- O
understand -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
victory -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
handed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
silver -X- -X- O
platter -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Instead -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
pulled -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
off -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
stopped -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bombing -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
North -X- -X- B-LOC
Vietnam -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
withdrew -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
presidential -X- -X- O
race -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
spent -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rest -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
term -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
office -X- -X- O
trying -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
surrender -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
North -X- -X- B-LOC
Vietnam -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
screwed -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
accepting -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
surrender -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
offered -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
American -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
NOT -X- -X- O
having -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
elected -X- -X- O
Richard -X- -X- B-PER
Nixon -X- -X- I-PER
to -X- -X- O
fix -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
mess -X- -X- O
LBJ -X- -X- B-PER
had -X- -X- O
made -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
surrender -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
antiwar -X- -X- O
movement -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
demanding -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
end -X- -X- O
Nixon -X- -X- B-PER
kept -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
promise -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
“ -X- -X- O
… -X- -X- O
peace -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
honor -X- -X- O
…. -X- -X- O
” -X- -X- O

But -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
another -X- -X- O
question -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

To -X- -X- O
emancipate -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
south -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
serious -X- -X- O
failure -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

To -X- -X- O
make -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
unpalatable -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
American -X- -X- O
public -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
pretty -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
succeeded -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Before -X- -X- O
Tet -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
unpopular -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
tolerable -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
majority -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Americans -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
loss -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
American -X- -X- O
lives -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
seen -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
cost -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
subduing -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
VC -X- -X- B-ORG
and -X- -X- O
NVA -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Tet -X- -X- O
made -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
clear -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
long -X- -X- O
way -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
over -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Americans -X- -X- O
thought -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
preserve -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
South -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
North -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
perfectly -X- -X- O
willing -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
suffer -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
losses -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
continue -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
fight -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

There -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
very -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
book -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
subject -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
written -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
General -X- -X- O
Vo -X- -X- B-PER
Nguyen -X- -X- I-PER
Giap -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

Try -X- -X- O
google -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
title -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
read -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

where -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
tours -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mekong -X- -X- B-LOC
Delta -X- -X- I-LOC
at -X- -X- O
reasonable -X- -X- O
prices -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

will -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Ho -X- -X- B-LOC
chi -X- -X- I-LOC
Minh -X- -X- I-LOC
for -X- -X- O
4 -X- -X- O
days -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
looking -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
1 -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
2 -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
trip -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Mekong -X- -X- B-LOC
delta -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
researching -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
line -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
things -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
quite -X- -X- O
pricey -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
tours -X- -X- O
look -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Should -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
settle -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
book -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
line -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

or -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
wait -X- -X- O
till -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
wait -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
tours -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
less -X- -X- O
money -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
same -X- -X- O
quality -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
tours -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

Also -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
tour -X- -X- O
recommendations -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
very -X- -X- O
helpful -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
well -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Thank -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
reliable -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
inexpensive -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
try -X- -X- O
Sinh -X- -X- B-LOC
Cafe -X- -X- I-LOC
/ -X- -X- I-LOC
Tourist -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
248 -X- -X- O
De -X- -X- O
Than -X- -X- O
St. -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
heart -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- B-LOC
back -X- -X- I-LOC
packer -X- -X- I-LOC
district -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
taken -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
tour -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
overnight -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
home -X- -X- O
stay -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
sweet -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
water -X- -X- O
market -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
wonderful -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
remember -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
exact -X- -X- O
cost -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
remember -X- -X- O
thinking -X- -X- O
how -X- -X- O
inexpensive -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Also -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Sinh -X- -X- B-LOC
Cafe -X- -X- I-LOC
has -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
around -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
long -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
very -X- -X- O
reputable -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

And -X- -X- O
no -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
work -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O
:) -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
satisfied -X- -X- O
customer -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

And -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
expect -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
party -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
tour -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
south -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
regular -X- -X- O
tourist -X- -X- O
towns -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Very -X- -X- O
few -X- -X- O
clubs -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
activities -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Oh -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
confused -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sinh -X- -X- B-LOC
Cafe -X- -X- I-LOC
is -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Cafe -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tour -X- -X- O
agency -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
own -X- -X- O
buses -X- -X- O
etc -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

tele -X- -X- O
# -X- -X- O
84838389593 -X- -X- O

have -X- -X- O
fun -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

There -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
see -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
delta -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
lifestyle -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
resort -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
're -X- -X- O
adventurous -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bus -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
water -X- -X- O
taxi -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
My -X- -X- B-LOC
Tho -X- -X- I-LOC
( -X- -X- O
near -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
live -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
Can -X- -X- B-LOC
Tho -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

From -X- -X- O
either -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
those -X- -X- O
cities -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
venture -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
spend -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
country -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Most -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
tourists -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
've -X- -X- O
come -X- -X- O
across -X- -X- O
buy -X- -X- O
tours -X- -X- O
along -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
My -X- -X- B-LOC
Tho -X- -X- I-LOC
waterfront -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

You -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
boat -X- -X- O
across -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
river -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
spend -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
biking -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
eating -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
local -X- -X- O
restaurant -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
buying -X- -X- O
souvenirs -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
doing -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
things -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
geared -X- -X- O
towards -X- -X- O
tourists -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
countryside -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
very -X- -X- O
beautiful -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
especially -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
few -X- -X- O
months -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
place -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

PS -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
make -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Thanh -X- -X- B-LOC
Pho -X- -X- I-LOC
Ben -X- -X- I-LOC
Tre -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
stay -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
friend -X- -X- O
Ken -X- -X- B-PER
's -X- -X- O
hotel -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
called -X- -X- O
Kiwi -X- -X- B-LOC
Heaven -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
across -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
river -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
Cho -X- -X- B-LOC
Ben -X- -X- I-LOC
Tre -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
little -X- -X- O
hard -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
foot -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
're -X- -X- O
rebuilding -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bridge -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
someone -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
moto -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
taxi -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
dollar -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
less -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
ex-pat -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
New -X- -X- B-LOC
Zealand -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
town -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
awhile -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
'll -X- -X- O
set -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
real -X- -X- O
tour -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
tourist -X- -X- O
fantasy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
trip -X- -X- O
where-ever -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
end -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
went -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
Intrepid -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
North -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
South -X- -X- O
Vietnam -X- -X- B-LOC
Trip -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
offer -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
separately -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
visited -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
made -X- -X- O
coconut -X- -X- O
candies -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
visited -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
local -X- -X- O
restaurant -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
attached -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
fish -X- -X- O
farm -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
rode -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
modified -X- -X- O
quad -X- -X- O
bikes -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
tropical -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
appeared -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
local -X- -X- O
hangout -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Intrepid -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
getting -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
away -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
touristy -X- -X- O
spots -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
showing -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
something -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
little -X- -X- O
different -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

what -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
unique -X- -X- O
customs -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
? -X- -X- O

As -X- -X- O
far -X- -X- O
ask -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
’m -X- -X- O
aware -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
unique -X- -X- O
custom -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
“ -X- -X- O
Country -X- -X- O
Wake -X- -X- O
” -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
travels -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
’ve -X- -X- O
never -X- -X- O
seen -X- -X- O
anything -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
often -X- -X- O
met -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
odd -X- -X- O
look -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
explain -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
foreigners -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
person -X- -X- O
dies -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
remains -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
“ -X- -X- O
waked -X- -X- O
” -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
home -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
roughly -X- -X- O
2 -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
3 -X- -X- O
days -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
visitors -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
come -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
house -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
pay -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
respects -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
desisted -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
couple -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
cups -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
tea -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sandwich -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bun -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
wake -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
included -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
sit -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
friends -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
sit -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
remains -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Wakes -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
common -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
north -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
south -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
boarder -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
Protestants -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Catholics -X- -X- O
alike -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

But -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
really -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
countryside -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
notable -X- -X- O
difference -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
noticed -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
south -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
one -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
wake -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
often -X- -X- O
held -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
chapel -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
funeral -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
tradition -X- -X- O
started -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
civil -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Another -X- -X- O
unique -X- -X- O
custom -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
dying -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- B-ORG
Pioneers -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- B-ORG
Pioneers -X- -X- I-ORG
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
organization -X- -X- O
started -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
end -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
19th -X- -X- O
century -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
pushed -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
supported -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ideal -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
temperance -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
abstaining -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
alcohol -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
attempt -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
deal -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
massive -X- -X- O
issue -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
alcoholism -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
gripped -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Pioneers -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
pledge -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
remain -X- -X- O
tee -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
total -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
hight -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
organization -X- -X- O
popularity -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
estimated -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
million -X- -X- O
members -X- -X- O
even -X- -X- O
filling -X- -X- O
Croke -X- -X- B-LOC
Park -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
25th -X- -X- O
anniversary -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
self -X- -X- O
am -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
appreciate -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
organization -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
unlikely -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
make -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
22nd -X- -X- O
century -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Orange -X- -X- O
Order -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
12th -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
July -X- -X- O
Marches -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
argued -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
Irish -X- -X- O
custom -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
unarguable -X- -X- O
ticks -X- -X- O
every -X- -X- O
criteria -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
considered -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
marches -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
12th -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
July -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
really -X- -X- O
attended -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
protestants -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Ulster -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
spite -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
largest -X- -X- O
attended -X- -X- O
paraded -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Barn -X- -X- O
brack -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ring -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

the -X- -X- O
irish -X- -X- O
customs -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
; -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
make -X- -X- O
sinnel -X- -X- O
cake -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
easter -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
barn -X- -X- O
brack -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
col -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
cannon -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Halloween -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

christmas -X- -X- O
cake -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
christmas -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

Would -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
recommend -X- -X- O
living -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Limerick -X- -X- B-LOC
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
student -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
've -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
given -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
opportunity -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
live -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Limerick -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
next -X- -X- O
year -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
course -X- -X- O
.. -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
Limerick -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
pros -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
cons -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

and -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
recommend -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
student -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
L.I.T -X- -X- B-LOC
is -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
close -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Moyross -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
yet -X- -X- O
again -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ppl -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
talk -X- -X- O
sh*t -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
Moyross -X- -X- B-LOC
still -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Limerick -X- -X- B-LOC
's -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
great -X- -X- O
student -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
loads -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
'll -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
spoilt -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
choice -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
fact -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
probably -X- -X- O
wo -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
ever -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
leave -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Orla -X- -X- B-PER
got -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Although -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
bad -X- -X- O
press -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
directing -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
AREA'S -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
limerick -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
nowhere -X- -X- O
near -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
university -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Limerick -X- -X- B-LOC
is -X- -X- O
such -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
full -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
shopping -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
life -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
career -X- -X- O
choices -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
social -X- -X- O
choices -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
came -X- -X- O
here -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
12 -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
ago -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
college -X- -X- O
..... -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Orla -X- -X- B-PER
got -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
spot -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
left -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
nor -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
now -X- -X- O
my -X- -X- O
home -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

Royal -X- -X- O
Caribbean -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
Carnival -X- -X- O
cruise -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

ONLY -X- -X- O
IF -X- -X- O
YOU -X- -X- O
HAVE -X- -X- O
BEEN -X- -X- O
ON -X- -X- O
BOARD -X- -X- O
* -X- -X- O
BOTH -X- -X- O
* -X- -X- O
!! -X- -X- O

i -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
know -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
liked -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
WHY -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

include -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
fun -X- -X- O
activities -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
teens -X- -X- O

- -X- -X- O
AND -X- -X- O
JUST -X- -X- O
MORE -X- -X- O
STUFF -X- -X- O
YOU -X- -X- O
LIKED -X- -X- O
OVERALL -X- -X- O

please -X- -X- O
specify -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
royal -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
carnival -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
(: -X- -X- O

Carnival -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Royal -X- -X- O
Caribbean -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
popular -X- -X- O
cruise -X- -X- O
lines -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
strong -X- -X- O
followings -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Some -X- -X- O
cruise -X- -X- O
aficionados -X- -X- O
refuse -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
sail -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Are -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
major -X- -X- O
differences -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

Explore -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
cruise -X- -X- O
may -X- -X- O
fit -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
needs -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

For -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
comparison -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
sailed -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
similar -X- -X- O
ships -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Carnival -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Royal -X- -X- O
Caribbean -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Itinerary -X- -X- O
Both -X- -X- O
ships -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Caribbean -X- -X- O
Islands -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
Jamaica -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Grand -X- -X- B-LOC
Cayman -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Cozumel -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
St. -X- -X- B-LOC
Thomas -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- B-LOC
Bahamas -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
St. -X- -X- B-LOC
Martin -X- -X- I-LOC
/ -X- -X- I-LOC
St. -X- -X- I-LOC
Maarten -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
visited -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
private -X- -X- O
island -X- -X- O
Half -X- -X- B-LOC
Moon -X- -X- I-LOC
Cay -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Puerto -X- -X- B-LOC
Rico -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Grand -X- -X- B-LOC
Turk -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
traveled -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
private -X- -X- O
island -X- -X- O
Coco -X- -X- B-LOC
Cay -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
Labadee -X- -X- B-LOC
( -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
north -X- -X- O
coast -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Haiti -X- -X- B-LOC
) -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
loved -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
locations -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ships -X- -X- O
visited -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
believe -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
should -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
distinguishing -X- -X- O
factor -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
deciding -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
cruise -X- -X- O
lines -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Shows -X- -X- O
Each -X- -X- O
night -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
variety -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
shows -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Usually -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
main -X- -X- O
show -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
entertainment -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
perhaps -X- -X- O
afterward -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
felt -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
main -X- -X- O
shows -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

On -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
liked -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
comedian -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
juggling -X- -X- O
act -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
love -X- -X- O
seeing -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
shows -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Royal -X- -X- O
Caribbean -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
main -X- -X- O
shows -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Carnival -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
slightly -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
comedians -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Dining -X- -X- O
Room -X- -X- O
We -X- -X- O
enjoyed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
atmosphere -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
dining -X- -X- O
rooms -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
felt -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
menu -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
little -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
variety -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Friendliness -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
staff -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
high -X- -X- O
grades -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
waiter -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
complained -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
trips -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
slightly -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
experience -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
feel -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
crews -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
excellent -X- -X- O
job -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
should -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
distinguishing -X- -X- O
factor -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
choosing -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
cruise -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Pools -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
salt -X- -X- O
water -X- -X- O
pools -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
cruise -X- -X- O
ships -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
pools -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
kids -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
adults -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
liked -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
pools -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
because -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
slide -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
kids -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
something -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
definitely -X- -X- O
enjoy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Spa -X- -X- O
We -X- -X- O
tried -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
spa -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Liberty -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
loved -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
try -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
spa -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mariner -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Usually -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
ca -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
wrong -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
getting -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
spa -X- -X- O
treatment -X- -X- O
...... -X- -X- O

Royal -X- -X- O
Caribbean -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
cruiseline -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
Regent -X- -X- O
Seven -X- -X- O
Seas -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Look -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
website -X- -X- O
rssc.com -X- -X- O

Royal -X- -X- O
Caribbean -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Carnival -X- -X- O
has -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
called -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
WalMart -X- -X- B-ORG
of -X- -X- O
cruise -X- -X- O
lines -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O

-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
travel -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
? -X- -X- O

My -X- -X- O
sister -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

I -X- -X- O
graduate -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
spring -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
'd -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
winter -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
too -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
tourists -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
since -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
'll -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
school -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
anytime -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
middle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
June -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
early -X- -X- O
November -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
want -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
too -X- -X- O
cold -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
sure -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
exactly -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
fall -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
... -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weather -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
really -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
autumn -X- -X- O
months -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
feel -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
need -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
middle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
summer -X- -X- O
either -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

We -X- -X- O
're -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
early -X- -X- O
20s -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
wanting -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
explore -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
beautiful -X- -X- O
country -X- -X- O
while -X- -X- O
we -X- -X- O
're -X- -X- O
still -X- -X- O
young -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
our -X- -X- O
lives -X- -X- O
start -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
even -X- -X- O
crazier -X- -X- O
! -X- -X- O

Can -X- -X- O
anyone -X- -X- O
give -X- -X- O
me -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
idea -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
us -X- -X- B-LOC
to -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
? -X- -X- O

People -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
on -X- -X- O
holiday -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weather -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
unpredictable -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

One -X- -X- O
thing -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
sure -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
Irish -X- -X- O
weather -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
how -X- -X- O
little -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
sure -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
may -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
shirtsleeves -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
sunglasses -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
February -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
winter -X- -X- O
woollies -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
March -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
even -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
summer -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

And -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rain -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
receives -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
lot -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
rain -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
certain -X- -X- O
areas -X- -X- O
getting -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
soaking -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
270 -X- -X- O
days -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
year -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

County -X- -X- B-LOC
Kerry -X- -X- I-LOC
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
worst -X- -X- O
affected -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
southeast -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
driest -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
enjoying -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
continental -X- -X- O
climate -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Irish -X- -X- O
weather -X- -X- O
works -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
‘ -X- -X- O
four -X- -X- O
seasons -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
’ -X- -X- O
principle -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
basic­ally -X- -X- O
means -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
ca -X- -X- O
n’t -X- -X- O
predict -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
thing -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
comes -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
behaviour -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
sky -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Some -X- -X- O
basic -X- -X- O
assumptions -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
however -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
made -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
summer -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
May -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
July -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
days -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
reasonably -X- -X- O
warm -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
– -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
importantly -X- -X- O
– -X- -X- O
very -X- -X- O
long -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
height -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
summer -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
wo -X- -X- O
n’t -X- -X- O
need -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
turn -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
lights -X- -X- O
until -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
10 -X- -X- O
pm -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
peak -X- -X- O
tourist -X- -X- O
season -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
means -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
far -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
people -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
everywhere -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
remote -X- -X- O
corners -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
island -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
prices -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
highest -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Not -X- -X- O
surprisingly -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
yearly -X- -X- O
festivals -X- -X- O
occur -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
these -X- -X- O
times -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
advantage -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
crowds -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
favourable -X- -X- O
weather -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Spring -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
February -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
April -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Autumn -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
August -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
October -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
make -X- -X- O
good -X- -X- O
alternatives -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
although -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
country -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
ever -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
growing -X- -X- O
popularity -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tourist -X- -X- O
destination -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
often -X- -X- O
blur -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
lines -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
mid -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
high -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
season -X- -X- O
tourism -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Still -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
chance -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
peace -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
quiet -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weather -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
surprisingly -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
April -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
September -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
mid-July -X- -X- O
– -X- -X- O
again -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
uncertainty -X- -X- O
principle -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Spring -X- -X- O
festivities -X- -X- O
include -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ever -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
popular -X- -X- O
St -X- -X- O
Patrick -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
Festival -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Although -X- -X- O
temperatures -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
often -X- -X- O
venture -X- -X- O
below -X- -X- O
freezing -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
winter -X- -X- O
( -X- -X- O
December -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
February -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
brutal -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
huge -X- -X- O
parts -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
country -X- -X- O
– -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
west -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
northwest -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
particular -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Crowds -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
thinnest -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
country -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
tourist -X- -X- O
attractions -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
services -X- -X- O
close -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
October -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n’t -X- -X- O
reopen -X- -X- O
until -X- -X- O
Easter -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
paradoxically -X- -X- O
leaves -X- -X- O
visitors -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
convincing -X- -X- O
taste -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
how -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
is -X- -X- O
experienced -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Irish -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
cold -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
grey -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
dark -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
5 -X- -X- O
pm -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
’s -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
pub -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rain -X- -X- O
starts -X- -X- O
sheeting -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
thing -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
bring -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
clothing -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
clothes -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
layer -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
cold -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
off -X- -X- O
layers -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
warms -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Waterproof -X- -X- O
clothing -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
footwear -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
essential -X- -X- O
plus -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
umbrella -X- -X- O
.. -X- -X- O

As -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
famous -X- -X- O
Scotsman -X- -X- O
Billy -X- -X- B-PER
Connolly -X- -X- I-PER
says -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
no -X- -X- O
such -X- -X- O
thing -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
bad -X- -X- O
weather -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
wrong -X- -X- O
clothes -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O

Afraid -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
can -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
helpful -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
really -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
case -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
pot -X- -X- O
luck -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
although -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weather -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
changeable -X- -X- O
often -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
cold -X- -X- O
wet -X- -X- O
morning -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
turn -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
lovely -X- -X- O
warm -X- -X- O
sunny -X- -X- O
afternoon -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
evening -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
visa -X- -X- O
versa -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

If -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
mean -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-LOC
of -X- -X- I-LOC
Ireland -X- -X- I-LOC
( -X- -X- O
Dublin -X- -X- B-LOC
) -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
anytime -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
summer -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
mild -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
US -X- -X- B-LOC
( -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
coming -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
US -X- -X- B-LOC
? -X- -X- O
) -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Their -X- -X- O
seasons -X- -X- O
are -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
same -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
countries -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Northern -X- -X- B-LOC
Hemisphere -X- -X- I-LOC
but -X- -X- O
I -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
suggest -X- -X- O
fall -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
does -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
pretty -X- -X- O
cold -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Ireland -X- -X- B-LOC
so -X- -X- O
going -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
winter -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
your -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
bet -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

September -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
example -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Rent -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
car -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
spend -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
couple -X- -X- O
days -X- -X- O
outside -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Dublin -X- -X- B-LOC
seeing -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
countryside -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
trip -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
lifetime -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

To -X- -X- O
explore -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
beautiful -X- -X- O
countryside -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
need -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
old -X- -X- O
enough -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
hire -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
car -X- -X- O
because -X- -X- O
public -X- -X- O
transport -X- -X- O
is -X- -X- O
expensive -X- -X- O
& -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
goes -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
far -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
main -X- -X- O
towns -X- -X- O
/ -X- -X- O
cities -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
rural -X- -X- O
places -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
n't -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bus -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
train -X- -X- O
service -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

You -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
stay -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- O
& -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bus -X- -X- O
tour -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
say -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Cliffs -X- -X- B-LOC
of -X- -X- I-LOC
Moher -X- -X- I-LOC
or -X- -X- O
Dingle -X- -X- B-LOC
peninsula -X- -X- I-LOC
but -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
tourists -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

By -X- -X- O
definition -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
tourists -X- -X- O
will -X- -X- O
go -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
places -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
might -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
put -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
few -X- -X- O
tourists -X- -X- O
along -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
way -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O
