Blind	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Alley	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
techniques	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
form	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
hand-to-hand	-X-	-X-	O
combat	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
Nar	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Kanji	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

Elements	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
system	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
integrated	-X-	-X-	O
into	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
hybrid	-X-	-X-	O
martial	-X-	-X-	O
arts	-X-	-X-	O
practiced	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Supreme	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Leader	-X-	-X-	I-PER
Snoke	-X-	-X-	I-PER
's	-X-	-X-	O
Elite	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Praetorian	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Guard	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Blinder	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
4B2	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
jamming	-X-	-X-	O
array	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
sensor	-X-	-X-	O
jammer	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Irilliad	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
commonly	-X-	-X-	O
installed	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
RZ-2	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
A-wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
interceptor	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
worked	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
conjunction	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
advanced	-X-	-X-	O
CloakEye	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
sensor	-X-	-X-	O
jammer	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
broadcast	-X-	-X-	O
data	-X-	-X-	O
bursts	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
disrupt	-X-	-X-	O
enemy	-X-	-X-	O
sensors	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
impede	-X-	-X-	O
detection	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Blissex-head	-X-	-X-	O
bit-drivers	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Pilex	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
bit	-X-	-X-	O
driver	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
could	-X-	-X-	O
be	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
scavenging	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Around	-X-	-X-	O
thirty	-X-	-X-	O
years	-X-	-X-	O
after	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Endor	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
scavenger	-X-	-X-	O
Rey	-X-	-X-	B-PER
carried	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
set	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Pilex	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
bit	-X-	-X-	O
drivers	-X-	-X-	O
including	-X-	-X-	O
both	-X-	-X-	O
Blissex-head	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
Wessex-head	-X-	-X-	O
bit-drivers	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
satchel	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
tools	-X-	-X-	O
while	-X-	-X-	O
she	-X-	-X-	O
lived	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Jakku	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

She	-X-	-X-	O
at	-X-	-X-	O
some	-X-	-X-	O
point	-X-	-X-	O
wrote	-X-	-X-	O
about	-X-	-X-	O
these	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
other	-X-	-X-	O
tools	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
survival	-X-	-X-	O
guide	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

After	-X-	-X-	O
she	-X-	-X-	O
fled	-X-	-X-	O
Jakku	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
with	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
former	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
stormtrooper	-X-	-X-	O
Finn	-X-	-X-	B-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
BB	-X-	-X-	O
unit	-X-	-X-	O
BB-8	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
YT-1300	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
light	-X-	-X-	O
freighter	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Millennium	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Falcon	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
Rey	-X-	-X-	B-PER
discovered	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
starship	-X-	-X-	O
's	-X-	-X-	O
motivator	-X-	-X-	O
needed	-X-	-X-	O
repair	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

While	-X-	-X-	O
fixing	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
she	-X-	-X-	O
had	-X-	-X-	O
Finn	-X-	-X-	B-PER
pass	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Pilex	-X-	-X-	O
driver	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Bunker	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Buster	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
shells	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
missiles	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
both	-X-	-X-	O
Armored	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Assault	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Tanks	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Separatist	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Droid	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
TX-130	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Saber-class	-X-	-X-	O
fighter	-X-	-X-	O
tanks	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Grand	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

At	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
point	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
AAT	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
used	-X-	-X-	O
these	-X-	-X-	O
shells	-X-	-X-	O
against	-X-	-X-	O
phase	-X-	-X-	O
II	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
troopers	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Changeling	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Mark	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
71NB	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
racing	-X-	-X-	O
starfighter	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Ace	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Squadron	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
pilot	-X-	-X-	O
Bo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Keevil	-X-	-X-	I-PER
flew	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Yellow	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Ace	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
New	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Era	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
community	-X-	-X-	O
junk	-X-	-X-	O
yard	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Mos	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Eisley	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
Tatooine	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
situated	-X-	-X-	O
directly	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
front	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
entrance	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
Chalmun	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
's	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
Cantina	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Crosshairs	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
98j	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
precision	-X-	-X-	O
holo-targeter	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
targeting	-X-	-X-	O
system	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Pallas	-X-	-X-	B-PER
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
RZ-2	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
A-wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
interceptor	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Defender	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
deflector	-X-	-X-	O
shield	-X-	-X-	O
projector	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
device	-X-	-X-	O
produced	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Chepat	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Combined	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
deflector	-X-	-X-	O
shield	-X-	-X-	O
generator	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
essential	-X-	-X-	O
component	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
BTL-A4	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Y-wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
assault	-X-	-X-	O
starfighter	-X-	-X-	O
/	-X-	-X-	O
bomber	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
T-65B	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
X-wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
starfighter	-X-	-X-	O
's	-X-	-X-	O
shielding	-X-	-X-	O
system	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Firecaller	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
light	-X-	-X-	O
flame	-X-	-X-	O
projector	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
flamethrower	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Merr-Sonn	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Munitions	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Inc.	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
banned	-X-	-X-	O
throughout	-X-	-X-	O
most	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
civilized	-X-	-X-	O
space	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Such	-X-	-X-	O
weapons	-X-	-X-	O
had	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
very	-X-	-X-	O
limited	-X-	-X-	O
fuel	-X-	-X-	O
supply	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Firecaller	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
relied	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
accelerite	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
unstable	-X-	-X-	O
starship	-X-	-X-	O
fuel	-X-	-X-	O
ingredient	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
burned	-X-	-X-	O
hotter	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
longer	-X-	-X-	O
than	-X-	-X-	O
most	-X-	-X-	O
substances	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

However	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
this	-X-	-X-	O
substance	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
easily	-X-	-X-	O
acquired	-X-	-X-	O
around	-X-	-X-	O
shipyards	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
fuel	-X-	-X-	O
depots	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Accelerite	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
enabled	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
weapon	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
spray	-X-	-X-	O
far	-X-	-X-	O
less	-X-	-X-	O
fuel	-X-	-X-	O
than	-X-	-X-	O
most	-X-	-X-	O
projectors	-X-	-X-	O
per	-X-	-X-	O
burst	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
flames	-X-	-X-	O
quickly	-X-	-X-	O
ignited	-X-	-X-	O
surrounding	-X-	-X-	O
materials	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Favored	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
vilest	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
beings	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Firecaller	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
generated	-X-	-X-	O
intense	-X-	-X-	O
heat	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
caused	-X-	-X-	O
terrible	-X-	-X-	O
pain	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
horrible	-X-	-X-	O
disfigurements	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
those	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
survive	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Gundark	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
scav-suit	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
creation	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
Arkanian	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
engineer	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
made	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
support	-X-	-X-	O
salvagers	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
assessing	-X-	-X-	O
lost	-X-	-X-	O
technology	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Huttsplitter	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
rifle	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
hand-crafted	-X-	-X-	O
personal	-X-	-X-	O
weapon	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Tasu	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Leech	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
leader	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
criminal	-X-	-X-	O
gang	-X-	-X-	O
Kanjiklub	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Leech	-X-	-X-	B-PER
brought	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
while	-X-	-X-	O
trying	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
reclaim	-X-	-X-	O
money	-X-	-X-	O
owed	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Han	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Solo	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
owner	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Baleen-class	-X-	-X-	O
heavy	-X-	-X-	O
freighter	-X-	-X-	O
Eravana	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

He	-X-	-X-	O
then	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
weapon	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
defend	-X-	-X-	O
himself	-X-	-X-	O
from	-X-	-X-	O
rathtars	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
attacked	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
men	-X-	-X-	O
onboard	-X-	-X-	O
Solo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
's	-X-	-X-	O
vessel	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

A	-X-	-X-	O
Jakku	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Night	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Special	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
rifle	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
rifle	-X-	-X-	O
owned	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
arms	-X-	-X-	O
dealer	-X-	-X-	O
Sarco	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Plank	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
operated	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Jakku	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Multi	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Imager	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
dedicated	-X-	-X-	O
energy	-X-	-X-	O
receptor	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
device	-X-	-X-	O
produced	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Melihat	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
along	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Fabritech	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
ANs-5d	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
lock	-X-	-X-	O
track	-X-	-X-	O
full-spectrum	-X-	-X-	O
transceiver	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Tana	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Ire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
electro-photo	-X-	-X-	O
receptor	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
comprise	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
T-65B	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
X-wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
starfighters	-X-	-X-	O
sensor	-X-	-X-	O
system	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Reb	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Squadron	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Resistance	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
squadron	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
V-4X-D	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
ski	-X-	-X-	O
speeders	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
fought	-X-	-X-	O
against	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Order	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Crait	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

Confronted	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
armed	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
after	-X-	-X-	O
taking	-X-	-X-	O
shelter	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
abandoned	-X-	-X-	O
Rebel	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Alliance	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
outpost	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Resistance	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
attempted	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
delay	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
attack	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
destroying	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
enemy	-X-	-X-	O
's	-X-	-X-	O
superlaser	-X-	-X-	O
siege	-X-	-X-	O
cannon	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Captain	-X-	-X-	O
Poe	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Dameron	-X-	-X-	I-PER
led	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
makeshift	-X-	-X-	O
sortie	-X-	-X-	O
against	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
besiegers	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
squadron	-X-	-X-	O
ultimately	-X-	-X-	O
failed	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
destroy	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
cannon	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Despite	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
loss	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Nodin	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Chavdri	-X-	-X-	I-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
Pammich	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Nerro	-X-	-X-	I-PER
Goode	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
rest	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
squadron	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
evacuated	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Millennium	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Falcon	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
with	-X-	-X-	O
help	-X-	-X-	O
from	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Rey	-X-	-X-	I-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Renegade	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
heavy	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
pistol	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
heavy	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
pistol	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
SoroSuub	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Corporation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
occupied	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
niche	-X-	-X-	O
similar	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
design	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
T-6	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Thunderer	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	O
BlasTech	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Industries	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
C-10	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Dragoneye	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Reaper	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	O
Czerka	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Arms	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
featured	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
highest	-X-	-X-	O
energy	-X-	-X-	O
output	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
any	-X-	-X-	O
SoroSuub	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
pistol	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

More	-X-	-X-	O
lightweight	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
better	-X-	-X-	O
priced	-X-	-X-	O
than	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
competition	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Renegade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
dominated	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
super-heavy	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
pistol	-X-	-X-	O
market	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
however	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
most	-X-	-X-	O
enthusiasts	-X-	-X-	O
eschewed	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
mass-market	-X-	-X-	O
weapon	-X-	-X-	O
due	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
poor	-X-	-X-	O
beam	-X-	-X-	O
cohesion	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
awkwardly	-X-	-X-	O
angeled	-X-	-X-	O
grip	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
preferred	-X-	-X-	O
pricier	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
higher-quality	-X-	-X-	O
options	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Screamer	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
sensor	-X-	-X-	O
jammer	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
sensor	-X-	-X-	O
jammer	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Bertriak	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
commonly	-X-	-X-	O
installed	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
T-65	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
X-wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
starfighter	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
created	-X-	-X-	O
noise	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
electromagnetic	-X-	-X-	O
spectrum	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
could	-X-	-X-	O
confuse	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
tracking	-X-	-X-	O
systems	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
TIE	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Fighters	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
or	-X-	-X-	O
seeker	-X-	-X-	O
missiles	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
snubble	-X-	-X-	O
special	-X-	-X-	O
pistol	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
just	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
snubble	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
black-colored	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
double-snub	-X-	-X-	O
nosed	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
pistol	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
had	-X-	-X-	O
limited	-X-	-X-	O
ammunition	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
packed	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
powerful	-X-	-X-	O
punch	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
included	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
stun	-X-	-X-	O
setting	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Grindalid	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Moloch	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
lieutenant	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
White	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Worms	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
gang	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
favored	-X-	-X-	O
using	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
snubble	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
equipped	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
scope	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
built	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
luma-compensators	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

He	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
disabled	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
stu	-X-	-X-	O
setting	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
pistol	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
ensure	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
always	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
lethal	-X-	-X-	O
force	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Subduer-9	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Riot	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Blaster	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
long-ranged	-X-	-X-	O
scatterblaster	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
SoroSuub	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Corporation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
most	-X-	-X-	O
common	-X-	-X-	O
law	-X-	-X-	O
enforcement	-X-	-X-	O
scatterblasters	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
galaxy	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Although	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
heavier	-X-	-X-	O
at	-X-	-X-	O
six	-X-	-X-	O
kilograms	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
not	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
manageable	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
standard	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
rifles	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
riot	-X-	-X-	O
blasters	-X-	-X-	O
could	-X-	-X-	O
subdue	-X-	-X-	O
large	-X-	-X-	O
groups	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
civilians	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Subduer-9	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
could	-X-	-X-	O
emit	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
wide	-X-	-X-	O
cone	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
stun	-X-	-X-	O
blasts	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
rendered	-X-	-X-	O
targets	-X-	-X-	O
unconscious	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
made	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
easy	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
place	-X-	-X-	O
them	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
binders	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
awaken	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
prison	-X-	-X-	O
cells	-X-	-X-	O
hours	-X-	-X-	O
later	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
cost	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Subduer-9	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
1,250	-X-	-X-	O
credits	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

An	-X-	-X-	O
award	-X-	-X-	O
colloquially	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
belt	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
presented	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
champions	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
Naval	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Corps	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Boxing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
combat	-X-	-X-	O
sport	-X-	-X-	O
practiced	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
naval	-X-	-X-	O
cadets	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Wasp	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
rifle	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
name	-X-	-X-	O
Razoo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Qin-Fee	-X-	-X-	I-PER
gave	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
customized	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
rifle	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
black	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
external	-X-	-X-	O
accelerator	-X-	-X-	O
barrel	-X-	-X-	O
cage	-X-	-X-	O
crudely	-X-	-X-	O
painted	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
yellow	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
pump	-X-	-X-	O
action	-X-	-X-	O
gas	-X-	-X-	O
compressor	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
reload	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Wessex-head	-X-	-X-	O
bit-drivers	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Pilex	-X-	-X-	O
bit	-X-	-X-	O
driver	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
could	-X-	-X-	O
be	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
scavenging	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Many	-X-	-X-	O
years	-X-	-X-	O
later	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Triple-Zero	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
discovered	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
memories	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
disgusted	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
circumstances	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
created	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Shortly	-X-	-X-	O
afterward	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Laxo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
killed	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
raid	-X-	-X-	O
brought	-X-	-X-	O
down	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Spanjaf	-X-	-X-	B-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

0-0	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
-	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
0	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
simply	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
Triple-Zero	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
or	-X-	-X-	O
just	-X-	-X-	O
Trip	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
protocol	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
designed	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
specialize	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
etiquette	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
customs	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
translation	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
torture	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

He	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
awoken	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Doctor	-X-	-X-	O
Aphra	-X-	-X-	B-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	O
Lord	-X-	-X-	O
Darth	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Vader	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
proceeded	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
perform	-X-	-X-	O
various	-X-	-X-	O
missions	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
two	-X-	-X-	O
alongside	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
fellow	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
companion	-X-	-X-	O
BT-1	-X-	-X-	B-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

After	-X-	-X-	O
Aphra	-X-	-X-	B-PER
faked	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
own	-X-	-X-	O
death	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
BT-1	-X-	-X-	B-PER
continued	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
roam	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
galaxy	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

A	-X-	-X-	O
male	-X-	-X-	O
individual	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
scientist	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
accidentally	-X-	-X-	O
created	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Triple-Zero	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
protocol	-X-	-X-	O
personality	-X-	-X-	O
matrix	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

When	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
added	-X-	-X-	O
cooperative	-X-	-X-	O
algorithms	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
matrix	-X-	-X-	O
—	-X-	-X-	O
including	-X-	-X-	O
morality	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
empathy	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
equability	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
loyalty	-X-	-X-	O
—	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
realized	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
subverting	-X-	-X-	O
them	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
fast	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
they	-X-	-X-	O
developed	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
making	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
personality	-X-	-X-	O
psychotic	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

While	-X-	-X-	O
fascinated	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
creation	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
individual	-X-	-X-	O
saw	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
reject	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
ordering	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
assistant	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
discard	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
trash	-X-	-X-	O
compactor	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

However	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
personality	-X-	-X-	O
matrix	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
control	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
assistant	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
body	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
escaping	-X-	-X-	O
destruction	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Many	-X-	-X-	O
years	-X-	-X-	O
later	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Triple-Zero	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
discovered	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
memories	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
disgusted	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
circumstances	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
created	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
0-LT	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
utility	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
utility	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
use	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
war	-X-	-X-	O
between	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Resistance	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
equipped	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
treaded	-X-	-X-	O
foot	-X-	-X-	O
pads	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
repurposed	-X-	-X-	O
domes	-X-	-X-	O
from	-X-	-X-	O
obsolete	-X-	-X-	O
astromech	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
models	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
009	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Fastshot	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
hair	-X-	-X-	O
trigger	-X-	-X-	O
produced	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
BlasTech	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Industries	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
03-R	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
cryogenic	-X-	-X-	O
power	-X-	-X-	O
cell	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
power	-X-	-X-	O
cell	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Thiodyne	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
along	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Novaldex	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
power	-X-	-X-	O
generator	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
power	-X-	-X-	O
BTL-A4	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Y-wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
assault	-X-	-X-	O
starfighter	-X-	-X-	O
/	-X-	-X-	O
bombers	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
04-Z	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
cryogenic	-X-	-X-	O
power	-X-	-X-	O
generator	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
power	-X-	-X-	O
generator	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Novaldex	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
use	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
T-65B	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
X-wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
starfighters	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

07	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
tractor	-X-	-X-	O
beam	-X-	-X-	O
projectors	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
tractor	-X-	-X-	O
beam	-X-	-X-	O
projector	-X-	-X-	O
produced	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
company	-X-	-X-	O
Phylon	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Ten	-X-	-X-	O
07s	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
were	-X-	-X-	O
included	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
armaments	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
I-class	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Star	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Destroyers	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

08	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Separatist	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
BX-series	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
commando	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
participated	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Rishi	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
moon	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	O
where	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
subsequently	-X-	-X-	O
destroyed	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

09	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Separatist	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
BX-series	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
commando	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
participated	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Rishi	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
moon	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	O
where	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
subsequently	-X-	-X-	O
destroyed	-X-	-X-	O
along	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
Unit	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
07	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
08	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

090192	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
spy	-X-	-X-	O
ship	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Confederacy	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Independent	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Systems	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
against	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

During	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
war	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
T-series	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
military	-X-	-X-	O
strategic	-X-	-X-	O
analysis	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
tactics	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
TX-532	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
utilized	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
starship	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
secret	-X-	-X-	O
operation	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
following	-X-	-X-	O
events	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
place	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
1	-X-	-X-	O
ABY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
3278	-X-	-X-	O
LY	-X-	-X-	O
according	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Lothal	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
7978	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
C	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
R	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
C	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
following	-X-	-X-	O
events	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
place	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
or	-X-	-X-	O
around	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
1	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
3276	-X-	-X-	O
LY	-X-	-X-	O
according	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Lothal	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
7976	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
C	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
R	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
C	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
1	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
4	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
FD	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
P-Tower	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
simply	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
P-Tower	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
light	-X-	-X-	O
fixed	-X-	-X-	O
anti-vehicle	-X-	-X-	O
weapon	-X-	-X-	O
emplacement	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Atgar	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
SpaceDefense	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Corporation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
held	-X-	-X-	O
enough	-X-	-X-	O
power	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
disable	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
AT-ST	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
rugged	-X-	-X-	O
dependability	-X-	-X-	O
meant	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
could	-X-	-X-	O
function	-X-	-X-	O
even	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
harshest	-X-	-X-	O
environments	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
following	-X-	-X-	O
events	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
place	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
10	-X-	-X-	O
ABY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
3287	-X-	-X-	O
LY	-X-	-X-	O
according	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Lothal	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
7987	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
C	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
R	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
C	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
following	-X-	-X-	O
events	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
place	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
10	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
3267	-X-	-X-	O
LY	-X-	-X-	O
according	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Lothal	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
7967	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
C	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
R	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
C	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
following	-X-	-X-	O
events	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
place	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
or	-X-	-X-	O
around	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
100	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
3177	-X-	-X-	O
LY	-X-	-X-	O
according	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Lothal	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
81	-X-	-X-	O
BFE	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
7877	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
C	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
R	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
C	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

100	-X-	-X-	O
level	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
levels	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Death	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Star	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

Shortly	-X-	-X-	O
before	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
station	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
destruction	-X-	-X-	O
at	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Yavin	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
explosion	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
reported	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
100	-X-	-X-	O
level	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
following	-X-	-X-	O
events	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
place	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
101	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
approximately	-X-	-X-	O
3176	-X-	-X-	O
LY	-X-	-X-	O
according	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Lothal	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
82	-X-	-X-	O
BFE	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
7876	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
C	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
R	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
C	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
following	-X-	-X-	O
events	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
place	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
or	-X-	-X-	O
around	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
1014	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
2263	-X-	-X-	O
LY	-X-	-X-	O
according	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Lothal	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
6963	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
C	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
R	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
C	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
calendar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

1044	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Chapel	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
warehouse	-X-	-X-	O
building	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
industrial	-X-	-X-	O
quarter	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Capital	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
City	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Lothal	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
on	-X-	-X-	O
Chapel	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Street	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

During	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
crackdown	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Yahenna	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Laxo	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
head	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Gray	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Syndicate	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
had	-X-	-X-	O
Rosey	-X-	-X-	B-PER
move	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
poet	-X-	-X-	O
Holshef	-X-	-X-	B-PER
to	-X-	-X-	O
this	-X-	-X-	O
location	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Holshef	-X-	-X-	B-PER
had	-X-	-X-	O
been	-X-	-X-	O
paying	-X-	-X-	O
Laxo	-X-	-X-	O
credits	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
keep	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
hidden	-X-	-X-	O
from	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Empire	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
when	-X-	-X-	O
Laxo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
sold	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
bounty	-X-	-X-	O
hunter	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
informed	-X-	-X-	O
Merei	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Spanjaf	-X-	-X-	I-PER
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
location	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
told	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
take	-X-	-X-	O
bounty	-X-	-X-	O
hunter	-X-	-X-	O
there	-X-	-X-	O
so	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
could	-X-	-X-	O
collect	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
bounty	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Shortly	-X-	-X-	O
afterward	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Laxo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
killed	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
raid	-X-	-X-	O
brought	-X-	-X-	O
down	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Spanjaf	-X-	-X-	B-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
104th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Battalion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Wolf	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Pack	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Battalion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
or	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Wolfpack	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Battalion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
trooper	-X-	-X-	O
military	-X-	-X-	O
battalion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Grand	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
104th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
led	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	O
General	-X-	-X-	O
Plo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Koon	-X-	-X-	I-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	O
Commander	-X-	-X-	O
CC-3636	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
trooper	-X-	-X-	O
nickname	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Wolffe	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
throughout	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
105th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Battalion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
battalion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
military	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Stormtrooper	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Corps	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Consisting	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
troopers	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Jetpack	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Troopers	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
—	-X-	-X-	O
elite	-X-	-X-	O
soldiers	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
army	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Eternal	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
—	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
105th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
war	-X-	-X-	O
between	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Resistance	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
strict	-X-	-X-	O
command	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Kylo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Ren	-X-	-X-	I-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Knights	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Ren	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
108th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
unit	-X-	-X-	O
within	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
armed	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
active	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Civil	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
War	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
following	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Endor	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
situated	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Gordian	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Reach	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Outer	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Rim	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
Territories	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
Colonel	-X-	-X-	O
Madrighast	-X-	-X-	B-PER
unsuccessfully	-X-	-X-	O
sought	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
have	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
204th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Imperial	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Fighter	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Wing	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
join	-X-	-X-	O
before	-X-	-X-	O
moving	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
regroup	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
108th	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

11-3K	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
viper	-X-	-X-	O
probe	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
variant	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Viper	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
probe	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Vandor	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

They	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
commonly	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
investigation	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
exploration	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
reconnaissance	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

They	-X-	-X-	O
included	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
rotating	-X-	-X-	O
blaster	-X-	-X-	O
collar	-X-	-X-	O
assembly	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
articulated	-X-	-X-	O
manipulator	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
sampling	-X-	-X-	O
claws	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

11-4D	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
protocol	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
service	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Darth	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Plagueis	-X-	-X-	I-PER
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
years	-X-	-X-	O
before	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
rise	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Some	-X-	-X-	O
time	-X-	-X-	O
before	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
Plagueis	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
killed	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
apprentice	-X-	-X-	O
Darth	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Sidious	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
11-4D	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
as	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
inheritance	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
went	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
faithfully	-X-	-X-	O
serve	-X-	-X-	O
Sidious	-X-	-X-	B-PER
for	-X-	-X-	O
many	-X-	-X-	O
years	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

1138	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
human	-X-	-X-	O
male	-X-	-X-	O
stormtrooper	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
military	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
decades	-X-	-X-	O
after	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Civil	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
War	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

He	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
members	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
FN	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Corps	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
participated	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
attack	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
Tuanul	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
village	-X-	-X-	O
located	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Jakku	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

After	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
attack	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
1138	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
checked	-X-	-X-	O
areas	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
village	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
fellow	-X-	-X-	O
stormtrooper	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
ordered	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
colleague	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
fan	-X-	-X-	O
out	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
their	-X-	-X-	O
search	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
second	-X-	-X-	O
complied	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

1138	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
B1-series	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
serving	-X-	-X-	O
under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Droid	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Crisis	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

1138	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
took	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Naboo	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
command	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
OOM-9	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
able	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
create	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
victory	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Federation	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
this	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
short	-X-	-X-	O
lived	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
every	-X-	-X-	O
Federation	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
shut	-X-	-X-	O
down	-X-	-X-	O
when	-X-	-X-	O
Anakin	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Skywalker	-X-	-X-	I-PER
destroyed	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Droid	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Control	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Ship	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
above	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

After	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
melted	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
be	-X-	-X-	O
remade	-X-	-X-	O
into	-X-	-X-	O
fence	-X-	-X-	O
posts	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
garden	-X-	-X-	O
trellises	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
art	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

1151	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
cadet	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Youth	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Brigade	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

1174	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
nicknamed	-X-	-X-	O
Whiplash	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
trooper	-X-	-X-	O
cadet	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Youth	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Brigade	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
12	-X-	-X-	O
stage	-X-	-X-	O
dynamo	-X-	-X-	O
power	-X-	-X-	O
generator	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
power	-X-	-X-	O
generator	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Libertine	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
sported	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
such	-X-	-X-	O
device	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

121-247	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
mining	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
resided	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
Anoat	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
at	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
time	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Iron	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Blockade	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

During	-X-	-X-	O
this	-X-	-X-	O
time	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Tam	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Bastion	-X-	-X-	I-PER
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Alliance	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
to	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Restore	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
sent	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
young	-X-	-X-	O
smuggler	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
disable	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
smuggler	-X-	-X-	O
succeeded	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
doing	-X-	-X-	O
so	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

1234	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
B1-series	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Droid	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

During	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	O
Crisis	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
1234	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
fought	-X-	-X-	O
against	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Gungan	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Grand	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
at	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Great	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Grass	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
Plains	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
destroyed	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Bombad	-X-	-X-	O
General	-X-	-X-	O
Jar	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Jar	-X-	-X-	I-PER
Binks	-X-	-X-	I-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
125-Z	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
treadspeeder	-X-	-X-	O
bike	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
speeder	-X-	-X-	O
bike	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
saw	-X-	-X-	O
service	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
war	-X-	-X-	O
between	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Resistance	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
125-Zr	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
repulsor	-X-	-X-	O
unit	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
repulsorlift	-X-	-X-	O
produced	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Aratech	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Repulsor	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Company	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
125-Zr	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
First	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
125-Z	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
treadspeeder	-X-	-X-	O
bikes	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Aratech-Loratus	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Corporation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
commanded	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	O
General	-X-	-X-	O
Jaro	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Tapal	-X-	-X-	I-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	O
Commander	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
fought	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Bracca	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Invasion	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
later	-X-	-X-	O
participated	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
implementation	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Order	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
66	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
against	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
resulted	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
death	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Tapal	-X-	-X-	B-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
entire	-X-	-X-	O
unit	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
well	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
destruction	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Albedo	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Brave	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

An	-X-	-X-	O
individual	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
14th	-X-	-X-	O
Atrisian	-X-	-X-	O
Emperor	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Kitel	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Phard	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
name	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Elite	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Praetorian	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Guard	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
First	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Order	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
traced	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
roots	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
this	-X-	-X-	O
individual	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
14th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Sector	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Fleet	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Navy	-X-	-X-	O
active	-X-	-X-	O
between	-X-	-X-	O
14	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
4	-X-	-X-	O
ABY	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Lieutenant	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Ralchio	-X-	-X-	I-PER
Nervi	-X-	-X-	I-PER
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
sector	-X-	-X-	O
fleet	-X-	-X-	O
before	-X-	-X-	O
coming	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
attention	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Grand	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Moff	-X-	-X-	I-PER
Ravik	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
governor	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Tolonda	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Oversector	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

Due	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
Ralchio	-X-	-X-	B-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
marriage	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
Lila	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Nervi	-X-	-X-	I-PER
from	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
influential	-X-	-X-	O
Nervi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
family	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
Lila	-X-	-X-	B-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
lobbying	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
Ravik	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
Ralchio	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
promoted	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
military	-X-	-X-	O
rank	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
captain	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
became	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
commanding	-X-	-X-	O
officer	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
own	-X-	-X-	O
naval	-X-	-X-	O
task	-X-	-X-	O
force	-X-	-X-	O
prior	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Xorrn	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
150	-X-	-X-	O
general	-X-	-X-	O
orders	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
set	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
orders	-X-	-X-	O
memorized	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
each	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
trooper	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Grand	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Along	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Republic	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Supreme	-X-	-X-	I-PER
Chancellor	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Security	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Council	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Galactic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Senate	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
could	-X-	-X-	O
activate	-X-	-X-	O
any	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
orders	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
1550-LEX	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
yacht	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
yacht	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
after	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Civil	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
War	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

One	-X-	-X-	O
such	-X-	-X-	O
ship	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Serendipity	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
belonged	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
Delia	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Leighton	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
featured	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
cantina	-X-	-X-	O
inside	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
15th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Deep	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Core	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Reserve	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Fleet	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Navy	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
reserve	-X-	-X-	O
fleet	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
service	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
command	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Admiral	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Yzu	-X-	-X-	I-PER
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Empire	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
reign	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
lasted	-X-	-X-	O
from	-X-	-X-	O
19	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
5	-X-	-X-	O
ABY	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Due	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
strategic	-X-	-X-	O
nature	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Empress	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Teta	-X-	-X-	I-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
resources	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
well	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
position	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
gateway	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
galaxy	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Deep	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Core	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
region	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
important	-X-	-X-	O
stronghold	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Empire	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

1647	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
date	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
calendar	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
saw	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
establishment	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Commerce	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Treaty	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
1647	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
agreement	-X-	-X-	O
between	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
to	-X-	-X-	O
ensure	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
latter	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
neutrality	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
times	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
war	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

1647	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
dated	-X-	-X-	O
prior	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
blockade	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Pantora	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
21	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
17th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Legion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Tanis	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Legion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
legion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Eternal	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
comprising	-X-	-X-	O
five-thousand	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
troopers	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Inspired	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
history	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
ancient	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
legion	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
named	-X-	-X-	O
after	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Lord	-X-	-X-	O
Darth	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Tanis	-X-	-X-	I-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
181st	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Fighter	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Wing	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
fighter	-X-	-X-	O
wing	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Starfighter	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Corps	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
group	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
red	-X-	-X-	O
stripes	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
adorned	-X-	-X-	O
their	-X-	-X-	O
starfighters	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
menacing	-X-	-X-	O
display	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
their	-X-	-X-	O
victims	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
inspired	-X-	-X-	O
fellow	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
squadrons	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
adopt	-X-	-X-	O
similar	-X-	-X-	O
designs	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

1933	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
B1-series	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Baktoid	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Combat	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Automata	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
who	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Droid	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

In	-X-	-X-	O
32	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
deployed	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
capital	-X-	-X-	O
city	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Theed	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
invasion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

1933	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
group	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
led	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
OOM	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
command	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
2163	-X-	-X-	B-PER
that	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
tasked	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
guarding	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Royal	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Starship	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Theed	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Hangar	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Corellian	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
1D	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
servo	-X-	-X-	O
turret	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
type	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
laser	-X-	-X-	O
turret	-X-	-X-	O
found	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
stock	-X-	-X-	O
Corellian	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Engineering	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Corporation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG

YT-2400	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
light	-X-	-X-	O
freighters	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
YT-2400	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
had	-X-	-X-	O
two	-X-	-X-	O
double	-X-	-X-	O
laser	-X-	-X-	O
cannons	-X-	-X-	O
mounted	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
dorsal	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
ventral	-X-	-X-	O
1D	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
servo	-X-	-X-	O
turrets	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

1MSE-KUP24	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
KUP24	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
messenger	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
forced	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
work	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
criminal	-X-	-X-	O
Pyke	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Syndicate	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
spices	-X-	-X-	O
mines	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Kessel	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
reign	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

In	-X-	-X-	O
10	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
1MSE-KUP24	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
present	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
mines	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
control	-X-	-X-	O
room	-X-	-X-	O
when	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
taken	-X-	-X-	O
over	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
group	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
criminals	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
started	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
revolution	-X-	-X-	O
against	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Pykes	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

2	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
000	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Senators	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
propaganda	-X-	-X-	O
poster	-X-	-X-	O
created	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
female	-X-	-X-	O
Ukian	-X-	-X-	O
artist	-X-	-X-	O
Kas	-X-	-X-	B-PER
unloDos	-X-	-X-	I-PER
for	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Confederacy	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Independent	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Systems	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
evoked	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
sentiment	-X-	-X-	O
common	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
Ukio	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
that	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
not	-X-	-X-	O
worth	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
membership	-X-	-X-	O
because	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
dispassionate	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
distant	-X-	-X-	O
Senate	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
poster	-X-	-X-	O
depicted	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Senate	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Building	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
at	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
time	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
had	-X-	-X-	O
text	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
both	-X-	-X-	O
High	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Galactic	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
Aurebesh	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Aurebesh	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
stated	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
The	-X-	-X-	O
winds	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
liberty	-X-	-X-	O
are	-X-	-X-	O
blowing	-X-	-X-	O
this	-X-	-X-	O
way	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
can	-X-	-X-	O
you	-X-	-X-	O
feel	-X-	-X-	O
them	-X-	-X-	O
?,	-X-	-X-	O
while	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
High	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Galactic	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
at	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
top	-X-	-X-	O
stated	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
There	-X-	-X-	O
are	-X-	-X-	O
2000	-X-	-X-	O
senators	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
this	-X-	-X-	O
building	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
slightly	-X-	-X-	O
below	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
None	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
them	-X-	-X-	O
care	-X-	-X-	O
about	-X-	-X-	O
you	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Written	-X-	-X-	O
at	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
very	-X-	-X-	O
bottom	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
poster	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
High	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Galactic	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
Confederacy	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Independent	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Systems	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Along	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
FX-7	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
2-1B	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
stationed	-X-	-X-	O
at	-X-	-X-	O
Echo	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Base	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
on	-X-	-X-	O
Hoth	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
and	-X-	-X-	O
treated	-X-	-X-	O
Luke	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Skywalker	-X-	-X-	I-PER
with	-X-	-X-	O
bacta	-X-	-X-	O
after	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
had	-X-	-X-	O
been	-X-	-X-	O
attacked	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
wampa	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

2-1B	-X-	-X-	B-PER
also	-X-	-X-	O
treated	-X-	-X-	O
Skywalker	-X-	-X-	B-PER
after	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
hand	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
amputated	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
duel	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
Darth	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Vader	-X-	-X-	I-PER
on	-X-	-X-	O
Bespin	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

2-1B	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Delta	-X-	-X-	I-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
masculine-programmed	-X-	-X-	O
2-1B	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
-	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
series	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
medical	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
initially	-X-	-X-	O
belonged	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

While	-X-	-X-	O
working	-X-	-X-	O
throughout	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
military	-X-	-X-	O
prison	-X-	-X-	O
system	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
developed	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
aversion	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
damage	-X-	-X-	O
done	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
organic	-X-	-X-	O
flesh	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
weapons	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
eventually	-X-	-X-	O
prompted	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
flee	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Once	-X-	-X-	O
free	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
took	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Delta	-X-	-X-	B-PER
moniker	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
show	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
not	-X-	-X-	O
merely	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
cog	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
system	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

2-1B	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
-	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
series	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
medical	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
2-1B	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
surgical	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
medical	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
common	-X-	-X-	O
throughout	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
galaxy	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Civil	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
War	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
2-M	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Saber-class	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
repulsortank	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
or	-X-	-X-	O
2-M	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Hover	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Tank	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
repulsorlift	-X-	-X-	O
tank	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Equipped	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
powerful	-X-	-X-	O
laser	-X-	-X-	O
cannons	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
excelled	-X-	-X-	O
against	-X-	-X-	O
heavily	-X-	-X-	O
fortified	-X-	-X-	O
defenses	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
slow	-X-	-X-	O
speed	-X-	-X-	O
left	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
vulnerable	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
rocket	-X-	-X-	O
turrets	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Thanks	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
shield	-X-	-X-	O
generator	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Saber-class	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
had	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
exceptional	-X-	-X-	O
beam	-X-	-X-	O
defense	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
ground-based	-X-	-X-	O
vehicle	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Saber-class	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
repulsortank	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
spawned	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
scout	-X-	-X-	O
variant	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Scout-class	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
2-M	-X-	-X-	O
repulsor	-X-	-X-	O
tank	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
2-MAL	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
personal	-X-	-X-	O
comlink	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
comlink	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Crozo	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

A	-X-	-X-	O
cheap	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
simple	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
yet	-X-	-X-	O
efficient	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
communications	-X-	-X-	O
device	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
commonly	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
soldiers	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Alliance	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
to	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Restore	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Jyn	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Erso	-X-	-X-	I-PER
notably	-X-	-X-	O
carried	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
at	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
time	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Operation	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Fracture	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
20-T	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Railcrawler	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
conveyex	-X-	-X-	O
transport	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
ATD-C45	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
or	-X-	-X-	O
simply	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
conveyex	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
heavily	-X-	-X-	O
armored	-X-	-X-	O
cargo	-X-	-X-	O
train	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Kuat	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Drive	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Yards	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
saw	-X-	-X-	O
action	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
reign	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

200	-X-	-X-	O
level	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
levels	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Death	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Star	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

Shortly	-X-	-X-	O
before	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
station	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
destruction	-X-	-X-	O
at	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Yavin	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
explosion	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
reported	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
200	-X-	-X-	O
level	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
201st	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Squadron	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
infantry	-X-	-X-	O
squadron	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
active	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
or	-X-	-X-	O
prior	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
14	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
led	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
General	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Markon	-X-	-X-	I-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

During	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
time	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
201st	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
and	-X-	-X-	O
Markon	-X-	-X-	B-PER
were	-X-	-X-	O
dispatched	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
Zeffo	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	O
where	-X-	-X-	O
they	-X-	-X-	O
evicted	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
civilians	-X-	-X-	O
from	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
village	-X-	-X-	O
using	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Code	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
94364	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
204th	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Imperial	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Fighter	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Wing	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
Shadow	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Wing	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
fighter	-X-	-X-	O
wing	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
navy	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
formed	-X-	-X-	O
at	-X-	-X-	O
least	-X-	-X-	O
twenty	-X-	-X-	O
years	-X-	-X-	O
before	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
hunt	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
Shadow	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Empire	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
earliest	-X-	-X-	O
volunteer	-X-	-X-	O
wings	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Eventually	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
became	-X-	-X-	O
one	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Empire	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
best	-X-	-X-	O
fighter	-X-	-X-	O
wings	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

It	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
primary	-X-	-X-	O
focus	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
putting	-X-	-X-	O
down	-X-	-X-	O
rebel	-X-	-X-	O
insurgency	-X-	-X-	O
like	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Rebel	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Alliance	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Shadow	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
earned	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
name	-X-	-X-	O
after	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Orinda	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Massacre	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
carried	-X-	-X-	O
out	-X-	-X-	O
bombardments	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
Mennar-Daye	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
and	-X-	-X-	O
Mek	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
'	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
tradi	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

After	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Hoth	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
in	-X-	-X-	O
3	-X-	-X-	O
ABY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Squadron	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Five	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	O
Shadow	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wing	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
fought	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
new	-X-	-X-	O
independent	-X-	-X-	O
faction	-X-	-X-	O
led	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
Admiral	-X-	-X-	O
Gratloe	-X-	-X-	B-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
escaped	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
Gratloe	-X-	-X-	B-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial-class	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Star	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Destroyer	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Celerity	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
20m-cp	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Strobe	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
/	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
C-Beam	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Lamp	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
model	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
starship	-X-	-X-	O
floodlight	-X-	-X-	O
manufactured	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Gelieg	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Han	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Solo	-X-	-X-	I-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
YT-1300	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
light	-X-	-X-	O
freighter	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Millennium	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Falcon	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
had	-X-	-X-	O
two	-X-	-X-	O
such	-X-	-X-	O
lamps	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
forward	-X-	-X-	O
mandibles	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
212th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Attack	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Battalion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
212th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Legion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
military	-X-	-X-	O
battalion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Grand	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
army	-X-	-X-	O
engineered	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
serve	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Led	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
General	-X-	-X-	O
Obi-Wan	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Kenobi	-X-	-X-	I-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
subordinate	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	O
Commander	-X-	-X-	O
CC-2224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Cody	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
212th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
fought	-X-	-X-	O
against	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Confederacy	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Independent	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Systems	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
throughout	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

By	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
third	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
last	-X-	-X-	O
year	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
conflict	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
212th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
led	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
invasion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Separatist-controlled	-X-	-X-	O
world	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Utapau	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	O
engaging	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
army	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
while	-X-	-X-	O
Kenobi	-X-	-X-	B-PER
hunted	-X-	-X-	O
General	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Grievous	-X-	-X-	I-PER
in	-X-	-X-	O
order	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
end	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
war	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

Although	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Master	-X-	-X-	I-PER
completed	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
task	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
killing	-X-	-X-	O
Grievous	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
ultimately	-X-	-X-	O
betrayed	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
soldiers	-X-	-X-	O
upon	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
activation	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Order	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
66	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
protocol	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
called	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
extermination	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
all	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
clones	-X-	-X-	O
failed	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
execute	-X-	-X-	O
their	-X-	-X-	O
former	-X-	-X-	O
leader	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
however	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
212th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Recon	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Division	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
subunit	-X-	-X-	O
under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
212th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Attack	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Battalion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
mobilized	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Grand	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

Under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
command	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	O
General	-X-	-X-	O
Obi-Wan	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Kenobi	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
unit	-X-	-X-	O
participated	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Second	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Battle	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Geonosis	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
when	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
invaded	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
regain	-X-	-X-	O
control	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

2163	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
OOM	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
command	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
within	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Droid	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Invasion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

In	-X-	-X-	O
32	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
attempted	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
stop	-X-	-X-	O
Qui-Gon	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Jinn	-X-	-X-	I-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
Queen	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Amidala	-X-	-X-	I-PER
from	-X-	-X-	O
going	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
Coruscant	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
ended	-X-	-X-	O
up	-X-	-X-	O
being	-X-	-X-	O
bisected	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
instead	-X-	-X-	O
alongside	-X-	-X-	O
1933	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
and	-X-	-X-	O
7169	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

His	-X-	-X-	O
death	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
vain	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
Jinn	-X-	-X-	B-PER
ended	-X-	-X-	O
up	-X-	-X-	O
eventually	-X-	-X-	O
going	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
Coruscant	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
21st	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Nova	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Corps	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
also	-X-	-X-	O
known	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Marines	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
prominent	-X-	-X-	O
military	-X-	-X-	O
unit	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
troopers	-X-	-X-	O
noted	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
their	-X-	-X-	O
unique	-X-	-X-	O
armor	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
relentlessness	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
combat	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
corps	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Grand	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
the	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Galactic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
as	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
4th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Sector	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
leadership	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
General	-X-	-X-	O
Ki-Adi	-X-	-X-	B-PER
-	-X-	-X-	I-PER
Mundi	-X-	-X-	I-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
Marshal	-X-	-X-	O
Commander	-X-	-X-	O
CC-1138	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Bacara	-X-	-X-	I-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

Prior	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
conclusion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
marines	-X-	-X-	O
fought	-X-	-X-	O
Separatist	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Alliance	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
droid	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Mygeeto	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Campaign	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
where	-X-	-X-	O
they	-X-	-X-	O
received	-X-	-X-	O
Order	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
66	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
causing	-X-	-X-	O
Mundi	-X-	-X-	B-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
men	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
betray	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
kill	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
battlefield	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

22	-X-	-X-	O
pickup	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
term	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
describe	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
maneuver	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
individual	-X-	-X-	O
would	-X-	-X-	O
hide	-X-	-X-	O
within	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
cargo	-X-	-X-	O
container	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
would	-X-	-X-	O
then	-X-	-X-	O
be	-X-	-X-	O
magnetically	-X-	-X-	O
picked	-X-	-X-	O
up	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
starship	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
crew	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Ghost	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
ran	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
22	-X-	-X-	O
pickup	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
their	-X-	-X-	O
mission	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
rescue	-X-	-X-	O
Wookiee	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
prisoners	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Spice	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Mines	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
of	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
Kessel	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

While	-X-	-X-	O
Kanan	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Jarrus	-X-	-X-	I-PER
held	-X-	-X-	O
off	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	O
troops	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
lightsaber	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Garazeb	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Orrelios	-X-	-X-	I-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
Sabine	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Wren	-X-	-X-	I-PER
led	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Wookiee	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
prisoners	-X-	-X-	O
into	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
cargo	-X-	-X-	O
container	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

That	-X-	-X-	O
container	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
then	-X-	-X-	O
picked	-X-	-X-	O
up	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Ghost	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
piloted	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
Hera	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Syndulla	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
crew	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
prisoners	-X-	-X-	O
successfully	-X-	-X-	O
escaped	-X-	-X-	O
Kessel	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
OOM	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
command	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Separatist	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Droid	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Confederacy	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Independent	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Systems	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

Shortly	-X-	-X-	O
after	-X-	-X-	O
being	-X-	-X-	O
promoted	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
deployed	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
moon	-X-	-X-	O
Rugosa	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
command	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Separatist	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Supreme	-X-	-X-	O
Leader	-X-	-X-	O
Asajj	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Ventress	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
where	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
led	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
army	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
attempt	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
stop	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Grand	-X-	-X-	O
Master	-X-	-X-	O
Yoda	-X-	-X-	B-PER
from	-X-	-X-	O
meeting	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
King	-X-	-X-	O
Katuunko	-X-	-X-	B-PER
of	-X-	-X-	O
Toydaria	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

After	-X-	-X-	O
failing	-X-	-X-	O
numerous	-X-	-X-	O
attempts	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
kill	-X-	-X-	O
Yoda	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
and	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
met	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	O
Master	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
came	-X-	-X-	O
out	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
hiding	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
sit	-X-	-X-	O
calmly	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
front	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Armored	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Assault	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Tank	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
ruse	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
not	-X-	-X-	O
anticipated	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Separatist	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
however	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
after	-X-	-X-	O
224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
contacted	-X-	-X-	O
Asajj	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Ventress	-X-	-X-	I-PER
for	-X-	-X-	O
clarification	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
commander	-X-	-X-	O
gave	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
order	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
fire	-X-	-X-	O
upon	-X-	-X-	O
Yoda	-X-	-X-	O
which	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
delayed	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
his	-X-	-X-	O
units	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
leading	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
trooper	-X-	-X-	O
ambush	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Confederate	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
forces	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
Yoda	-X-	-X-	B-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
dismantling	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
was	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
designation	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
human	-X-	-X-	O
male	-X-	-X-	O
officer	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Coruscant	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Security	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Force	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
underworld	-X-	-X-	O
police	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

On	-X-	-X-	O
Coruscant	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Level	-X-	-X-	O
1313	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
confronted	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
criminal	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
both	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
criminal	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
224	-X-	-X-	B-PER
were	-X-	-X-	O
grabbed	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
sarlacc	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
pulled	-X-	-X-	O
away	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
224th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Imperial	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Armored	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Division	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
previously	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
224th	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Clone	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
division	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
under	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
,	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
unit	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
service	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
reign	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

2296	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
designation	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
OOM-series	-X-	-X-	O
security	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Droid	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

In	-X-	-X-	O
32	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
stationed	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
board	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
modified	-X-	-X-	O
Lucrehulk-class	-X-	-X-	O
LH-3210	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
cargo	-X-	-X-	O
freighter	-X-	-X-	O
Saak	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
'	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
ak	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
while	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
starship	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
blockade	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

During	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
blockade	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
2296	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
freighter	-X-	-X-	O
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
hangar	-X-	-X-	O
when	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Consular-class	-X-	-X-	O
cruiser	-X-	-X-	O
Radiant	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
VII	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
arrived	-X-	-X-	O
carrying	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
pair	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
ambassadors	-X-	-X-	O
from	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Republic	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

2391	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
designation	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
an	-X-	-X-	O
OOM-series	-X-	-X-	O
security	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
that	-X-	-X-	O
served	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
Droid	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

In	-X-	-X-	O
32	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
stationed	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
board	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
modified	-X-	-X-	O
Lucrehulk-class	-X-	-X-	O
LH-3210	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
cargo	-X-	-X-	O
freighter	-X-	-X-	O
Saak	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
'	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
ak	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
while	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
starship	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
blockade	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Dowutin	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
big	-X-	-X-	O
game	-X-	-X-	O
hunter	-X-	-X-	O
Grummgar	-X-	-X-	B-PER
used	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
242	-X-	-X-	O
hunting	-X-	-X-	O
rifle	-X-	-X-	O
while	-X-	-X-	O
illegally	-X-	-X-	O
hunting	-X-	-X-	O
molsumes	-X-	-X-	O
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	O
Ithor	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

While	-X-	-X-	O
conversing	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
fellow	-X-	-X-	O
hunter	-X-	-X-	O
Nysorly	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
Grummgar	-X-	-X-	B-PER
shot	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
molsume	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
rifle	-X-	-X-	O
when	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
attempted	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
attack	-X-	-X-	O
Nysorly	-X-	-X-	B-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

Ironically	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Nysorly	-X-	-X-	B-PER
shot	-X-	-X-	O
Grummgar	-X-	-X-	B-PER
'	-X-	-X-	O
s	-X-	-X-	O
speeder	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
nearly	-X-	-X-	O
killed	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
response	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
having	-X-	-X-	O
been	-X-	-X-	O
unaware	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
molsume	-X-	-X-	O
behind	-X-	-X-	O
her	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

261	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
black-and	-X-	-X-	O
-	-X-	-X-	O
gold	-X-	-X-	O
R-series	-X-	-X-	O
astromech	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
masculine	-X-	-X-	O
programming	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
service	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

At	-X-	-X-	O
some	-X-	-X-	O
point	-X-	-X-	O
before	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Yavin	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
261	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
among	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
many	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
used	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
maintain	-X-	-X-	O
operations	-X-	-X-	O
aboard	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Death	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Star	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
battle	-X-	-X-	O
station	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

However	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
astromech	-X-	-X-	O
went	-X-	-X-	O
rogue	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
stealing	-X-	-X-	O
secret	-X-	-X-	O
documents	-X-	-X-	O
and	-X-	-X-	O
escaping	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
Lambda-class	-X-	-X-	O
T-4a	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
shuttle	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
Imperials	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
then	-X-	-X-	O
hired	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trandoshan	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
bounty	-X-	-X-	O
hunter	-X-	-X-	O
Bossk	-X-	-X-	B-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
who	-X-	-X-	O
traced	-X-	-X-	O
261	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
to	-X-	-X-	O
Tatooine	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
and	-X-	-X-	O
retrieved	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
from	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
clan	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Jawas	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
rogue	-X-	-X-	O
astromech	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
then	-X-	-X-	O
escorted	-X-	-X-	O
back	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Empire	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

2638	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
B1-series	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Droid	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Confederacy	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Independent	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Systems	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
that	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
active	-X-	-X-	O
during	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Clone	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Wars	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

In	-X-	-X-	O
19	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
2638	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
involved	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Battle	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
of	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Utapau	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
where	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
fired	-X-	-X-	O
near	-X-	-X-	O
Republic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Jedi	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
General	-X-	-X-	O
Obi-Wan	-X-	-X-	B-PER
Kenobi	-X-	-X-	I-PER
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
blasted	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
clone	-X-	-X-	O
troopers	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

264	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
readapted	-X-	-X-	O
R4	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
astromech	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
working	-X-	-X-	O
for	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Press	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Corps	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
as	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
communications	-X-	-X-	O
courier	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
taken	-X-	-X-	O
prisoner	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
crew	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Ghost	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
so	-X-	-X-	O
their	-X-	-X-	O
own	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
Chopper	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
,	-X-	-X-	O
could	-X-	-X-	O
pose	-X-	-X-	O
as	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
courier	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
rebels	-X-	-X-	O
considered	-X-	-X-	O
keeping	-X-	-X-	O
him	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
but	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
thrown	-X-	-X-	O
out	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Ghost	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
by	-X-	-X-	O
Chopper	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
.	-X-	-X-	O

They	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
given	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
name	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Sith	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Lord	-X-	-X-	O
Tenebrous	-X-	-X-	B-PER
.	-X-	-X-	O

2767	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
B1-series	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Trade	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Federation	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Droid	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O

In	-X-	-X-	O
32	-X-	-X-	O
BBY	-X-	-X-	O
,	-X-	-X-	O
he	-X-	-X-	O
was	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
forces	-X-	-X-	O
deployed	-X-	-X-	O
to	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
city	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
Theed	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
on	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
planet	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Naboo	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Federation	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
during	-X-	-X-	O
its	-X-	-X-	O
invasion	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
world	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

2767	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
part	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
group	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
led	-X-	-X-	O
by	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
OOM	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
command	-X-	-X-	O
battle	-X-	-X-	O
droid	-X-	-X-	O
2163	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
that	-X-	-X-	O
were	-X-	-X-	O
tasked	-X-	-X-	O
with	-X-	-X-	O
guarding	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Naboo	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
Royal	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
Starship	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Theed	-X-	-X-	B-LOC
Hangar	-X-	-X-	I-LOC
.	-X-	-X-	O

27th	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
generation	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
droidspeak	-X-	-X-	I-MISC
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
compressed	-X-	-X-	O
variant	-X-	-X-	O
of	-X-	-X-	O
standard	-X-	-X-	O
droidspeak	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

BB-series	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
astromech	-X-	-X-	O
droids	-X-	-X-	O
like	-X-	-X-	O
BB-8	-X-	-X-	B-MISC
spoke	-X-	-X-	O
it	-X-	-X-	O
.	-X-	-X-	O

The	-X-	-X-	O
291st	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Legion	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
was	-X-	-X-	O
a	-X-	-X-	O
legion	-X-	-X-	O
in	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Imperial	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Army	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
of	-X-	-X-	O
the	-X-	-X-	O
Galactic	-X-	-X-	B-ORG
Empire	-X-	-X-	I-ORG
.	-X-	-X-	O