Blind B-LOC
Alley I-LOC
techniques O
were O
a O
form O
of O
hand-to-hand O
combat O
used O
on O
Nar B-LOC
Kanji I-LOC
. O

Elements O
of O
that O
system O
were O
integrated O
into O
the O
hybrid O
martial O
arts O
practiced O
by O
Supreme B-PER
Leader I-PER
Snoke I-PER
's O
Elite B-ORG
Praetorian I-ORG
Guard I-ORG
. O

The B-MISC
Blinder I-MISC
4B2 I-MISC
jamming O
array O
was O
a O
type O
of O
sensor O
jammer O
manufactured O
by O
Irilliad B-ORG
and O
was O
commonly O
installed O
on O
the O
RZ-2 B-MISC
A-wing I-MISC
interceptor O
. O

It O
worked O
in O
conjunction O
with O
an O
advanced O
CloakEye B-MISC
sensor O
jammer O
that O
broadcast O
data O
bursts O
to O
disrupt O
enemy O
sensors O
and O
impede O
detection O
. O

Blissex-head O
bit-drivers O
were O
a O
type O
of O
Pilex B-MISC
bit O
driver O
which O
could O
be O
used O
for O
scavenging O
. O

Around O
thirty O
years O
after O
the O
Battle B-MISC
of I-MISC
Endor I-MISC
, O
the O
scavenger O
Rey B-PER
carried O
a O
set O
of O
Pilex B-MISC
bit O
drivers O
including O
both O
Blissex-head O
and O
Wessex-head O
bit-drivers O
in O
her O
satchel O
of O
tools O
while O
she O
lived O
on O
the O
planet O
Jakku B-LOC
. O

She O
at O
some O
point O
wrote O
about O
these O
and O
her O
other O
tools O
in O
her O
survival O
guide O
. O

After O
she O
fled O
Jakku B-LOC
with O
the O
former O
First B-ORG
Order I-ORG
stormtrooper O
Finn B-PER
and O
the O
BB O
unit O
BB-8 B-MISC
on O
the O
YT-1300 B-MISC
light O
freighter O
known O
as O
the O
Millennium B-MISC
Falcon I-MISC
, O
Rey B-PER
discovered O
that O
the O
starship O
's O
motivator O
needed O
repair O
. O

While O
fixing O
it O
she O
had O
Finn B-PER
pass O
her O
a O
Pilex O
driver O
. O

Bunker B-MISC
Buster I-MISC
shells O
were O
missiles O
used O
by O
both O
Armored B-MISC
Assault I-MISC
Tanks I-MISC
of O
the O
Separatist B-ORG
Droid I-ORG
Army I-ORG
and O
TX-130 B-MISC
Saber-class O
fighter O
tanks O
of O
the O
Grand B-ORG
Army I-ORG
of I-ORG
the I-ORG
Republic I-ORG
. O

At O
one O
point O
, O
an O
AAT B-MISC
used O
these O
shells
against O
phase O
II O
clone O
troopers O
. O

The O
Changeling B-MISC
Mark I-MISC
71NB I-MISC
was O
a O
type O
of O
racing O
starfighter O
. O

Ace B-ORG
Squadron I-ORG
pilot O
Bo B-PER
Keevil I-PER
flew O
one O
, O
the O
Yellow B-MISC
Ace I-MISC
, O
during O
the O
New B-MISC
Republic I-MISC
Era I-MISC
. O

The O
community O
junk O
yard O
of O
Mos B-LOC
Eisley I-LOC
, I-LOC
Tatooine I-LOC
, O
was O
situated O
directly O
in O
front O
of O
the O
entrance O
to O
Chalmun B-LOC
's I-LOC
Cantina I-LOC
. O

The O
Crosshairs B-MISC
98j I-MISC
precision O
holo-targeter O
was O
a O
targeting O
system O
manufactured O
by O
Pallas B-PER
that O
was O
used O
in O
the O
RZ-2 B-MISC
A-wing I-MISC
interceptor O
. O

The O
Defender B-MISC
deflector O
shield O
projector O
was O
a O
device O
produced O
by O
Chepat B-ORG
. O

Combined O
with O
a O
deflector O
shield O
generator O
, O
it O
was O
an O
essential O
component O
in O
a O
BTL-A4 B-MISC
Y-wing I-MISC
assault O
starfighter O
/ O
bomber O
and O
T-65B B-MISC
X-wing I-MISC
starfighter O
's O
shielding O
system O
. O

The O
Firecaller B-MISC
light O
flame O
projector O
was O
a O
type O
of O
flamethrower O
manufactured O
by O
Merr-Sonn B-ORG
Munitions I-ORG
, I-ORG
Inc. I-ORG
that O
was O
banned O
throughout O
most O
of O
civilized O
space O
. O

Such O
weapons O
had O
a O
very O
limited O
fuel O
supply O
, O
but O
the O
Firecaller B-MISC
relied O
on O
accelerite O
, O
an O
unstable O
starship O
fuel O
ingredient O
that O
burned O
hotter O
and O
longer O
than O
most O
substances O
. O

However O
, O
this O
substance O
was O
easily O
acquired O
around O
shipyards O
and O
fuel O
depots O
. O

Accelerite B-MISC
enabled O
the O
weapon O
to O
spray O
far O
less O
fuel O
than O
most O
projectors O
per O
burst O
, O
as O
the O
flames O
quickly O
ignited O
surrounding O
materials O
. O

Favored O
by O
the O
vilest O
of O
beings O
, O
the O
Firecaller B-MISC
generated O
intense O
heat O
that O
caused O
terrible O
pain O
and O
horrible O
disfigurements O
for O
those O
who O
survive O
. O

The O
Gundark B-MISC
scav-suit O
was O
a O
creation O
by O
an O
Arkanian B-LOC
engineer O
, O
made O
to O
support O
salvagers O
in O
assessing O
lost O
technology O
. O

The O
Huttsplitter B-MISC
blaster O
rifle O
was O
the O
hand-crafted O
personal O
weapon O
of O
Tasu B-PER
Leech I-PER
, O
leader O
of O
the O
criminal O
gang O
Kanjiklub B-ORG
. O

Leech B-PER
brought O
it O
with O
him O
while O
trying O
to O
reclaim O
money O
owed O
to O
him O
by O
Han B-PER
Solo I-PER
, O
owner O
of O
the O
Baleen-class O
heavy O
freighter O
Eravana B-MISC
. O

He O
then O
used O
the O
weapon O
to O
defend O
himself O
from O
rathtars O
that O
attacked O
him O
and O
his O
men O
onboard O
Solo B-PER
's O
vessel O
. O

A O
Jakku B-MISC
Night I-MISC
Special I-MISC
blaster O
rifle O
was O
a O
type O
of O
blaster O
rifle O
owned O
by O
the O
arms O
dealer O
Sarco B-PER
Plank I-PER
, O
who O
operated O
on O
the O
planet O
Jakku B-LOC
. O

The O
Multi B-MISC
Imager I-MISC
dedicated O
energy O
receptor O
was O
a O
device O
produced O
by O
Melihat B-ORG
. O

It O
was O
used O
along O
with O
a O
Fabritech B-MISC
ANs-5d I-MISC
lock O
track O
full-spectrum O
transceiver O
and O
a O
Tana B-ORG
Ire I-ORG
electro-photo O
receptor O
to O
comprise O
a O
T-65B B-MISC
X-wing I-MISC
starfighters O
sensor O
system O
. O

Reb B-ORG
Squadron I-ORG
was O
a O
Resistance B-ORG
squadron O
of O
V-4X-D B-MISC
ski O
speeders O
that O
fought O
against O
the O
First B-MISC
Order I-MISC
during O
the O
Battle B-MISC
of I-MISC
Crait I-MISC
. O

Confronted O
by O
the O
armed O
forces O
of O
the O
First B-ORG
Order I-ORG
after O
taking O
shelter O
in O
an O
abandoned O
Rebel B-ORG
Alliance I-ORG
outpost O
, O
the O
Resistance B-ORG
attempted O
to O
delay O
the O
attack O
by O
destroying O
the O
enemy O
's O
superlaser O
siege O
cannon O
. O

Captain O
Poe B-PER
Dameron I-PER
led O
the O
makeshift O
sortie O
against O
the O
besiegers O
, O
but O
his O
squadron O
ultimately O
failed O
to O
destroy O
the O
cannon O
. O

Despite O
the O
loss O
of O
Nodin B-PER
Chavdri I-PER
and O
Pammich B-PER
Nerro I-PER
Goode I-PER
, O
the O
rest O
of O
the O
squadron O
was O
evacuated O
on O
the O
Millennium B-MISC
Falcon I-MISC
with O
help O
from O
the O
Jedi B-PER
Rey I-PER
. O

The O
Renegade B-MISC
heavy O
blaster O
pistol O
was O
a O
type O
of O
heavy O
blaster O
pistol O
manufactured O
by O
SoroSuub B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
. O

It O
occupied O
a O
niche O
similar O
in O
design O
to O
that O
of O
the O
T-6 B-MISC
Thunderer I-MISC
of O
BlasTech B-ORG
Industries I-ORG
and O
the O
C-10 B-MISC
Dragoneye I-MISC
Reaper I-MISC
of O
Czerka B-ORG
Arms I-ORG
, O
and O
it O
featured O
the O
highest O
energy O
output O
of O
any O
SoroSuub B-ORG
blaster O
pistol O
model O
. O

More O
lightweight O
and O
better O
priced O
than O
its O
competition O
, O
the O
Renegade B-ORG
dominated O
the O
super-heavy O
blaster O
pistol O
market O
, O
however O
, O
most O
enthusiasts O
eschewed O
the O
mass-market O
weapon O
due O
to O
its O
poor O
beam O
cohesion O
and O
awkwardly O
angeled O
grip O
, O
and O
preferred O
pricier O
but O
higher-quality O
options O
. O

The O
Screamer B-MISC
sensor O
jammer O
was O
a O
sensor O
jammer O
manufactured O
by O
Bertriak B-ORG
and O
was O
commonly O
installed O
on O
the O
T-65 B-MISC
X-wing I-MISC
starfighter O
. O

It O
created O
noise O
on O
the O
electromagnetic O
spectrum O
that O
could O
confuse O
the O
tracking O
systems O
of O
TIE B-MISC
Fighters I-MISC
or O
seeker O
missiles O
. O

The O
snubble O
special O
pistol O
, O
also O
known O
as O
just O
the O
snubble O
, O
was O
a O
black-colored O
model O
of O
double-snub O
nosed O
blaster O
pistol O
. O

The O
blaster O
had O
limited O
ammunition O
but O
packed O
a O
powerful O
punch O
and O
included O
a O
stun O
setting O
. O

The O
Grindalid B-PER
Moloch I-PER
, O
a O
lieutenant O
of O
the O
White B-ORG
Worms I-ORG
gang O
, O
favored O
using O
a O
snubble O
that O
was O
equipped O
with O
a O
scope O
with O
built O
in O
luma-compensators O
. O

He O
also O
disabled O
the O
stu O
setting O
on O
his O
pistol O
to O
ensure O
he O
always O
used O
lethal O
force O
. O

The B-MISC
Subduer-9 I-MISC
Riot I-MISC
Blaster I-MISC
was O
a O
type O
of O
long-ranged O
scatterblaster O
manufactured O
by O
SoroSuub B-ORG
Corporation I-ORG
, O
and O
was O
one O
of O
the O
most O
common O
law O
enforcement O
scatterblasters O
in O
the O
galaxy O
. O

Although O
it O
was O
heavier O
at O
six O
kilograms O
and O
not O
as O
manageable O
as O
standard O
blaster O
rifles O
, O
riot O
blasters O
could O
subdue O
large O
groups O
of O
civilians O
. O

The O
Subduer-9 B-MISC
could O
emit O
a O
wide O
cone O
of O
stun O
blasts O
, O
which O
rendered O
targets O
unconscious O
and O
made O
it O
easy O
to O
place O
them O
in O
binders O
and O
awaken O
in O
prison O
cells O
hours O
later O
. O

The O
cost O
of O
the O
Subduer-9 B-MISC
was O
1,250 O
credits O
. O

An O
award O
colloquially O
known O
as O
the O
belt O
was O
presented O
to O
champions O
in O
Naval B-MISC
Corps I-MISC
Boxing I-MISC
, O
a O
combat O
sport O
practiced O
by O
Imperial O
naval O
cadets O
. O

The O
Wasp B-MISC
blaster O
rifle O
was O
the O
name O
Razoo B-PER
Qin-Fee I-PER
gave O
to O
his O
customized O
blaster O
rifle O
. O

It O
was O
black O
with O
an O
external O
accelerator O
barrel O
cage O
crudely O
painted O
in O
yellow O
and O
used O
a O
pump O
action O
gas O
compressor O
to O
reload O
. O

Wessex-head O
bit-drivers O
were O
a O
type O
of O
Pilex O
bit O
driver
which O
could O
be O
used O
for O
scavenging O
. O

Many O
years O
later O
, O
Triple-Zero B-MISC
discovered O
his O
memories O
and O
was O
disgusted O
by O
the O
circumstances O
in O
which O
he O
was O
created O
. O

Shortly O
afterward O
, O
Laxo B-PER
was O
killed O
in O
an O
Imperial O
raid O
brought O
down O
by O
Spanjaf B-PER
. O