-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
sealer -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tool -X- -X- O
Rey -X- -X- B-PER
used -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
fix -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Millennium -X- -X- B-MISC
Falcon -X- -X- I-MISC
when -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
motivator -X- -X- O
went -X- -X- O
bad -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
hard -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Finn -X- -X- B-PER
to -X- -X- O
locate -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
aid -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
BB-8 -X- -X- B-MISC
, -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
able -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
give -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Rey -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
seallia -X- -X- B-MISC
sandwich -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
toasted -X- -X- O
sandwich -X- -X- O
dish -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
breakfast -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Devaronian -X- -X- O
chef -X- -X- O
Sama -X- -X- B-PER
Macoy -X- -X- I-PER
served -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
double-toasted -X- -X- O
seallia -X- -X- B-MISC
sandwich -X- -X- I-MISC
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
heavy -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
sweet -X- -X- O
blood -X- -X- O
syrup -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
entry -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
round -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
cooking -X- -X- O
competition -X- -X- O
meant -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
determine -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
next -X- -X- O
sous-chef -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
castle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
pirate -X- -X- O
Maz -X- -X- B-PER
Kanata -X- -X- I-PER
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Takodana -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Artiodac -X- -X- O
Strono -X- -X- B-PER
Tuggs -X- -X- I-PER
who -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
head -X- -X- O
chef -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
castle -X- -X- B-LOC
considered -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
sandwich -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
favourite -X- -X- O
entry -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
round -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
tasked -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
contestants -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
creating -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
breakfast -X- -X- O
platter -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sean -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
Padawan -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
active -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
High -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- O
Era -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sean -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
brought -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-LOC
Temple -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
Coruscant -X- -X- B-LOC
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
child -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
younglings -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
trained -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Master -X- -X- I-PER
Oslord -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

There -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
began -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
train -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
abilities -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Force -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
lacked -X- -X- O
behind -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
peers -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
85 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
age -X- -X- O
fourteen -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
seen -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
somewhat -X- -X- O
controversial -X- -X- O
move -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
famed -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
talented -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Master -X- -X- I-PER
Mostema -X- -X- I-PER
took -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Padawan -X- -X- O
learner -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sean -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
constructed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
Padawan -X- -X- O
Sean -X- -X- B-PER
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
High -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- O
Era -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
search -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Ezra -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
voyage -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Unknown -X- -X- B-LOC
Regions -X- -X- I-LOC
undertaken -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mandalorian -X- -X- O
Spectre -X- -X- O
Sabine -X- -X- B-PER
Wren -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
former -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
Padawan -X- -X- O
Ahsoka -X- -X- B-PER
Tano -X- -X- I-PER
to -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
Ezra -X- -X- B-PER
Bridger -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Padawan -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
friend -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
theirs -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Years -X- -X- O
earlier -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Liberation -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Lothal -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Bridger -X- -X- B-PER
had -X- -X- O
summoned -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
pod -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
purrgil -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
defeat -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Seventh -X- -X- O
Fleet -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
those -X- -X- O
starships -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
dealt -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
animals -X- -X- O
attacked -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- B-MISC
Destroyer -X- -X- I-MISC
Chimaera -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
pulling -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Grand -X- -X- B-PER
Admiral -X- -X- I-PER
Thrawn -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Bridger -X- -X- B-PER
away -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
hyperspace -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
deep -X- -X- O
space -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Freemakers -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
egged -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
assisted -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Naare -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
secret -X- -X- O
Sith -X- -X- O
agent -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Emperor -X- -X- B-PER
Palpatine -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
wanted -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
exploit -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
powers -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Kyber -X- -X- O
Saber -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
himself -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Freemakers -X- -X- B-ORG
learnt -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Naare -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
true -X- -X- O
identity -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Freemakers -X- -X- B-ORG
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
urging -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
youngest -X- -X- O
member -X- -X- O
Rowan -X- -X- B-PER
Freemaker -X- -X- O
took -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
race -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
Naare -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Hutt -X- -X- O
crime -X- -X- O
lord -X- -X- O
Graballa -X- -X- B-PER
to -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
pieces -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Kyber -X- -X- O
Saber -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Though -X- -X- O
Naare -X- -X- B-PER
managed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
reforge -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Kyber -X- -X- O
Saber -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Freemakers -X- -X- B-ORG
managed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
steal -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
following -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
skirmish -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Coruscant -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
Rowan -X- -X- B-PER
destroyed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Kyber -X- -X- O
Saber -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Freemakers -X- -X- B-ORG
joined -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
search -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Yiprukk -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
search -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mother -X- -X- O
looking -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
Force-sensitive -X- -X- O
son -X- -X- O
Yiprukk -X- -X- B-PER
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Seastone -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
green -X- -X- O
substance -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
carved -X- -X- O
grip -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Master -X- -X- I-PER
Avar -X- -X- I-PER
Kriss -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
inlaid -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Seatroopers -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
stormtroopers -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Stormtrooper -X- -X- B-ORG
Corps -X- -X- I-ORG
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
that -X- -X- O
specialized -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
aquatic -X- -X- O
environments -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Seatroopers -X- -X- O
saw -X- -X- O
action -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Mon -X- -X- B-LOC
Cala -X- -X- I-LOC
in -X- -X- O
18 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Seaweed -X- -X- O
came -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ocean -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
foodstuff -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Lanai -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
spiced -X- -X- O
seaweed -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Festival -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- O
Return -X- -X- I-MISC
on -X- -X- O
Ahch-To -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
Poe -X- -X- B-PER
Dameron -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
Finn -X- -X- B-PER
attended -X- -X- O
Nifera -X- -X- B-PER
Shu -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
birthday -X- -X- O
party -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
variety -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
seafoods -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
displayed -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
beds -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
multicolored -X- -X- O
seaweed -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
keeping -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ocean -X- -X- O
theme -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Seaweed -X- -X- O
clung -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Luke -X- -X- B-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
T-65B -X- -X- B-MISC
X-wing -X- -X- I-MISC
starfighter -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
raised -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
waters -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Ahch-To -X- -X- B-LOC
after -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
submersion -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

She -X- -X- O
danced -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
group -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
humans -X- -X- O
while -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
hermit -X- -X- O
Lando -X- -X- B-PER
Calrissian -X- -X- I-PER
led -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- O
agents -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
festival -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
safety -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
agents -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
spotted -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Seboca -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Dug -X- -X- O
holovid -X- -X- O
star -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
22 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
shortly -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
beginning -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Seboca -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
entertaining -X- -X- O
Senator -X- -X- B-PER
Bogg -X- -X- I-PER
Tyrell -X- -X- I-PER
on -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
airspeeder -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Knight -X- -X- I-PER
Obi-Wan -X- -X- I-PER
Kenobi -X- -X- I-PER
nearly -X- -X- O
crashed -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
while -X- -X- O
trying -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
capture -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clawdite -X- -X- O
bounty -X- -X- O
hunter -X- -X- O
Zam -X- -X- B-PER
Wesell -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
leading -X- -X- O
Seboca -X- -X- B-PER
to -X- -X- O
insult -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
nearly -X- -X- O
hitting -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Seboca -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
later -X- -X- O
present -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
Dex -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Diner -X- -X- O
conversing -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
patrons -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
Kenobi -X- -X- B-PER
talked -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
Dexter -X- -X- B-PER
Jettster -X- -X- I-PER
about -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Kamino -X- -X- O
saberdart -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sebris -X- -X- B-LOC
Alpha -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Hays -X- -X- B-LOC
Minor -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Sebris -X- -X- B-LOC
Beta -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Hays -X- -X- B-LOC
Minor -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Sebris -X- -X- B-LOC
Gamma -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
village -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Hays -X- -X- B-LOC
Minor -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
destroyed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
ground-penetrating -X- -X- O
incendiary -X- -X- O
bombs -X- -X- O
dropped -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
bombers -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
residents -X- -X- O
refused -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
follow -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
orders -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sebulba -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
Dug -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
hailed -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Malastare -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
vicious -X- -X- O
podracer -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
flew -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
massive -X- -X- O
orange -X- -X- O
podracer -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
split-x -X- -X- O
configuration -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Sebulba -X- -X- B-PER
would -X- -X- O
often -X- -X- O
bump -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
smash -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
way -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
competition -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
crowd -X- -X- O
favorite -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
course -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Boonta -X- -X- B-MISC
Eve -X- -X- I-MISC
Classic -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Outer -X- -X- B-LOC
Rim -X- -X- I-LOC
planet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Tatooine -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Sebulba -X- -X- B-PER
maintained -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
strong -X- -X- O
rivalry -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
podracings -X- -X- O
few -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
participants -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
young -X- -X- O
boy -X- -X- O
named -X- -X- O
Anakin -X- -X- B-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
short -X- -X- O
while -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Invasion -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Naboo -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Sebulba -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Skywalker -X- -X- B-PER
competed -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Boonta -X- -X- B-MISC
race -X- -X- O
together -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Dug -X- -X- O
Sebulba -X- -X- B-PER
owned -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
massive -X- -X- O
orange -X- -X- O
podracer -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
podrace -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sebulba -X- -X- B-PER
could -X- -X- O
control -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
flamethrowers -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
cockpit -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
torch -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
pilots -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Secessionists -X- -X- B-ORG
represented -X- -X- O
star -X- -X- O
systems -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
considering -X- -X- O
leaving -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
although -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
body -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
small -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
voting -X- -X- O
bloc -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
vital -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
systems -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
increase -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
influence -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
threatening -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
secede -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Despite -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
systems -X- -X- O
sought -X- -X- O
diplomatic -X- -X- O
solutions -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Secon -X- -X- B-PER
Daree -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Lutrillian -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
piloted -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
X-wing -X- -X- B-MISC
starfighter -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Starfighter -X- -X- O
Corps -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ill-fated -X- -X- O
attack -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Lothal -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Daree -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
captured -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Noghri -X- -X- O
assassin -X- -X- O
Rukh -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
handed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
custody -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
short -X- -X- O
unit -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
measurement -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Shortly -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
infiltration -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Hivebase-1 -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
launched -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
attack -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Son-tuul -X- -X- B-ORG
Pride -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
led -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Lieutenant-Inspector -X- -X- O
Magna -X- -X- B-PER
Tolvan -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
entirety -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
mercenaries -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
either -X- -X- O
killed -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
captured -X- -X- O
except -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
leader -X- -X- O
0-0 -X- -X- B-PER
- -X- -X- I-PER
0 -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
assailant -X- -X- O
BT-1 -X- -X- B-PER
who -X- -X- O
pretended -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
innocent -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
caught -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
crossfire -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tolvan -X- -X- B-PER
then -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
Chelli -X- -X- B-PER
Lona -X- -X- I-PER
Aphra -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
Dek-Nil -X- -X- B-PER
taken -X- -X- O
away -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Accresker -X- -X- B-LOC
Jail -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

At -X- -X- O
least -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Christophsis -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
took -X- -X- O
place -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Christophsis -X- -X- B-LOC
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
deducing -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Master -X- -X- I-PER
Quinlan -X- -X- I-PER
Vos -X- -X- I-PER
had -X- -X- O
fallen -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
dark -X- -X- O
side -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Force -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-ORG
Council -X- -X- I-ORG
sent -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
kill -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-ORG
leader -X- -X- O
Count -X- -X- B-PER
Dooku -X- -X- I-PER
in -X- -X- O
order -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
test -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
loyalty -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

From -X- -X- O
Vos -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
lover -X- -X- O
Asajj -X- -X- B-PER
Ventress -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
learned -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Dooku -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
dreadnought -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
visiting -X- -X- O
Christophsis -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Together -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Vos -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Ventress -X- -X- B-PER
traveled -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Dooku -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
flagship -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
Vos -X- -X- O
managed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
engage -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
duel -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Unknown -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Vos -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
Obi-Wan -X- -X- B-PER
Kenobi -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
Anakin -X- -X- B-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
tailed -X- -X- O
along -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
began -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
Maul -X- -X- B-PER
brought -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
captive -X- -X- O
Sith -X- -X- O
Lord -X- -X- O
Count -X- -X- B-PER
Dooku -X- -X- I-PER
to -X- -X- O
Dathomir -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
Talzin -X- -X- B-PER
could -X- -X- O
drain -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Count -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
life -X- -X- O
force -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
use -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
return -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
previously-destroyed -X- -X- O
physical -X- -X- O
form -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Darth -X- -X- B-PER
Sidious -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
able -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
trace -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Dooku -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
apprentice -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
traveled -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
General -X- -X- B-PER
Grievous -X- -X- I-PER
to -X- -X- O
Dathomir -X- -X- B-LOC
to -X- -X- O
rescue -X- -X- O
Dooku -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
defeat -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
enemies -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Felucia -X- -X- B-LOC
saw -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
clash -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
for -X- -X- O
control -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Felucia -X- -X- B-LOC
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Having -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
forced -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
retreat -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Felucia -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
re-established -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
presence -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
thanks -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
efforts -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
General -X- -X- O
Anakin -X- -X- B-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
Padawan -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Ahsoka -X- -X- B-PER
Tano -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
led -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
clone -X- -X- O
troopers -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
offensive -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
Separatist-held -X- -X- B-ORG
territory -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
retaliation -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
General -X- -X- B-PER
Grievous -X- -X- I-PER
supplied -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
outposts -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Felucia -X- -X- B-LOC
with -X- -X- O
reinforcements -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
secure -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
system -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Confederacy -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Responding -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
arrival -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
detachment -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Skywalker -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
Tano -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
Master -X- -X- O
Plo -X- -X- B-PER
Koon -X- -X- I-PER
targeted -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
enemy -X- -X- O
outpost -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
three-pronged -X- -X- O
assault -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
each -X- -X- O
leading -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
squad -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
divide -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-ORG
defenses -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Geonosis -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Geonosis -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
took -X- -X- O
place -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Geonosis -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
site -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
conflict -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
opening -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
class -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
skilled -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
engineering -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
technical -X- -X- O
sciences -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Astromech -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
class -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
coronation -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
R -X- -X- B-PER
é -X- -X- I-PER
illata -X- -X- I-PER
as -X- -X- O
monarch -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Naboo -X- -X- B-LOC
took -X- -X- O
place -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
steps -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Theed -X- -X- B-LOC
Royal -X- -X- I-LOC
Palace -X- -X- I-LOC
in -X- -X- O
28 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

R -X- -X- B-PER
é -X- -X- I-PER
illata -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
re-elected -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
throne -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Royal -X- -X- B-ORG
House -X- -X- I-ORG
of -X- -X- O
Naboo -X- -X- B-LOC
to -X- -X- O
serve -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
final -X- -X- O
term -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
Queen -X- -X- O
following -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
stepping -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Padm -X- -X- B-PER
é -X- -X- I-PER
Amidala -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
defense -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
starfleet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
Defense -X- -X- O
Overlord -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Garwian -X- -X- B-ORG
Unity -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Frangelic -X- -X- B-PER
held -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
flight -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
unit -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
T-65B -X- -X- B-MISC
X-wing -X- -X- I-MISC
starfighters -X- -X- I-MISC
within -X- -X- O
Red -X- -X- B-ORG
Squadron -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
starfighter -X- -X- O
squadron -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- B-ORG
to -X- -X- O
Restore -X- -X- I-ORG
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
took -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Yavin -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
led -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Major -X- -X- O
Ralo -X- -X- B-PER
Surrel -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
Harb -X- -X- B-PER
Binli -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
John -X- -X- B-PER
D -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O
Branon -X- -X- B-PER
as -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
wingmen -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
Lieutenant -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
rank -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
deck -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
Frobb -X- -X- B-PER
held -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rank -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
lieutenant -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
year -X- -X- O
0 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Teso -X- -X- B-PER
Broosh -X- -X- I-PER
held -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rank -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
204th -X- -X- B-MISC
Imperial -X- -X- I-MISC
Fighter -X- -X- I-MISC
Wing -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
mate -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
title -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
aboard -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
starships -X- -X- O
crew -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
34 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
smuggler -X- -X- O
Han -X- -X- B-PER
Solo -X- -X- I-PER
offered -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
scavenger -X- -X- O
Rey -X- -X- B-PER
the -X- -X- O
opportunity -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
mate -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Millennium -X- -X- B-MISC
Falcon -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
looking -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
crew -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
help -X- -X- O
himself -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Chewbacca -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
Minister -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
political -X- -X- O
rank -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Clabron -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
directly -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
Grand -X- -X- O
Minister -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Clabronian -X- -X- O
Tarmin -X- -X- B-PER
held -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
title -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
replaced -X- -X- O
Stin -X- -X- B-PER
as -X- -X- O
Grand -X- -X- O
Minister -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
assassinated -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Colossus -X- -X- O
platform -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Kazuda -X- -X- B-PER
Xiono -X- -X- I-PER
undertook -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
Doza -X- -X- B-MISC
Tower -X- -X- I-MISC
to -X- -X- O
try -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
how -X- -X- O
Captain -X- -X- O
Imanuel -X- -X- B-PER
Doza -X- -X- I-PER
might -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
colluding -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
unwittingly -X- -X- O
assisted -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Doza -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
daughter -X- -X- O
Torra -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
snuck -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
tower -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
father -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
attempted -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
lock -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
room -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
own -X- -X- O
protection -X- -X- O
while -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
meeting -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Commander -X- -X- O
Pyre -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

Jedi -X- -X- O
Plo -X- -X- B-PER
Koon -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
Ahsoka -X- -X- B-PER
Tano -X- -X- I-PER
conducted -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Florrum -X- -X- B-LOC
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
confront -X- -X- O
Boba -X- -X- B-PER
Fett -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
allied -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
bounty -X- -X- O
hunter -X- -X- O
Aurra -X- -X- B-PER

Sing -X- -X- B-PER
to -X- -X- O
kill -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
Master -X- -X- O
Mace -X- -X- B-PER
Windu -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
ended -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
arrest -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Fett -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Bossk -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
while -X- -X- O
Sing -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
presumed -X- -X- O
dead -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Jedi -X- -X- O
Master -X- -X- O
Obi-Wan -X- -X- B-PER
Kenobi -X- -X- I-PER
executed -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
prevent -X- -X- O
bounty -X- -X- O
hunter -X- -X- O
Cad -X- -X- B-PER
Bane -X- -X- I-PER
from -X- -X- O
kidnapping -X- -X- O
Wee -X- -X- B-PER
Dunn -X- -X- I-PER
on -X- -X- O
Rodia -X- -X- B-LOC
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
2 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Phoenix -X- -X- B-PER
Cell -X- -X- I-PER
undertook -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Ryloth -X- -X- B-LOC
to -X- -X- O
recover -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Kalikori -X- -X- B-MISC
artifact -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Meanwhile -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Free -X- -X- O
Ryloth -X- -X- O
Movement -X- -X- O
leader -X- -X- O
Cham -X- -X- B-PER
Syndulla -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
Gobi -X- -X- B-PER
Glie -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
Numa -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
Spectres -X- -X- O
staged -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
diversionary -X- -X- O
attack -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Tulara -X- -X- B-LOC
Ravine -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Hera -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Ezra -X- -X- B-PER
were -X- -X- O
captured -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Grand -X- -X- O
Admiral -X- -X- O
Thrawn -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
subordinate -X- -X- O
Captain -X- -X- O
Slavin -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

Thrawn -X- -X- B-PER
added -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Kalikori -X- -X- B-MISC
to -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
art -X- -X- O
collection -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
delegated -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rest -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
operations -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Slavin -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Captain -X- -X- O
Slavin -X- -X- B-PER
then -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
Hera -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Ezra -X- -X- B-PER
as -X- -X- O
hostages -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
force -X- -X- O
Cham -X- -X- B-PER
to -X- -X- O
surrender -X- -X- O
himself -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

However -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Hera -X- -X- B-PER
got -X- -X- O
Chopper -X- -X- B-PER
to -X- -X- O
plant -X- -X- O
explosives -X- -X- O
throughout -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
building -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

This -X- -X- O
created -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
explosion -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
allowed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
rebel -X- -X- O
factions -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
2 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
members -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Phoenix -X- -X- B-ORG
Cell -X- -X- I-ORG
undertook -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
third -X- -X- O
moon -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Concord -X- -X- B-LOC
Dawn -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
discovered -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
Mandalorians -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
Viceroy -X- -X- B-PER
Gar -X- -X- I-PER
Saxon -X- -X- I-PER
had -X- -X- O
attacked -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
encampment -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
massacred -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Protectors -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Due -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
shared -X- -X- O
experiences -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Rau -X- -X- B-PER
decided -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
join -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rebellion -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- B-LOC
Moon -X- -X- I-LOC
of -X- -X- I-LOC
Thrinittik -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
rocky -X- -X- O
moon -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Toshma -X- -X- B-PER
Jefkin -X- -X- I-PER
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
aboard -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Tantive -X- -X- B-MISC
IV -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
platoon -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
platoon -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
army -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
deployed -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Vrogas -X- -X- B-LOC
Vas -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
platoon -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
platoon -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
patrol -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
platoon -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
BX-series -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
commandos -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Sith -X- -X- B-PER
Lord -X- -X- I-PER
Darth -X- -X- I-PER
Vader -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Chelli -X- -X- B-PER
Lona -X- -X- I-PER
Aphra -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
crew -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Shortly -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Yavin -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
platoon -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
involved -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
skirmish -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Cylo -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
research -X- -X- O
base -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

As -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
attempts -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
over -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Colossus -X- -X- O
platform -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Kragan -X- -X- B-PER
Gorr -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
pirate -X- -X- O
gang -X- -X- O
launched -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
raid -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
platform -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
attempt -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Due -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
gang -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
spy -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Synara -X- -X- B-PER
San -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
informing -X- -X- O
Gorr -X- -X- B-PER
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Ace -X- -X- O
Squadron -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
off-platform -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
targeting -X- -X- O
computer -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
platform -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
defense -X- -X- O
turbolasers -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Gorr -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
gang -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
able -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
much -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
damage -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
attack -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- B-PER
Sister -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
formerly -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
Trilla -X- -X- B-PER
Suduri -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Force-sensitive -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Inquisitorius -X- -X- B-ORG
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
reign -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Trained -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
arts -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- B-PER
Sister -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
expert -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
duelist -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Empire -X- -X- B-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
deadliest -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
hunters -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

However -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Suduri -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
strongest -X- -X- O
asset -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
brilliant -X- -X- O
intellect -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
able -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
anticipate -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
behavior -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
prey -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

She -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
hunt -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
Padawan -X- -X- O
Cal -X- -X- B-PER
Kestis -X- -X- I-PER
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Great -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
Purge -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
third -X- -X- O
duel -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Bogano -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Kestis -X- -X- B-PER
disarmed -X- -X- O
Suduri -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
grabbed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
forced -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
relive -X- -X- O
Suduri -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
capture -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
conscription -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Inquisitorius -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
psychometry -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
allowing -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
steal -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
holocron -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Kestis -X- -X- B-PER
gave -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
saber -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
master -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Cere -X- -X- B-PER
Junda -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- B-PER
Sister -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
former -X- -X- O
Master -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
knighted -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

By -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
Kestis -X- -X- B-PER
faced -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- B-PER
Sister -X- -X- I-PER
in -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
fourth -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
final -X- -X- O
duel -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
Fortress -X- -X- B-LOC
Inquisitorius -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
replaced -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
new -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
skirmish -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mesulan -X- -X- B-LOC
Remnants -X- -X- I-LOC
Belt -X- -X- I-LOC
occurred -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
Fyzen -X- -X- B-PER
Gor -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
Substation -X- -X- B-LOC
Grimdock -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Solo -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Calrissian -X- -X- B-PER
themselves -X- -X- O
later -X- -X- O
arrived -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Chevalier -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
having -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
visiting -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
asylum -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Grava -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
finding -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Remnants -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
skirmish -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Elthree -X- -X- B-MISC
Assault -X- -X- I-MISC
Team -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
founded -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
earlier -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
L3-37 -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
entered -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
skirmish -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
Gor -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Original -X- -X- O
Dozen -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Calrissian -X- -X- B-PER
managed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
destroy -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
transmitter -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Solo -X- -X- B-PER
killed -X- -X- O
Gor -X- -X- B-PER
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Chevalier -X- -X- B-MISC
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
laser -X- -X- O
cannons -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Around -X- -X- O
9 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
attack -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
base -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
led -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Magistrate -X- -X- B-PER
Greef -X- -X- I-PER
Karga -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
confrontation -X- -X- O
effectively -X- -X- O
ended -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
presence -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Nevarro -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
Squadron -X- -X- O
Commander -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
rank -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
Navy -X- -X- I-ORG
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
/ -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- B-ORG
War -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Due -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
role -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
defending -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bridge -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Commander -X- -X- O
Pyre -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Resurgent-class -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- O
Destroyer -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Escape -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
Aeos -X- -X- B-LOC
Prime -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- O
Order -X- -X- O
TIE -X- -X- O
Fighter -X- -X- O
Pilot -X- -X- O
cadet -X- -X- O
Tamara -X- -X- B-PER
Ryvora -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
promoted -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- O
Squadron -X- -X- O
Commander -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Second -X- -X- O
weapons -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
starfleet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Upon -X- -X- O
gaining -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rank -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
junior -X- -X- O
lieutenant -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Thrawn -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
assigned -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
weapons -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
aboard -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Gozanti-class -X- -X- O
cruiser -X- -X- O
Blood -X- -X- B-MISC
Crow -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Long -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- O
Civil -X- -X- O
War -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Whill -X- -X- B-PER
talked -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
another -X- -X- O
Whill -X- -X- B-PER
about -X- -X- O
recording -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
history -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
galaxy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Second-wave -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
term -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
original -X- -X- O
settlers -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Jelucan -X- -X- B-LOC
to -X- -X- O
describe -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
settlers -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
arrived -X- -X- O
350 -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
initial -X- -X- O
settlement -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Secondary -X- -X- O
sensor -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
starfleet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Although -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Nobles -X- -X- O
frowned -X- -X- O
upon -X- -X- O
calling -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
assassins -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
those -X- -X- O
agents -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
trained -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
infiltrate -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
bases -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
just -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
deadly -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
blaster -X- -X- O
than -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
gun-for -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
hire -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Having -X- -X- O
fallen -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
favor -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
Emperor -X- -X- B-PER
Palpatine -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
Vader -X- -X- B-PER
had -X- -X- O
recruited -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rogue -X- -X- O
archaeologist -X- -X- O
Doctor -X- -X- O
Chelli -X- -X- B-PER
Aphra -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
assassin -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
BT-1 -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
0-0 -X- -X- B-PER
- -X- -X- I-PER
0 -X- -X- I-PER
to -X- -X- O
assist -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
building -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
army -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
unquestionably -X- -X- O
loyal -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Vader -X- -X- B-PER
soon -X- -X- O
arrived -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Geonosis -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
team -X- -X- O
infiltrated -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
lair -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Karina -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Geonosian -X- -X- O
queen -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
utilized -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
factory -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
produce -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
children -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
injured -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
left -X- -X- O
unable -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
produce -X- -X- O
offspring -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
sterilization -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Geonosis -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

While -X- -X- O
BT-1 -X- -X- B-MISC
fired -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
queen -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
B1-series -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Vader -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Aphra -X- -X- B-PER
severed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
queen -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
factory -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Aphra -X- -X- B-PER
used -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
starship -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Ark -X- -X- B-MISC
Angel -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
blow -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
large -X- -X- O
hole -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
roof -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
lair -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Vader -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
own -X- -X- O
starship -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
extract -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
factory -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Vader -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
team -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
large -X- -X- O
crane -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
captured -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
factory -X- -X- O
began -X- -X- O
producing -X- -X- O
BX-series -X- -X- B-MISC
droid -X- -X- O
commandos -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Vader -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
assault -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
research -X- -X- O
base -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
rival -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
operative -X- -X- O
named -X- -X- O
Cylo -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
efforts -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
restore -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
destroyed -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
that -X- -X- O
brought -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
conflict -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Inquisitorius -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
followed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rebellion -X- -X- B-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
theft -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
plans -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Death -X- -X- B-LOC
Star -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
planet-destroying -X- -X- O
deep -X- -X- O
space -X- -X- O
mobile -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
station -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Scarif -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

As -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
concluded -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
plans -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
nearly -X- -X- O
reclaimed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Darth -X- -X- B-PER
Vader -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
successfully -X- -X- O
transferred -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Princess -X- -X- O
Leia -X- -X- B-PER
Organa -X- -X- I-PER
of -X- -X- O
Alderaan -X- -X- B-LOC
aboard -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Tantive -X- -X- B-MISC
IV -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
secret -X- -X- O
Phoenix -X- -X- B-ORG
Cell -X- -X- I-ORG
route -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
secret -X- -X- O
hyperspace -X- -X- O
route -X- -X- O
created -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
RA-7 -X- -X- O
protocol -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
AP-5 -X- -X- B-MISC
when -X- -X- O
using -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
databank -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
data -X- -X- O
obtained -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Phoenix -X- -X- B-ORG
Cell -X- -X- I-ORG
to -X- -X- O
reach -X- -X- O
Atollon -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
CZ-series -X- -X- O
secretary -X- -X- O
/ -X- -X- O
business -X- -X- O
communications -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
example -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

One -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
notable -X- -X- O
secretary -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
CZ-1G5 -X- -X- B-MISC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
CZ -X- -X- O
unit -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
Niima -X- -X- B-LOC
Outpost -X- -X- I-LOC
for -X- -X- O
over -X- -X- O
three -X- -X- O
hundred -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
helped -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Kubaz -X- -X- O
banker -X- -X- O
Rikard -X- -X- B-PER
Lovas -X- -X- I-PER
carry -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
devilish -X- -X- O
plan -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
help -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
make -X- -X- O
money -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Secretary -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Cabinet -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
individual -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
led -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- B-ORG
Cabinet -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
ministers -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
civilian -X- -X- O
body -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- B-ORG
to -X- -X- O
Restore -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- B-ORG
Civil -X- -X- I-ORG
Government -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Viceroy -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
former -X- -X- O
Senator -X- -X- O
Bail -X- -X- B-PER
Organa -X- -X- I-PER
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
Secretary -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Cabinet -X- -X- B-ORG
until -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
death -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
0 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Secretary -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Transportation -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
leader -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
Transport -X- -X- I-ORG
Bureau -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
responsible -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
maintaining -X- -X- O
safe -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
reliable -X- -X- O
travel -X- -X- O
across -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
reported -X- -X- O
directly -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
incumbent -X- -X- O
Supreme -X- -X- O
Chancellor -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
held -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Muun -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
named -X- -X- O
Jeffo -X- -X- B-PER
Lorillia -X- -X- I-PER
in -X- -X- O
232 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
Chancellor -X- -X- O
Lina -X- -X- B-PER
Soh -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

Coruscant -X- -X- B-ORG
Guard -X- -X- I-ORG
riot -X- -X- O
troopers -X- -X- O
believed -X- -X- O
Duchess -X- -X- O
Satine -X- -X- B-PER
Kryze -X- -X- I-PER
fled -X- -X- O
toward -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
section -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
police -X- -X- O
identified -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
suspect -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
murder -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Davu -X- -X- B-PER
Golec -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
space -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
land -X- -X- O
framed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
artificial -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
conventional -X- -X- O
boundary -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sector -X- -X- B-LOC
11 -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Sundari -X- -X- B-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Mandalore -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Some -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
siege -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Maul -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
assistance -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- O
clone -X- -X- O
troopers -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
able -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
keep -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
control -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
though -X- -X- O
fighting -X- -X- O
still -X- -X- O
occurred -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- B-LOC
11 -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Sector -X- -X- B-LOC
11 -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
designation -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Rugosa -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
group -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
searching -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Master -X- -X- I-PER
Yoda -X- -X- I-PER
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Ambush -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Rugosa -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
22 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
OOM -X- -X- O
command -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
noticed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- B-LOC
11 -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
ordered -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
troops -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
fire -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
sergeant -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
unsure -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
commanding -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
ordered -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
fire -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
leading -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
irate -X- -X- O
OOM -X- -X- O
command -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
point -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sector -X- -X- B-LOC
3263827 -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
received -X- -X- O
refuse -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
Black -X- -X- B-LOC
Spire -X- -X- I-LOC
Outpost -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
remote -X- -X- O
settlement -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Batuu -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Outer -X- -X- B-LOC
Rim -X- -X- I-LOC
Territories -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Garbage -X- -X- O
receptacles -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
outpost -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
stamped -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
orders -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
written -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Aurebesh -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
transport -X- -X- O
trash -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
age -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Lothal -X- -X- B-LOC
sector -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
including -X- -X- O
Sector -X- -X- B-LOC
33 -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Sector -X- -X- B-LOC
47 -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
area -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
space -X- -X- O
above -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Forest -X- -X- O
Moon -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Endor -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Endor -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- O
Civil -X- -X- O
War -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- O
Destroyers -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Sector -X- -X- B-LOC
47 -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
ambushed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- O
Fleet -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- O
Mon -X- -X- O
Calamari -X- -X- O
controller -X- -X- O
informed -X- -X- O
Admiral -X- -X- O
Gial -X- -X- B-PER
Ackbar -X- -X- I-PER
about -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
vessels -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Sector -X- -X- B-LOC
5-1 -X- -X- I-LOC
- -X- -X- I-LOC
5 -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Capital -X- -X- O
City -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Lothal -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Sector -X- -X- B-LOC
5-1 -X- -X- I-LOC
- -X- -X- I-LOC
5 -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
desert -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Geonosis -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Geonosis -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Grand -X- -X- I-PER
Master -X- -X- I-PER
Yoda -X- -X- I-PER
ordered -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
fire -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
focused -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
nearest -X- -X- O
starship -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Captain -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
forward -X- -X- O
command -X- -X- O
center -X- -X- O
ordered -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
quadrants -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
allowing -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Self-Propelled -X- -X- O
Heavy -X- -X- O
Artillery -X- -X- O
Turbolasers -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
take -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
core -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
fell -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
battlefield -X- -X- O
below -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
continued -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
ultimately -X- -X- O
won -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Kazuda -X- -X- B-PER
Xiono -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
BB-8 -X- -X- B-MISC
encountered -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
pirates -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- B-LOC
7-E -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
managed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
prevent -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
stealing -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
crates -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
blasters -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

2J99 -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
ruled -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Empire -X- -X- B-ORG
and -X- -X- O
controlled -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Moff -X- -X- B-PER
Stattata -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
Governor -X- -X- B-PER
Arihnda -X- -X- I-PER
Pryce -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Lothal -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

RMS -X- -X- B-MISC
droids -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
gray -X- -X- O
plating -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
single -X- -X- O
band -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
red -X- -X- O
near -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
top -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
body -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

RN-18 -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
mining -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
stolen -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
pirate -X- -X- O
Fortombro -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
reprogrammed -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
numerous -X- -X- O
combat -X- -X- O
protocols -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Ro -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
starfleet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
who -X- -X- O
fought -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- O
Civil -X- -X- O
War -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

By -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
Ro -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
prowesses -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
passed -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
history -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
commemorative -X- -X- O
armbands -X- -X- O
worn -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
sergeants -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
bore -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Aurebesh -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

General -X- -X- O
Hux -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
monitor -X- -X- O
wore -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
uniform -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
designating -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sergeant -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Ro -X- -X- B-PER
family -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
humanoid -X- -X- O
species -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
members -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
included -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Eyes -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Nihil -X- -X- B-PER
Asgar -X- -X- I-PER
Ro -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
son -X- -X- O
Marchion -X- -X- B-PER
Ro -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

Hailing -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
homeworld -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
history -X- -X- O
entwined -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mysterious -X- -X- O
artifact -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
Marchion -X- -X- B-PER
believed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
connected -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
bad -X- -X- O
things -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
befallen -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
ancestors -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Several -X- -X- O
generations -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
held -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
hyperspace -X- -X- O
prospector -X- -X- O
Mari -X- -X- B-PER
San -X- -X- I-PER
Tekka -X- -X- I-PER
prisoner -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
utilize -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
ability -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
discover -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Paths -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
difficult-to -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
traverse -X- -X- O
hyperspace -X- -X- O
routes -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Asgar -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Marchion -X- -X- B-PER
Ro -X- -X- I-PER
hailed -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
homeworld -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
abandoned -X- -X- O
long -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Great -X- -X- O
Disaster -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
eventually -X- -X- O
joining -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Nihil -X- -X- B-ORG
pirates -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
leaving -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
homeworld -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
closest -X- -X- O
thing -X- -X- O
Marchion -X- -X- B-PER
had -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
home -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
flagship -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Gaze -X- -X- B-MISC
Electric -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
ro -X- -X- O
hypa -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
serpentine -X- -X- O
creature -X- -X- O
native -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
desert -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Mataou -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Anoat -X- -X- B-LOC
sector -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
red -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
purple -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
appearance -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
highly -X- -X- O
venomous -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
capable -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
spewing -X- -X- O
potent -X- -X- O
poison -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
prey -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Ro -X- -X- B-PER
Thran -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Gran -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
hunter -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
hire -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

At -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
point -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
captured -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bull -X- -X- O
krykna -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Tyn -X- -X- B-ORG
Syndicate -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
later -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
hunters -X- -X- O
hired -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
archeologist -X- -X- O
Doctor -X- -X- O
Chelli -X- -X- B-PER
Aphra -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
swallowed -X- -X- O
alive -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Shadowfang -X- -X- O
Beast -X- -X- O
guarding -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
temple -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
X3-299 -X- -X- B-LOC
- -X- -X- I-LOC
11 -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Aphra -X- -X- B-PER
wanted -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
hunter -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
subdue -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
beast -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
kill -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
stomach -X- -X- O
; -X- -X- O
however -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Thran -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
killed -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
activated -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
temple -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
traps -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
launched -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
spears -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Gran -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
pinned -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
wall -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
hunters -X- -X- O
Nokk -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Winloss -X- -X- B-PER
later -X- -X- O
discovered -X- -X- O
Thran -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
body -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
Aphra -X- -X- B-PER
claimed -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
must -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
hired -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
someone -X- -X- O
else -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
capture -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
beast -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Thran -X- -X- B-PER
had -X- -X- O
black -X- -X- O
eyes -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
pink -X- -X- O
skin -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
wore -X- -X- O
red -X- -X- O
armor -X- -X- O
over -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
black -X- -X- O
shirt -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
blue -X- -X- O
pants -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
death -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Ro-Loo -X- -X- B-LOC
Triangle -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
nebula -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
portions -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
fleet -X- -X- O
hid -X- -X- O
away -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Endor -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
fleet -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
big -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
residing -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Vulpinus -X- -X- B-LOC
Nebula -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
however -X- -X- O
there -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
still -X- -X- O
hundreds -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- O
Destroyers -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
thousands -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
smaller -X- -X- O
craft -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Ro-roos -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
creatures -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
existed -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
galaxy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
equipped -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
database -X- -X- O
detailing -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
species -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
child -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
care -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
perform -X- -X- O
minor -X- -X- O
medical -X- -X- O
operations -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
emergencies -X- -X- O
while -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
contacting -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
authorities -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Ro-ti -X- -X- B-MISC
- -X- -X- I-MISC
Mundi -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Venator-class -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- O
Destroyer -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Open -X- -X- O
Circle -X- -X- O
Fleet -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
major -X- -X- O
space -X- -X- O
fleet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
Navy -X- -X- I-ORG
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Wars -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- O
Destroyer -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
notably -X- -X- O
involved -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
defense -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Coruscant -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
capital -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
naval -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Confederacy -X- -X- B-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
Independent -X- -X- I-ORG
Systems -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Ro-ti -X- -X- B-MISC
- -X- -X- I-MISC
Mundi -X- -X- I-MISC
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
carrier -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Flight -X- -X- O
Squad -X- -X- O
Seven -X- -X- O
— -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
starfighter -X- -X- O
squadron -X- -X- O
led -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- O
Commander -X- -X- B-PER
CC-2237 -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

Stationed -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
secret -X- -X- O
facility -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Mustafar -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
RO-Z67 -X- -X- B-MISC
worked -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
Force-sensitive -X- -X- O
children -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
kidnapped -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bounty -X- -X- O
hunter -X- -X- O
Cad -X- -X- B-PER
Bane -X- -X- I-PER
on -X- -X- O
behalf -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Sidious -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

Sidious -X- -X- B-PER
planned -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
train -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
children -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
become -X- -X- O
dark -X- -X- O
side -X- -X- O
spies -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
RO-Z67 -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
destroyed -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- O
Knight -X- -X- O
Anakin -X- -X- B-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
Padawan -X- -X- O
apprentice -X- -X- O
Ahsoka -X- -X- B-PER
Tano -X- -X- I-PER
rescued -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
children -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Roach -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
member -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- B-ORG
to -X- -X- O
Restore -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
61st -X- -X- O
Mobile -X- -X- O
Infantry -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
better -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
Twilight -X- -X- O
Company -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Namir -X- -X- B-PER
took -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
liking -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
became -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
company -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
able -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
determine -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Roach -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
recovering -X- -X- O
spice -X- -X- O
addict -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

She -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
ultimately -X- -X- O
killed -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Siege -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Inyusu -X- -X- B-LOC
Tor -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Sullust -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
roach-rat -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
rat -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
hide -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
scuttle -X- -X- O
around -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
darkness -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Roachrats -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
creature -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
scattered -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
exposed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
sunlight -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Roast -X- -X- O
nuna -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
cooked -X- -X- O
meal -X- -X- O
made -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
roast -X- -X- O
nuna -X- -X- O
meat -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
found -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bar -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Roasted -X- -X- O
Chando -X- -X- O
Peppers -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
dish -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
contained -X- -X- O
roasted -X- -X- O
strips -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
orange -X- -X- O
chando -X- -X- O
peppers -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sweet -X- -X- O
variety -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
pepper -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
originated -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Chandrila -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Roasted -X- -X- O
Endorian -X- -X- O
Tip-Yip -X- -X- O
Salad -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
dish -X- -X- O
centered -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
meat -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Endor -X- -X- B-LOC
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Tip-yip -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Marinated -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
oven-roasted -X- -X- O
tip-yip -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
mixed -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
greens -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
roasted -X- -X- O
vegetables -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
pumpkin -X- -X- O
seeds -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
then -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
salad -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
tossed -X- -X- O
together -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
green-colored -X- -X- O
sauce -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
34 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
salad -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
available -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
Docking -X- -X- O
Bay -X- -X- O
7 -X- -X- O
Food -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Cargo -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
Black -X- -X- O
Spire -X- -X- O
Outpost -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O
