# sent_id = 0
# text = A sealer was a tool Rey used to fix the Millennium Falcon when the motivator went bad.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31079
A	O
sealer	O
was	O
a	O
tool	O
Rey	B-PER
used	O
to	O
fix	O
the	O
Millennium	B-MISC
Falcon	I-MISC
when	O
the	O
motivator	O
went	O
bad	O
.	O

# sent_id = 1
# text = It was hard for Finn to locate it, but with some aid from BB-8, he was able to find it and give it to Rey.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 17966
It	O
was	O
hard	O
for	O
Finn	B-PER
to	O
locate	O
it	O
,	O
but	O
with	O
some	O
aid	O
from	O
BB-8	B-MISC
,	O
he	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
find	O
it	O
and	O
give	O
it	O
to	O
Rey	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 2
# text = A seallia sandwich was a toasted sandwich dish which could be served for breakfast.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 59885
A	O
seallia	B-MISC
sandwich	I-MISC
was	O
a	O
toasted	O
sandwich	O
dish	O
which	O
could	O
be	O
served	O
for	O
breakfast	O
.	O

# sent_id = 3
# text = The Devaronian chef Sama Macoy served a double-toasted seallia sandwich with a heavy and sweet blood syrup as her entry into the first round of a cooking competition meant to determine the next sous-chef of the castle of the pirate Maz Kanata on the planet Takodana.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 47211
The	O
Devaronian	O
chef	O
Sama	B-PER
Macoy	I-PER
served	O
a	O
double-toasted	O
seallia	B-MISC
sandwich	I-MISC
with	O
a	O
heavy	O
and	O
sweet	O
blood	O
syrup	O
as	O
her	O
entry	O
into	O
the	O
first	O
round	O
of	O
a	O
cooking	O
competition	O
meant	O
to	O
determine	O
the	O
next	O
sous-chef	O
of	O
the	O
castle	O
of	O
the	O
pirate	O
Maz	B-PER
Kanata	I-PER
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Takodana	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 4
# text = The Artiodac Strono Tuggs who worked as head chef at the castle considered the sandwich his favourite entry in the first round, which had tasked the contestants with creating a breakfast platter.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 3562831
The	O
Artiodac	O
Strono	B-PER
Tuggs	I-PER
who	O
worked	O
as	O
head	O
chef	O
at	O
the	O
castle	B-LOC
considered	O
the	O
sandwich	O
his	O
favourite	O
entry	O
in	O
the	O
first	O
round	O
,	O
which	O
had	O
tasked	O
the	O
contestants	O
with	O
creating	O
a	O
breakfast	O
platter	O
.	O

# sent_id = 5
# text = Sean was a human male Jedi Padawan who was active during the High Republic Era.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11885
Sean	B-PER
was	O
a	O
human	O
male	O
Jedi	O
Padawan	O
who	O
was	O
active	O
during	O
the	O
High	O
Republic	O
Era	O
.	O

# sent_id = 6
# text = Sean was brought to the Jedi Temple on Coruscant as a child.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 61650
Sean	B-PER
was	O
brought	O
to	O
the	O
Jedi	B-LOC
Temple	I-LOC
on	O
Coruscant	B-LOC
as	O
a	O
child	O
.	O

# sent_id = 7
# text = He and many other younglings were trained by Jedi Master Oslord.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 20170
He	O
and	O
many	O
other	O
younglings	O
were	O
trained	O
by	O
Jedi	B-PER
Master	I-PER
Oslord	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 8
# text = There he began to train to be a Jedi, but his abilities in The Force always lacked behind his peers.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 14742
There	O
he	O
began	O
to	O
train	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
Jedi	O
,	O
but	O
his	O
abilities	O
in	O
The	O
Force	O
always	O
lacked	O
behind	O
his	O
peers	O
.	O

# sent_id = 9
# text = In 85 BBY, at age fourteen, in what was seen as a somewhat controversial move in the Jedi Order, famed and talented Jedi Master Mostema took him on as a Padawan learner.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31592
In	O
85	O
BBY	O
,	O
at	O
age	O
fourteen	O
,	O
in	O
what	O
was	O
seen	O
as	O
a	O
somewhat	O
controversial	O
move	O
in	O
the	O
Jedi	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
,	O
famed	O
and	O
talented	O
Jedi	B-PER
Master	I-PER
Mostema	I-PER
took	O
him	O
on	O
as	O
a	O
Padawan	O
learner	O
.	O

# sent_id = 10
# text = To justify this decision, she claimed she could best guide the Padawan's growth.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 9577
To	O
justify	O
this	O
decision	O
,	O
she	O
claimed	O
she	O
could	O
best	O
guide	O
the	O
Padawan	O
'	O
s	O
growth	O
.	O

# sent_id = 11
# text = Sean's lightsaber was a Jedi lightsaber constructed by Jedi Padawan Sean during the High Republic Era.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 22172
Sean	B-PER
'	O
s	O
lightsaber	O
was	O
a	O
Jedi	O
lightsaber	O
constructed	O
by	O
Jedi	O
Padawan	O
Sean	B-PER
during	O
the	O
High	O
Republic	O
Era	O
.	O

# sent_id = 12
# text = The search for Ezra was a voyage into the Unknown Regions undertaken by the Mandalorian Spectre Sabine Wren and former Jedi Padawan Ahsoka Tano to find Ezra Bridger, a Padawan and friend of theirs.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 108509
The	O
search	O
for	O
Ezra	B-PER
was	O
a	O
voyage	O
into	O
the	O
Unknown	B-LOC
Regions	I-LOC
undertaken	O
by	O
the	O
Mandalorian	O
Spectre	O
Sabine	B-PER
Wren	I-PER
and	O
former	O
Jedi	O
Padawan	O
Ahsoka	B-PER
Tano	I-PER
to	O
find	O
Ezra	B-PER
Bridger	I-PER
,	O
a	O
Padawan	O
and	O
friend	O
of	O
theirs	O
.	O

# sent_id = 13
# text = Years earlier during the Liberation of Lothal, Bridger had summoned a pod of purrgil to defeat the Seventh Fleet, and, after those starships were dealt with, the animals attacked the Star Destroyer Chimaera, pulling it, Grand Admiral Thrawn, and Bridger away into hyperspace to deep space.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 58296
Years	O
earlier	O
during	O
the	O
Liberation	O
of	O
Lothal	B-LOC
,	O
Bridger	B-PER
had	O
summoned	O
a	O
pod	O
of	O
purrgil	O
to	O
defeat	O
the	O
Seventh	O
Fleet	O
,	O
and	O
,	O
after	O
those	O
starships	O
were	O
dealt	O
with	O
,	O
the	O
animals	O
attacked	O
the	O
Star	B-MISC
Destroyer	I-MISC
Chimaera	I-MISC
,	O
pulling	O
it	O
,	O
Grand	B-PER
Admiral	I-PER
Thrawn	I-PER
,	O
and	O
Bridger	B-PER
away	O
into	O
hyperspace	O
to	O
deep	O
space	O
.	O

# sent_id = 14
# text = In 3 ABY, the Freemakers, a family of scavengers embarked on a quest to search for the legendary Kyber Saber, a lightsaber forged completely from Kyber crystals.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 20213
In	O
3	O
ABY	O
,	O
the	O
Freemakers	O
,	O
a	O
family	O
of	O
scavengers	O
embarked	O
on	O
a	O
quest	O
to	O
search	O
for	O
the	O
legendary	O
Kyber	O
Saber	O
,	O
a	O
lightsaber	O
forged	O
completely	O
from	O
Kyber	O
crystals	O
.	O

# sent_id = 15
# text = The Freemakers were egged on and assisted by Naare, a secret Sith agent of Emperor Palpatine, who wanted to exploit the powers of the Kyber Saber for himself.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31304
The	O
Freemakers	O
were	O
egged	O
on	O
and	O
assisted	O
by	O
Naare	B-PER
,	O
a	O
secret	O
Sith	O
agent	O
of	O
Emperor	B-PER
Palpatine	I-PER
,	O
who	O
wanted	O
to	O
exploit	O
the	O
powers	O
of	O
the	O
Kyber	O
Saber	O
for	O
himself	O
.	O

# sent_id = 16
# text = After the Freemakers learnt of Naare's true identity, the Freemakers at the urging of the youngest member Rowan Freemaker took part in a race against Naare and the Hutt crime lord Graballa to find the pieces of the Kyber Saber.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 51836
After	O
the	O
Freemakers	B-ORG
learnt	O
of	O
Naare	B-PER
'	O
s	O
true	O
identity	O
,	O
the	O
Freemakers	B-ORG
at	O
the	O
urging	O
of	O
the	O
youngest	O
member	O
Rowan	B-PER
Freemaker	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
a	O
race	O
against	O
Naare	B-PER
and	O
the	O
Hutt	O
crime	O
lord	O
Graballa	B-PER
to	O
find	O
the	O
pieces	O
of	O
the	O
Kyber	O
Saber	O
.	O

# sent_id = 17
# text = Though Naare managed to reforge the Kyber Saber, the Freemakers managed to steal it from her following a skirmish on Coruscant.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 13637
Though	O
Naare	B-PER
managed	O
to	O
reforge	O
the	O
Kyber	O
Saber	O
,	O
the	O
Freemakers	B-ORG
managed	O
to	O
steal	O
it	O
from	O
her	O
following	O
a	O
skirmish	O
on	O
Coruscant	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 18
# text = After Rowan destroyed the Kyber Saber, the Freemakers joined the Rebel Alliance.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 14690
After	O
Rowan	B-PER
destroyed	O
the	O
Kyber	O
Saber	O
,	O
the	O
Freemakers	B-ORG
joined	O
the	O
Rebel	B-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 19
# text = A search for a Tusken totem was undertaken on the planet Tatooine.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 10103
A	O
search	O
for	O
a	O
Tusken	O
totem	O
was	O
undertaken	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Tatooine	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 20
# text = The search for Yiprukk was a search by a mother looking for her Force-sensitive son Yiprukk during the Clone Wars.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 19407
The	O
search	O
for	O
Yiprukk	B-PER
was	O
a	O
search	O
by	O
a	O
mother	O
looking	O
for	O
her	O
Force-sensitive	O
son	O
Yiprukk	B-PER
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
.	O

# sent_id = 21
# text = Seastone was a green substance.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 3314
Seastone	O
was	O
a	O
green	O
substance	O
.	O

# sent_id = 22
# text = The carved grip of Jedi Master Avar Kriss' lightsaber was inlaid with it.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 93797
The	O
carved	O
grip	O
of	O
Jedi	B-PER
Master	I-PER
Avar	I-PER
Kriss	I-PER
'	O
lightsaber	O
was	O
inlaid	O
with	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 23
# text = Seatroopers were stormtroopers in the Stormtrooper Corps of the Galactic Empire that specialized in aquatic environments.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 29391
Seatroopers	O
were	O
stormtroopers	O
in	O
the	O
Stormtrooper	B-ORG
Corps	I-ORG
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
that	O
specialized	O
in	O
aquatic	O
environments	O
.	O

# sent_id = 24
# text = They were equipped with various aquatic equipment including scuba backpacks, underwater propulsion jets, and flippers.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 690241
They	O
were	O
equipped	O
with	O
various	O
aquatic	O
equipment	O
including	O
scuba	O
backpacks	O
,	O
underwater	O
propulsion	O
jets	O
,	O
and	O
flippers	O
.	O

# sent_id = 25
# text = Seatroopers saw action on the planet Mon Cala in 18 BBY.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 15110
Seatroopers	O
saw	O
action	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Mon	B-LOC
Cala	I-LOC
in	O
18	O
BBY	O
.	O

# sent_id = 26
# text = Other seatroopers were also stationed on the planet Lothal.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 12437
Other	O
seatroopers	O
were	O
also	O
stationed	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Lothal	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 27
# text = Seaweed came from the ocean and could be a type of foodstuff.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 10390
Seaweed	O
came	O
from	O
the	O
ocean	O
and	O
could	O
be	O
a	O
type	O
of	O
foodstuff	O
.	O

# sent_id = 28
# text = The Lanai served spiced seaweed at the Festival of Return on Ahch-To.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 42642
The	O
Lanai	O
served	O
spiced	O
seaweed	O
at	O
the	O
Festival	B-MISC
of	O
Return	I-MISC
on	O
Ahch-To	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 29
# text = When Poe Dameron and Finn attended Nifera Shu's birthday party, a variety of seafoods were displayed on beds of multicolored seaweed in keeping with the ocean theme.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 124712
When	O
Poe	B-PER
Dameron	I-PER
and	O
Finn	B-PER
attended	O
Nifera	B-PER
Shu	I-PER
'	O
s	O
birthday	O
party	O
,	O
a	O
variety	O
of	O
seafoods	O
were	O
displayed	O
on	O
beds	O
of	O
multicolored	O
seaweed	O
in	O
keeping	O
with	O
the	O
ocean	O
theme	O
.	O

# sent_id = 30
# text = Seaweed clung to Luke Skywalker's T-65B X-wing starfighter when he raised it from the waters of Ahch-To after its years of submersion.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31695
Seaweed	O
clung	O
to	O
Luke	B-PER
Skywalker	I-PER
'	O
s	O
T-65B	B-MISC
X-wing	I-MISC
starfighter	O
when	O
he	O
raised	O
it	O
from	O
the	O
waters	O
of	O
Ahch-To	B-LOC
after	O
its	O
years	O
of	O
submersion	O
.	O

# sent_id = 31
# text = Seb Astro is a human male Bespin Wing Guard at Cloud City working under Lando Calrissian as his top guard.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 34822
Seb	B-PER
Astro	I-PER
is	O
a	O
human	O
male	O
Bespin	O
Wing	O
Guard	O
at	O
Cloud	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
working	O
under	O
Lando	B-PER
Calrissian	I-PER
as	O
his	O
top	O
guard	O
.	O

# sent_id = 32
# text = Sebla Sarobia was a human female who attended the Aki-Aki Festival of the Ancestors in the Forbidden Valley of the planet Pasaana in 35 ABY.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 146789
Sebla	B-PER
Sarobia	I-PER
was	O
a	O
human	O
female	O
who	O
attended	O
the	O
Aki-Aki	B-MISC
Festival	I-MISC
of	O
the	O
Ancestors	O
in	O
the	O
Forbidden	B-LOC
Valley	I-LOC
of	O
the	O
planet	B-LOC
Pasaana	I-LOC
in	O
35	O
ABY	O
.	O

# sent_id = 33
# text = She danced with a group of humans while the hermit Lando Calrissian led several Resistance agents through the festival to safety after the agents were spotted by the First Order.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 30990
She	O
danced	O
with	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
humans	O
while	O
the	O
hermit	O
Lando	B-PER
Calrissian	I-PER
led	O
several	O
Resistance	O
agents	O
through	O
the	O
festival	O
to	O
safety	O
after	O
the	O
agents	O
were	O
spotted	O
by	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 34
# text = Seboca was a Dug holovid star.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 89834
Seboca	B-PER
was	O
a	O
Dug	O
holovid	O
star	O
.	O

# sent_id = 35
# text = In 22 BBY, shortly before the beginning of the Clone Wars, Seboca was entertaining Senator Bogg Tyrell on an airspeeder when Jedi Knight Obi-Wan Kenobi nearly crashed against them while trying to capture the Clawdite bounty hunter Zam Wesell, leading Seboca to insult the Jedi for nearly hitting them.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 69589
In	O
22	O
BBY	O
,	O
shortly	O
before	O
the	O
beginning	O
of	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
,	O
Seboca	B-PER
was	O
entertaining	O
Senator	B-PER
Bogg	I-PER
Tyrell	I-PER
on	O
an	O
airspeeder	O
when	O
Jedi	B-PER
Knight	I-PER
Obi-Wan	I-PER
Kenobi	I-PER
nearly	O
crashed	O
against	O
them	O
while	O
trying	O
to	O
capture	O
the	O
Clawdite	O
bounty	O
hunter	O
Zam	B-PER
Wesell	I-PER
,	O
leading	O
Seboca	B-PER
to	O
insult	O
the	O
Jedi	O
for	O
nearly	O
hitting	O
them	O
.	O

# sent_id = 36
# text = Seboca was later present at Dex's Diner conversing with two patrons as Kenobi talked with Dexter Jettster about a Kamino saberdart.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 19109
Seboca	B-PER
was	O
later	O
present	O
at	O
Dex	B-PER
'	O
s	O
Diner	O
conversing	O
with	O
two	O
patrons	O
as	O
Kenobi	B-PER
talked	O
with	O
Dexter	B-PER
Jettster	I-PER
about	O
a	O
Kamino	O
saberdart	O
.	O

# sent_id = 37
# text = He wore a brown pants and a red jacket and that was the latest fashion on Coruscant.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 9317
He	O
wore	O
a	O
brown	O
pants	O
and	O
a	O
red	O
jacket	O
and	O
that	O
was	O
the	O
latest	O
fashion	O
on	O
Coruscant	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 38
# text = Sebris Alpha was a location on Hays Minor.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 17917
Sebris	B-LOC
Alpha	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
on	O
Hays	B-LOC
Minor	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 39
# text = Sebris Beta was a location on Hays Minor.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 17890
Sebris	B-LOC
Beta	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
on	O
Hays	B-LOC
Minor	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 40
# text = Sebris Gamma was a village on the planet Hays Minor.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 16427
Sebris	B-LOC
Gamma	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
village	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Hays	B-LOC
Minor	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 41
# text = It was destroyed by ground-penetrating incendiary bombs dropped by First Order bombers when the residents refused to follow the First Order's orders.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 54449
It	O
was	O
destroyed	O
by	O
ground-penetrating	O
incendiary	O
bombs	O
dropped	O
by	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
bombers	O
when	O
the	O
residents	O
refused	O
to	O
follow	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
orders	O
.	O

# sent_id = 42
# text = Sebulba was a male Dug who hailed from the planet of Malastare.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 13781
Sebulba	B-PER
was	O
a	O
male	O
Dug	O
who	O
hailed	O
from	O
the	O
planet	O
of	O
Malastare	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 43
# text = A vicious podracer pilot who flew a massive orange podracer with a split-x configuration, Sebulba would often bump and smash his way through the competition.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 17611
A	O
vicious	O
podracer	O
pilot	O
who	O
flew	O
a	O
massive	O
orange	O
podracer	O
with	O
a	O
split-x	O
configuration	O
,	O
Sebulba	B-PER
would	O
often	O
bump	O
and	O
smash	O
his	O
way	O
through	O
the	O
competition	O
.	O

# sent_id = 44
# text = A skilled pilot in his own right, he nonetheless opted to install various illegal weapons on his podracer, such as a flamethrower built into the left engine, to ensure his victories on the track.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11615
A	O
skilled	O
pilot	O
in	O
his	O
own	O
right	O
,	O
he	O
nonetheless	O
opted	O
to	O
install	O
various	O
illegal	O
weapons	O
on	O
his	O
podracer	O
,	O
such	O
as	O
a	O
flamethrower	O
built	O
into	O
the	O
left	O
engine	O
,	O
to	O
ensure	O
his	O
victories	O
on	O
the	O
track	O
.	O

# sent_id = 45
# text = The crowd favorite of a course known as the Boonta Eve Classic, located on the Outer Rim planet of Tatooine, Sebulba maintained a strong rivalry with one of podracings few human participants, a young boy named Anakin Skywalker.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 35466
The	O
crowd	O
favorite	O
of	O
a	O
course	O
known	O
as	O
the	O
Boonta	B-MISC
Eve	I-MISC
Classic	I-MISC
,	O
located	O
on	O
the	O
Outer	B-LOC
Rim	I-LOC
planet	O
of	O
Tatooine	B-LOC
,	O
Sebulba	B-PER
maintained	O
a	O
strong	O
rivalry	O
with	O
one	O
of	O
podracings	O
few	O
human	O
participants	O
,	O
a	O
young	O
boy	O
named	O
Anakin	B-PER
Skywalker	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 46
# text = A short while after the Invasion of Naboo, Sebulba and Skywalker competed in a Boonta race together.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 44580
A	O
short	O
while	O
after	O
the	O
Invasion	O
of	O
Naboo	B-LOC
,	O
Sebulba	B-PER
and	O
Skywalker	B-PER
competed	O
in	O
a	O
Boonta	B-MISC
race	O
together	O
.	O

# sent_id = 47
# text = The Dug Sebulba owned a massive orange podracer, which he used to podrace with.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 8616
The	O
Dug	O
Sebulba	B-PER
owned	O
a	O
massive	O
orange	O
podracer	O
,	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
podrace	O
with	O
.	O

# sent_id = 48
# text = Sebulba was an ambitious cheater, and had secretly installed not only ion disrupters and magna spikes, but two illegal flamethrowers into each engine.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 9877
Sebulba	B-PER
was	O
an	O
ambitious	O
cheater	O
,	O
and	O
had	O
secretly	O
installed	O
not	O
only	O
ion	O
disrupters	O
and	O
magna	O
spikes	O
,	O
but	O
two	O
illegal	O
flamethrowers	O
into	O
each	O
engine	O
.	O

# sent_id = 49
# text = Sebulba could control the flamethrowers from his cockpit, and used them to torch other pilots.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 6406
Sebulba	B-PER
could	O
control	O
the	O
flamethrowers	O
from	O
his	O
cockpit	O
,	O
and	O
used	O
them	O
to	O
torch	O
other	O
pilots	O
.	O

# sent_id = 50
# text = The Secessionist Faction, more simply known as the Secessionists, was an extreme political wing of the Pacifist Faction of the senate of the Galactic Republic.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 32168
The	O
Secessionist	B-ORG
Faction	I-ORG
,	O
more	O
simply	O
known	O
as	O
the	O
Secessionists	B-ORG
,	O
was	O
an	O
extreme	O
political	O
wing	O
of	O
the	O
Pacifist	B-ORG
Faction	I-ORG
of	O
the	O
senate	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 51
# text = The Secessionists represented star systems that were considering leaving the Republic, and although the body was small as a voting bloc, it was vital as systems could increase their influence by threatening to secede.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 20922
The	O
Secessionists	B-ORG
represented	O
star	O
systems	O
that	O
were	O
considering	O
leaving	O
the	O
Republic	B-ORG
,	O
and	O
although	O
the	O
body	O
was	O
small	O
as	O
a	O
voting	O
bloc	O
,	O
it	O
was	O
vital	O
as	O
systems	O
could	O
increase	O
their	O
influence	O
by	O
threatening	O
to	O
secede	O
.	O

# sent_id = 52
# text = Despite this, most systems sought diplomatic solutions.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 24479
Despite	O
this	O
,	O
most	O
systems	O
sought	O
diplomatic	O
solutions	O
.	O

# sent_id = 53
# text = Secon Daree was a Lutrillian who piloted an X-wing starfighter in the Rebel Alliance's Starfighter Corps during the ill-fated attack on Lothal.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 32065
Secon	B-PER
Daree	I-PER
was	O
a	O
Lutrillian	O
who	O
piloted	O
an	O
X-wing	B-MISC
starfighter	O
in	O
the	O
Rebel	B-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
Starfighter	O
Corps	O
during	O
the	O
ill-fated	O
attack	O
on	O
Lothal	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 54
# text = Daree was captured by the Noghri assassin Rukh, who handed the pilot to Imperial custody.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 18993
Daree	B-PER
was	O
captured	O
by	O
the	O
Noghri	O
assassin	O
Rukh	B-PER
,	O
who	O
handed	O
the	O
pilot	O
to	O
Imperial	O
custody	O
.	O

# sent_id = 55
# text = A second was a short unit of time measurement.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 7280
A	O
second	O
was	O
a	O
short	O
unit	O
of	O
time	O
measurement	O
.	O

# sent_id = 56
# text = Shortly after the infiltration of Hivebase-1, the Galactic Empire launched an attack on the Son-tuul Pride, led by Lieutenant-Inspector Magna Tolvan.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 42539
Shortly	O
after	O
the	O
infiltration	O
of	O
Hivebase-1	B-LOC
,	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
launched	O
an	O
attack	O
on	O
the	O
Son-tuul	B-ORG
Pride	I-ORG
,	O
led	O
by	O
Lieutenant-Inspector	O
Magna	B-PER
Tolvan	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 57
# text = The entirety of the mercenaries there were either killed or captured except for their leader 0-0-0 and his assailant BT-1 who pretended to be innocent droids caught in the crossfire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 22317
The	O
entirety	O
of	O
the	O
mercenaries	O
there	O
were	O
either	O
killed	O
or	O
captured	O
except	O
for	O
their	O
leader	O
0-0	B-PER
-	I-PER
0	I-PER
and	O
his	O
assailant	O
BT-1	B-PER
who	O
pretended	O
to	O
be	O
innocent	O
droids	O
caught	O
in	O
the	O
crossfire	O
.	O

# sent_id = 58
# text = Tolvan then had Chelli Lona Aphra and Dek-Nil taken away to Accresker Jail.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 23838
Tolvan	B-PER
then	O
had	O
Chelli	B-PER
Lona	I-PER
Aphra	I-PER
and	O
Dek-Nil	B-PER
taken	O
away	O
to	O
Accresker	B-LOC
Jail	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 59
# text = At least two years after the Battle of Christophsis, a second battle took place on the planet Christophsis during the Clone Wars.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 24243
At	O
least	O
two	O
years	O
after	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Christophsis	O
,	O
a	O
second	O
battle	O
took	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Christophsis	B-LOC
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
.	O

# sent_id = 60
# text = After deducing that the Jedi Master Quinlan Vos had fallen to the dark side of the Force, the Jedi Council sent him on a mission to kill the Separatist leader Count Dooku in order to test his loyalty.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 49431
After	O
deducing	O
that	O
the	O
Jedi	B-PER
Master	I-PER
Quinlan	I-PER
Vos	I-PER
had	O
fallen	O
to	O
the	O
dark	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Force	O
,	O
the	O
Jedi	B-ORG
Council	I-ORG
sent	O
him	O
on	O
a	O
mission	O
to	O
kill	O
the	O
Separatist	B-ORG
leader	O
Count	B-PER
Dooku	I-PER
in	O
order	O
to	O
test	O
his	O
loyalty	O
.	O

# sent_id = 61
# text = From Vos' lover Asajj Ventress, the Jedi learned that Dooku's dreadnought would be visiting Christophsis.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 25424
From	O
Vos	B-PER
'	O
lover	O
Asajj	B-PER
Ventress	I-PER
,	O
the	O
Jedi	O
learned	O
that	O
Dooku	B-PER
'	O
s	O
dreadnought	O
would	O
be	O
visiting	O
Christophsis	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 62
# text = Together, Vos and Ventress traveled to Dooku's flagship where Vos managed to engage in a lightsaber duel.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 18265
Together	O
,	O
Vos	B-PER
and	O
Ventress	B-PER
traveled	O
to	O
Dooku	B-PER
'	O
s	O
flagship	O
where	O
Vos	O
managed	O
to	O
engage	O
in	O
a	O
lightsaber	O
duel	O
.	O

# sent_id = 63
# text = Unknown to Vos, the Jedi Obi-Wan Kenobi and Anakin Skywalker tailed along.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 14519
Unknown	O
to	O
Vos	B-PER
,	O
the	O
Jedi	O
Obi-Wan	B-PER
Kenobi	I-PER
and	O
Anakin	B-PER
Skywalker	I-PER
tailed	O
along	O
.	O

# sent_id = 64
# text = The Second Battle of Dathomir was a battle fought during the Clone Wars on Dathomir  between the combined forces of the Sith and the Confederacy of Independent Systems; and the renegade Sith Lord Maul and Mother Talzin.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 115078
The	O
Second	O
Battle	O
of	O
Dathomir	B-LOC
was	O
a	O
battle	O
fought	O
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
on	O
Dathomir	B-LOC
between	O
the	O
combined	O
forces	O
of	O
the	O
Sith	B-ORG
and	O
the	O
Confederacy	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Independent	I-ORG
Systems	I-ORG
;	O
and	O
the	O
renegade	O
Sith	O
Lord	O
Maul	B-PER
and	O
Mother	O
Talzin	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 65
# text = The battle began after Maul brought the captive Sith Lord Count Dooku to Dathomir, so Talzin could drain the Count's life force and use it to return her previously-destroyed physical form.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 32749
The	O
battle	O
began	O
after	O
Maul	B-PER
brought	O
the	O
captive	O
Sith	O
Lord	O
Count	B-PER
Dooku	I-PER
to	O
Dathomir	B-LOC
,	O
so	O
Talzin	B-PER
could	O
drain	O
the	O
Count	B-PER
'	O
s	O
life	O
force	O
and	O
use	O
it	O
to	O
return	O
her	O
previously-destroyed	O
physical	O
form	O
.	O

# sent_id = 66
# text = Darth Sidious was able to trace the location of Dooku, his apprentice, and traveled with General Grievous to Dathomir to rescue Dooku and defeat their enemies.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 29888
Darth	B-PER
Sidious	I-PER
was	O
able	O
to	O
trace	O
the	O
location	O
of	O
Dooku	B-PER
,	O
his	O
apprentice	O
,	O
and	O
traveled	O
with	O
General	B-PER
Grievous	I-PER
to	O
Dathomir	B-LOC
to	O
rescue	O
Dooku	B-PER
and	O
defeat	O
their	O
enemies	O
.	O

# sent_id = 67
# text = The Second Battle of Felucia saw a clash between Galactic Republic and the Separatist Alliance for control of the planet Felucia during the Clone Wars.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 30082
The	O
Second	O
Battle	O
of	O
Felucia	B-LOC
saw	O
a	O
clash	O
between	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
and	O
the	O
Separatist	B-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
for	O
control	O
of	O
the	O
planet	O
Felucia	B-LOC
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
.	O

# sent_id = 68
# text = Having been forced into a retreat at the first battle of Felucia, the Republic re-established a presence there thanks to the efforts of Jedi General Anakin Skywalker and his Padawan, Ahsoka Tano, who led their clone troopers on an offensive into Separatist-held territory.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 34146
Having	O
been	O
forced	O
into	O
a	O
retreat	O
at	O
the	O
first	O
battle	O
of	O
Felucia	B-LOC
,	O
the	O
Republic	B-ORG
re-established	O
a	O
presence	O
there	O
thanks	O
to	O
the	O
efforts	O
of	O
Jedi	O
General	O
Anakin	B-PER
Skywalker	I-PER
and	O
his	O
Padawan	O
,	O
Ahsoka	B-PER
Tano	I-PER
,	O
who	O
led	O
their	O
clone	O
troopers	O
on	O
an	O
offensive	O
into	O
Separatist-held	B-ORG
territory	O
.	O

# sent_id = 69
# text = In retaliation, General Grievous supplied one of his outposts on Felucia with reinforcements to secure the system for the Confederacy.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 33709
In	O
retaliation	O
,	O
General	B-PER
Grievous	I-PER
supplied	O
one	O
of	O
his	O
outposts	O
on	O
Felucia	B-LOC
with	O
reinforcements	O
to	O
secure	O
the	O
system	O
for	O
the	O
Confederacy	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 70
# text = Responding to the arrival of the battle droid detachment, Skywalker, Tano, and Jedi Master Plo Koon targeted the enemy outpost with a three-pronged assault, each leading a squad to divide the Separatist defenses.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 21698
Responding	O
to	O
the	O
arrival	O
of	O
the	O
battle	O
droid	O
detachment	O
,	O
Skywalker	B-PER
,	O
Tano	B-PER
,	O
and	O
Jedi	O
Master	O
Plo	B-PER
Koon	I-PER
targeted	O
the	O
enemy	O
outpost	O
with	O
a	O
three-pronged	O
assault	O
,	O
each	O
leading	O
a	O
squad	O
to	O
divide	O
the	O
Separatist	B-ORG
defenses	O
.	O

# sent_id = 71
# text = The Second Battle of Geonosis, also known as the battle of Geonosis, took place during the Clone Wars on the planet Geonosis, the site of the conflict's opening battle.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 15903
The	O
Second	O
Battle	O
of	O
Geonosis	B-LOC
,	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
the	O
battle	O
of	O
Geonosis	B-LOC
,	O
took	O
place	O
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Geonosis	B-LOC
,	O
the	O
site	O
of	O
the	O
conflict	O
'	O
s	O
opening	O
battle	O
.	O

# sent_id = 72
# text = Second class  droids were droids skilled in engineering and technical sciences.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 6644
Second	O
class	O
droids	O
were	O
droids	O
skilled	O
in	O
engineering	O
and	O
technical	O
sciences	O
.	O

# sent_id = 73
# text = Astromech droids were second class droids.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 6989
Astromech	O
droids	O
were	O
second	O
class	O
droids	O
.	O

# sent_id = 74
# text = The second coronation of Réillata as monarch of Naboo took place on the steps of Theed Royal Palace in 28 BBY.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 76452
The	O
second	O
coronation	O
of	O
R	B-PER
é	I-PER
illata	I-PER
as	O
monarch	O
of	O
Naboo	B-LOC
took	O
place	O
on	O
the	O
steps	O
of	O
Theed	B-LOC
Royal	I-LOC
Palace	I-LOC
in	O
28	O
BBY	O
.	O

# sent_id = 75
# text = Réillata was re-elected to the throne of the Royal House of Naboo to serve a second and final term as Queen following the stepping down of Padmé Amidala.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31272
R	B-PER
é	I-PER
illata	I-PER
was	O
re-elected	O
to	O
the	O
throne	O
of	O
the	O
Royal	B-ORG
House	I-ORG
of	O
Naboo	B-LOC
to	O
serve	O
a	O
second	O
and	O
final	O
term	O
as	O
Queen	O
following	O
the	O
stepping	O
down	O
of	O
Padm	B-PER
é	I-PER
Amidala	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 76
# text = Second defense officer was a position within the starfleet of the Galactic Empire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 10753
Second	O
defense	O
officer	O
was	O
a	O
position	O
within	O
the	O
starfleet	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 77
# text = Second Defense Overlord was a position in the Garwian Unity.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 14712
Second	O
Defense	O
Overlord	O
was	O
a	O
position	O
in	O
the	O
Garwian	B-ORG
Unity	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 78
# text = Frangelic held the position at the time of the Clone Wars.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 6674
Frangelic	B-PER
held	O
the	O
position	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
.	O

# sent_id = 79
# text = Second flight was a unit of T-65B X-wing starfighters within Red Squadron, a starfighter squadron that was part of the Alliance to Restore the Republic.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 319122
Second	O
flight	O
was	O
a	O
unit	O
of	O
T-65B	B-MISC
X-wing	I-MISC
starfighters	I-MISC
within	O
Red	B-ORG
Squadron	I-ORG
,	O
a	O
starfighter	O
squadron	O
that	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
Alliance	B-ORG
to	O
Restore	I-ORG
the	O
Republic	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 80
# text = They took part in the Battle of Yavin and was led by Major Ralo Surrel, with Harb Binli and John D. Branon as his wingmen.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 40397
They	O
took	O
part	O
in	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Yavin	B-LOC
and	O
was	O
led	O
by	O
Major	O
Ralo	B-PER
Surrel	I-PER
,	O
with	O
Harb	B-PER
Binli	I-PER
and	O
John	B-PER
D	I-PER
.	O
Branon	B-PER
as	O
his	O
wingmen	O
.	O

# sent_id = 81
# text = Second Lieutenant was a rank used within the Galactic Empire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 10494
Second	O
Lieutenant	O
was	O
a	O
rank	O
used	O
within	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 82
# text = The deck officer Frobb held the rank of second lieutenant in the year 0 BBY.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 10846
The	O
deck	O
officer	O
Frobb	B-PER
held	O
the	O
rank	O
of	O
second	O
lieutenant	O
in	O
the	O
year	O
0	O
BBY	O
.	O

# sent_id = 83
# text = Second Lieutenant Commander was a military rank used by the Galactic Empire during the Galactic Civil War.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11408
Second	O
Lieutenant	O
Commander	O
was	O
a	O
military	O
rank	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
during	O
the	O
Galactic	O
Civil	O
War	O
.	O

# sent_id = 84
# text = Teso Broosh held the rank when he was part of the 204th Imperial Fighter Wing.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 18700
Teso	B-PER
Broosh	I-PER
held	O
the	O
rank	O
when	O
he	O
was	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
204th	B-MISC
Imperial	I-MISC
Fighter	I-MISC
Wing	I-MISC
.	O

# sent_id = 85
# text = Second mate was a title used aboard a starships crew.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 5266
Second	O
mate	O
was	O
a	O
title	O
used	O
aboard	O
a	O
starships	O
crew	O
.	O

# sent_id = 86
# text = In 34 ABY, the smuggler Han Solo offered the scavenger Rey the opportunity to be the second mate on his ship, the Millennium Falcon, as he was looking for more crew to help himself and Chewbacca.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 95906
In	O
34	O
ABY	O
,	O
the	O
smuggler	O
Han	B-PER
Solo	I-PER
offered	O
the	O
scavenger	O
Rey	B-PER
the	O
opportunity	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
second	O
mate	O
on	O
his	O
ship	O
,	O
the	O
Millennium	B-MISC
Falcon	I-MISC
,	O
as	O
he	O
was	O
looking	O
for	O
more	O
crew	O
to	O
help	O
himself	O
and	O
Chewbacca	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 87
# text = Rey, however, declined the offer as she felt she had to return to Jakku.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 15445
Rey	B-PER
,	O
however	O
,	O
declined	O
the	O
offer	O
as	O
she	O
felt	O
she	O
had	O
to	O
return	O
to	O
Jakku	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 88
# text = Second Minister was a political rank on Clabron, directly under Grand Minister.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 12606
Second	O
Minister	O
was	O
a	O
political	O
rank	O
on	O
Clabron	B-LOC
,	O
directly	O
under	O
Grand	O
Minister	O
.	O

# sent_id = 89
# text = The Clabronian Tarmin held the title during the Clone Wars, but replaced Stin as Grand Minister after he was assassinated.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 16639
The	O
Clabronian	O
Tarmin	B-PER
held	O
the	O
title	O
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
,	O
but	O
replaced	O
Stin	B-PER
as	O
Grand	O
Minister	O
after	O
he	O
was	O
assassinated	O
.	O

# sent_id = 90
# text = During the reign of the Galactic Empire, Jedi Padawan Cal Kestis undertook a second mission to the planet Bogano to recover Eno Cordova's holocron.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 26992
During	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
,	O
Jedi	O
Padawan	O
Cal	B-PER
Kestis	I-PER
undertook	O
a	O
second	O
mission	O
to	O
the	O
planet	O
Bogano	B-LOC
to	O
recover	O
Eno	B-PER
Cordova	I-PER
'	O
s	O
holocron	O
.	O

# sent_id = 91
# text = After reaching the Bogano Vault, Cal was confronted by the Second Sister, who stole the holocron, though she lost her lightsaber to him.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 21754
After	O
reaching	O
the	O
Bogano	B-MISC
Vault	I-MISC
,	O
Cal	B-PER
was	O
confronted	O
by	O
the	O
Second	B-PER
Sister	I-PER
,	O
who	O
stole	O
the	O
holocron	O
,	O
though	O
she	O
lost	O
her	O
lightsaber	O
to	O
him	O
.	O

# sent_id = 92
# text = During the mission on the Colossus platform, Kazuda Xiono undertook a second mission into Doza Tower to try and find out how Captain Imanuel Doza might be colluding with the First Order.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 54671
During	O
the	O
mission	O
on	O
the	O
Colossus	O
platform	O
,	O
Kazuda	B-PER
Xiono	I-PER
undertook	O
a	O
second	O
mission	O
into	O
Doza	B-MISC
Tower	I-MISC
to	O
try	O
and	O
find	O
out	O
how	O
Captain	O
Imanuel	B-PER
Doza	I-PER
might	O
be	O
colluding	O
with	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 93
# text = He was unwittingly assisted by Doza's daughter Torra, who had snuck out of the tower that day after her father had attempted to lock her in her room for her own protection while he had a meeting with the First Order's Commander Pyre.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 25239
He	O
was	O
unwittingly	O
assisted	O
by	O
Doza	B-PER
'	O
s	O
daughter	O
Torra	B-PER
,	O
who	O
had	O
snuck	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
tower	O
that	O
day	O
after	O
her	O
father	O
had	O
attempted	O
to	O
lock	O
her	O
in	O
her	O
room	O
for	O
her	O
own	O
protection	O
while	O
he	O
had	O
a	O
meeting	O
with	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
Commander	O
Pyre	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 94
# text = Jedi Plo Koon and Ahsoka Tano conducted a mission to Florrum during the Clone Wars to confront Boba Fett, who had allied with bounty hunter Aurra
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 27498
Jedi	O
Plo	B-PER
Koon	I-PER
and	O
Ahsoka	B-PER
Tano	I-PER
conducted	O
a	O
mission	O
to	O
Florrum	B-LOC
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
to	O
confront	O
Boba	B-PER
Fett	I-PER
,	O
who	O
had	O
allied	O
with	O
bounty	O
hunter	O
Aurra	B-PER

# sent_id = 95
# text = Sing to kill Jedi Master Mace Windu.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 18830
Sing	B-PER
to	O
kill	O
Jedi	O
Master	O
Mace	B-PER
Windu	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 96
# text = The mission ended with the arrest of Fett and Bossk, while Sing was presumed dead.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 8858
The	O
mission	O
ended	O
with	O
the	O
arrest	O
of	O
Fett	B-PER
and	O
Bossk	B-PER
,	O
while	O
Sing	B-PER
was	O
presumed	O
dead	O
.	O

# sent_id = 97
# text = Jedi Master Obi-Wan Kenobi executed a mission to prevent bounty hunter Cad Bane from kidnapping Wee Dunn on Rodia during the Clone Wars.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 28335
Jedi	O
Master	O
Obi-Wan	B-PER
Kenobi	I-PER
executed	O
a	O
mission	O
to	O
prevent	O
bounty	O
hunter	O
Cad	B-PER
Bane	I-PER
from	O
kidnapping	O
Wee	B-PER
Dunn	I-PER
on	O
Rodia	B-LOC
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
.	O

# sent_id = 98
# text = In 2 BBY, Phoenix Cell undertook a second mission to the planet Ryloth to recover the Kalikori artifact from the Galactic Empire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 28273
In	O
2	O
BBY	O
,	O
Phoenix	B-PER
Cell	I-PER
undertook	O
a	O
second	O
mission	O
to	O
the	O
planet	O
Ryloth	B-LOC
to	O
recover	O
the	O
Kalikori	B-MISC
artifact	O
from	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 99
# text = Hera Syndulla, Ezra Bridger, and Chopper infiltrated the Syndulla residence, which had become the new Imperial headquarters in the Tann Province.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 45800
Hera	B-PER
Syndulla	I-PER
,	O
Ezra	B-PER
Bridger	I-PER
,	O
and	O
Chopper	B-PER
infiltrated	O
the	O
Syndulla	B-LOC
residence	I-LOC
,	O
which	O
had	O
become	O
the	O
new	O
Imperial	O
headquarters	O
in	O
the	O
Tann	B-LOC
Province	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 100
# text = Meanwhile, the Free Ryloth Movement leader Cham Syndulla, Gobi Glie, Numa, and the other Spectres staged a diversionary attack in the Tulara Ravine.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 30186
Meanwhile	O
,	O
the	O
Free	O
Ryloth	O
Movement	O
leader	O
Cham	B-PER
Syndulla	I-PER
,	O
Gobi	B-PER
Glie	I-PER
,	O
Numa	B-PER
,	O
and	O
the	O
other	O
Spectres	O
staged	O
a	O
diversionary	O
attack	O
in	O
the	O
Tulara	B-LOC
Ravine	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 101
# text = Hera and Ezra were captured by Grand Admiral Thrawn and his subordinate Captain Slavin.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 10297
Hera	B-PER
and	O
Ezra	B-PER
were	O
captured	O
by	O
Grand	O
Admiral	O
Thrawn	B-PER
and	O
his	O
subordinate	O
Captain	O
Slavin	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 102
# text = Thrawn added the Kalikori to his art collection and delegated the rest of the military operations to Slavin.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 16052
Thrawn	B-PER
added	O
the	O
Kalikori	B-MISC
to	O
his	O
art	O
collection	O
and	O
delegated	O
the	O
rest	O
of	O
the	O
military	O
operations	O
to	O
Slavin	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 103
# text = Captain Slavin then used Hera and Ezra as hostages to force Cham to surrender himself.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 23773
Captain	O
Slavin	B-PER
then	O
used	O
Hera	B-PER
and	O
Ezra	B-PER
as	O
hostages	O
to	O
force	O
Cham	B-PER
to	O
surrender	O
himself	O
.	O

# sent_id = 104
# text = However, Hera got Chopper to plant explosives throughout the building.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 8039
However	O
,	O
Hera	B-PER
got	O
Chopper	B-PER
to	O
plant	O
explosives	O
throughout	O
the	O
building	O
.	O

# sent_id = 105
# text = This created an explosion which allowed the two rebel factions to escape.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 5771
This	O
created	O
an	O
explosion	O
which	O
allowed	O
the	O
two	O
rebel	O
factions	O
to	O
escape	O
.	O

# sent_id = 106
# text = In 2 BBY, members of Phoenix Cell undertook a mission to the third moon of Concord Dawn.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 26149
In	O
2	O
BBY	O
,	O
members	O
of	O
Phoenix	B-ORG
Cell	I-ORG
undertook	O
a	O
mission	O
to	O
the	O
third	O
moon	O
of	O
Concord	B-LOC
Dawn	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 107
# text = After the Phoenix Cell lost contact with the Mandalorian Protectors, Fenn Rau, Sabine Wren, Ezra Bridger, and Chopper traveled to the third moon to investigate.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 43717
After	O
the	O
Phoenix	B-ORG
Cell	I-ORG
lost	O
contact	O
with	O
the	O
Mandalorian	B-ORG
Protectors	I-ORG
,	O
Fenn	B-PER
Rau	I-PER
,	O
Sabine	B-PER
Wren	I-PER
,	O
Ezra	B-PER
Bridger	I-PER
,	O
and	O
Chopper	B-PER
traveled	O
to	O
the	O
third	O
moon	O
to	O
investigate	O
.	O

# sent_id = 108
# text = They discovered that Imperial Mandalorians under Viceroy Gar Saxon had attacked the encampment and massacred the Protectors.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 23025
They	O
discovered	O
that	O
Imperial	O
Mandalorians	O
under	O
Viceroy	B-PER
Gar	I-PER
Saxon	I-PER
had	O
attacked	O
the	O
encampment	O
and	O
massacred	O
the	O
Protectors	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 109
# text = Working together, they managed to escape the Protectors and flee offworld.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 12745
Working	O
together	O
,	O
they	O
managed	O
to	O
escape	O
the	O
Protectors	B-ORG
and	O
flee	O
offworld	O
.	O

# sent_id = 110
# text = Due to their shared experiences, Rau decided to join the rebellion.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 8940
Due	O
to	O
their	O
shared	O
experiences	O
,	O
Rau	B-PER
decided	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
rebellion	O
.	O

# sent_id = 114
# text = During the reign of the Galactic Empire, Jedi Padawan Cal Kestis undertook a second mission to the planet Zeffo to prevent the Galactic Empire from learning the secrets of the tomb of Miktrull.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31981
During	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
,	O
Jedi	O
Padawan	O
Cal	B-PER
Kestis	I-PER
undertook	O
a	O
second	O
mission	O
to	O
the	O
planet	O
Zeffo	B-LOC
to	O
prevent	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
from	O
learning	O
the	O
secrets	O
of	O
the	O
tomb	O
of	O
Miktrull	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 115
# text = The Second Moon of Thrinittik was a rocky moon.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11866
The	O
Second	B-LOC
Moon	I-LOC
of	I-LOC
Thrinittik	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
rocky	O
moon	O
.	O

# sent_id = 116
# text = As a child, Chelli Aphra lived in a house in the University Quarter on the moon, along with her mother Lona Aphra and father Korin Aphra.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 29818
As	O
a	O
child	O
,	O
Chelli	B-PER
Aphra	I-PER
lived	O
in	O
a	O
house	O
in	O
the	O
University	B-LOC
Quarter	I-LOC
on	O
the	O
moon	O
,	O
along	O
with	O
her	O
mother	O
Lona	B-PER
Aphra	I-PER
and	O
father	O
Korin	B-PER
Aphra	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 117
# text = Second officer was a position held by an individual who served as third in command of a starship.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 6883
Second	O
officer	O
was	O
a	O
position	O
held	O
by	O
an	O
individual	O
who	O
served	O
as	O
third	O
in	O
command	O
of	O
a	O
starship	O
.	O

# sent_id = 118
# text = Toshma Jefkin served as the second officer aboard the Tantive IV.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 83217
Toshma	B-PER
Jefkin	I-PER
served	O
as	O
the	O
second	O
officer	O
aboard	O
the	O
Tantive	B-MISC
IV	I-MISC
.	O

# sent_id = 119
# text = Second platoon was a platoon in the Rebel Alliance's army that was deployed during the Battle of Vrogas Vas.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 52184
Second	O
platoon	O
was	O
a	O
platoon	O
in	O
the	O
Rebel	B-ORG
Alliance	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
army	O
that	O
was	O
deployed	O
during	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Vrogas	B-LOC
Vas	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 120
# text = During the battle, the platoon came across the Sith Lord Darth Vader who destroyed some of their tanks.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 14291
During	O
the	O
battle	O
,	O
the	O
platoon	O
came	O
across	O
the	O
Sith	B-PER
Lord	I-PER
Darth	I-PER
Vader	I-PER
who	O
destroyed	O
some	O
of	O
their	O
tanks	O
.	O

# sent_id = 121
# text = Second platoon, also known as platoon two or as patrol two, was a platoon of BX-series droid commandos that were part of Sith Lord Darth Vader's and Chelli Lona Aphra's crew.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 23610
Second	O
platoon	O
,	O
also	O
known	O
as	O
platoon	O
two	O
or	O
as	O
patrol	O
two	O
,	O
was	O
a	O
platoon	O
of	O
BX-series	O
droid	O
commandos	O
that	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
Sith	B-PER
Lord	I-PER
Darth	I-PER
Vader	I-PER
'	O
s	O
and	O
Chelli	B-PER
Lona	I-PER
Aphra	I-PER
'	O
s	O
crew	O
.	O

# sent_id = 122
# text = Shortly after the Battle of Yavin, second platoon was involved in a skirmish in Cylo's research base.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 22481
Shortly	O
after	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Yavin	B-LOC
,	O
second	O
platoon	O
was	O
involved	O
in	O
a	O
skirmish	O
in	O
Cylo	B-PER
'	O
s	O
research	O
base	O
.	O

# sent_id = 123
# text = As part of the First Order's attempts to take over the Colossus platform, Kragan Gorr and his pirate gang launched a second raid on the platform, some time after their first attempt.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 28308
As	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
attempts	O
to	O
take	O
over	O
the	O
Colossus	O
platform	O
,	O
Kragan	B-PER
Gorr	I-PER
and	O
his	O
pirate	O
gang	O
launched	O
a	O
second	O
raid	O
on	O
the	O
platform	O
,	O
some	O
time	O
after	O
their	O
first	O
attempt	O
.	O

# sent_id = 124
# text = Due to the gang's spy, Synara San, informing Gorr that the Ace Squadron was off-platform and the targeting computer for the platform's defense turbolasers was down, Gorr and his gang were able to do much more damage than in their first attack.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 39463
Due	O
to	O
the	O
gang	O
'	O
s	O
spy	O
,	O
Synara	B-PER
San	I-PER
,	O
informing	O
Gorr	B-PER
that	O
the	O
Ace	O
Squadron	O
was	O
off-platform	O
and	O
the	O
targeting	O
computer	O
for	O
the	O
platform	O
'	O
s	O
defense	O
turbolasers	O
was	O
down	O
,	O
Gorr	B-PER
and	O
his	O
gang	O
were	O
able	O
to	O
do	O
much	O
more	O
damage	O
than	O
in	O
their	O
first	O
attack	O
.	O

# sent_id = 125
# text = Around 9 ABY, during the New Republic Era, the Mandalorian Din Djarin and his allies mounted a rescue of Grogu from a remnant of the fallen Galactic Empire led by Moff Gideon.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 37111
Around	O
9	O
ABY	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
New	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
Era	O
,	O
the	O
Mandalorian	B-PER
Din	I-PER
Djarin	I-PER
and	O
his	O
allies	O
mounted	O
a	O
rescue	O
of	O
Grogu	B-PER
from	O
a	O
remnant	O
of	O
the	O
fallen	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
led	O
by	O
Moff	B-PER
Gideon	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 126
# text = The Second Sister, formerly known as Trilla Suduri, was a Force-sensitive human female who served in the Inquisitorius during the reign of the Galactic Empire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 27143
The	O
Second	B-PER
Sister	I-PER
,	O
formerly	O
known	O
as	O
Trilla	B-PER
Suduri	I-PER
,	O
was	O
a	O
Force-sensitive	O
human	O
female	O
who	O
served	O
in	O
the	O
Inquisitorius	B-ORG
during	O
the	O
reign	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 127
# text = Trained in the Jedi arts, the Second Sister was an expert lightsaber duelist and one of the Empire's deadliest Jedi hunters.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 32675
Trained	O
in	O
the	O
Jedi	O
arts	O
,	O
the	O
Second	B-PER
Sister	I-PER
was	O
an	O
expert	O
lightsaber	O
duelist	O
and	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
Empire	B-ORG
'	O
s	O
deadliest	O
Jedi	O
hunters	O
.	O

# sent_id = 128
# text = However, Suduri's strongest asset was her brilliant intellect, being able to anticipate the behavior of her prey.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11799
However	O
,	O
Suduri	B-PER
'	O
s	O
strongest	O
asset	O
was	O
her	O
brilliant	O
intellect	O
,	O
being	O
able	O
to	O
anticipate	O
the	O
behavior	O
of	O
her	O
prey	O
.	O

# sent_id = 129
# text = A double-bladed spinning lightsaber was utilized by the Second Sister during her time as a member of the Inquisitorius.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 12987
A	O
double-bladed	O
spinning	O
lightsaber	O
was	O
utilized	O
by	O
the	O
Second	B-PER
Sister	I-PER
during	O
her	O
time	O
as	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Inquisitorius	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 130
# text = After Trilla Suduri was captured by the Galactic Empire and turned to the dark side of the Force, Suduri became known as the Second Sister and used the lightsaber as her primary weapon.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 27904
After	O
Trilla	B-PER
Suduri	I-PER
was	O
captured	O
by	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
and	O
turned	O
to	O
the	O
dark	O
side	O
of	O
the	O
Force	O
,	O
Suduri	B-PER
became	O
known	O
as	O
the	O
Second	B-PER
Sister	I-PER
and	O
used	O
the	O
lightsaber	O
as	O
her	O
primary	O
weapon	O
.	O

# sent_id = 131
# text = She used it to hunt down Padawan Cal Kestis during the Great Jedi Purge.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 12398
She	O
used	O
it	O
to	O
hunt	O
down	O
Padawan	O
Cal	B-PER
Kestis	I-PER
during	O
the	O
Great	O
Jedi	O
Purge	O
.	O

# sent_id = 132
# text = During their third duel on Bogano, Kestis disarmed Suduri, grabbed the lightsaber, and was forced to relive Suduri's capture and conscription into the Inquisitorius through his psychometry, allowing her to steal a Jedi holocron and escape.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 54107
During	O
their	O
third	O
duel	O
on	O
Bogano	B-LOC
,	O
Kestis	B-PER
disarmed	O
Suduri	B-PER
,	O
grabbed	O
the	O
lightsaber	O
,	O
and	O
was	O
forced	O
to	O
relive	O
Suduri	B-PER
'	O
s	O
capture	O
and	O
conscription	O
into	O
the	O
Inquisitorius	O
through	O
his	O
psychometry	O
,	O
allowing	O
her	O
to	O
steal	O
a	O
Jedi	O
holocron	O
and	O
escape	O
.	O

# sent_id = 133
# text = Kestis gave the saber to his master, Cere Junda, the Second Sister's former Master, who knighted him with it.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 17172
Kestis	B-PER
gave	O
the	O
saber	O
to	O
his	O
master	O
,	O
Cere	B-PER
Junda	I-PER
,	O
the	O
Second	B-PER
Sister	I-PER
'	O
s	O
former	O
Master	O
,	O
who	O
knighted	O
him	O
with	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 134
# text = Junda used the lightsaber as her primary weapon during the Mission to Nur.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 12002
Junda	B-PER
used	O
the	O
lightsaber	O
as	O
her	O
primary	O
weapon	O
during	O
the	O
Mission	O
to	O
Nur	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 135
# text = By the time Kestis faced the Second Sister in their fourth and final duel at Fortress Inquisitorius, she had replaced this lightsaber with a new one.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 29773
By	O
the	O
time	O
Kestis	B-PER
faced	O
the	O
Second	B-PER
Sister	I-PER
in	O
their	O
fourth	O
and	O
final	O
duel	O
at	O
Fortress	B-LOC
Inquisitorius	I-LOC
,	O
she	O
had	O
replaced	O
this	O
lightsaber	O
with	O
a	O
new	O
one	O
.	O

# sent_id = 136
# text = A skirmish in the Mesulan Remnants Belt occurred after Fyzen Gor's escape from Substation Grimdock.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31842
A	O
skirmish	O
in	O
the	O
Mesulan	B-LOC
Remnants	I-LOC
Belt	I-LOC
occurred	O
after	O
Fyzen	B-PER
Gor	I-PER
'	O
s	O
escape	O
from	O
Substation	B-LOC
Grimdock	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 137
# text = Attempting to prevent Gor from activating the Phylanx Redux Transmitter, Han Solo and Lando Calrissian's team tracked the transmitter to the Mesulan Remnants, but their starship, the Vermillion, was hijacked by Gor.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 95169
Attempting	O
to	O
prevent	O
Gor	B-PER
from	O
activating	O
the	O
Phylanx	B-MISC
Redux	I-MISC
Transmitter	I-MISC
,	O
Han	B-PER
Solo	I-PER
and	O
Lando	B-PER
Calrissian	I-PER
'	O
s	O
team	O
tracked	O
the	O
transmitter	O
to	O
the	O
Mesulan	B-LOC
Remnants	I-LOC
,	O
but	O
their	O
starship	O
,	O
the	O
Vermillion	B-MISC
,	O
was	O
hijacked	O
by	O
Gor	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 138
# text = Solo and Calrissian themselves later arrived in the Chevalier, having been visiting the asylum on Grava, finding the Remnants.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 17897
Solo	B-PER
and	O
Calrissian	B-PER
themselves	O
later	O
arrived	O
in	O
the	O
Chevalier	B-LOC
,	O
having	O
been	O
visiting	O
the	O
asylum	O
on	O
Grava	B-LOC
,	O
finding	O
the	O
Remnants	O
.	O

# sent_id = 139
# text = During the skirmish, the Elthree Assault Team, founded years earlier by L3-37, entered the skirmish against Gor's Original Dozen.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 23297
During	O
the	O
skirmish	O
,	O
the	O
Elthree	B-MISC
Assault	I-MISC
Team	I-MISC
,	O
founded	O
years	O
earlier	O
by	O
L3-37	B-PER
,	O
entered	O
the	O
skirmish	O
against	O
Gor	B-PER
'	O
s	O
Original	O
Dozen	O
.	O

# sent_id = 140
# text = Calrissian managed to destroy the transmitter, and Solo killed Gor with the Chevalier's laser cannons.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 21941
Calrissian	B-PER
managed	O
to	O
destroy	O
the	O
transmitter	O
,	O
and	O
Solo	B-PER
killed	O
Gor	B-PER
with	O
the	O
Chevalier	B-MISC
'	O
s	O
laser	O
cannons	O
.	O

# sent_id = 141
# text = Around 9 ABY, an attack on an Imperial base was led by Magistrate Greef Karga.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 13074
Around	O
9	O
ABY	O
,	O
an	O
attack	O
on	O
an	O
Imperial	O
base	O
was	O
led	O
by	O
Magistrate	B-PER
Greef	I-PER
Karga	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 142
# text = He and his companions Din Djarin, Carasynthia Dune, and a Mythrol infiltrated the installation and destroyed it, stealing a Trexler 906 Armored Marauder to escape in.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 39514
He	O
and	O
his	O
companions	O
Din	B-PER
Djarin	I-PER
,	O
Carasynthia	B-PER
Dune	I-PER
,	O
and	O
a	O
Mythrol	B-PER
infiltrated	O
the	O
installation	O
and	O
destroyed	O
it	O
,	O
stealing	O
a	O
Trexler	B-MISC
906	I-MISC
Armored	I-MISC
Marauder	I-MISC
to	O
escape	O
in	O
.	O

# sent_id = 143
# text = The confrontation effectively ended the Imperial presence on Nevarro.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11047
The	O
confrontation	O
effectively	O
ended	O
the	O
Imperial	O
presence	O
on	O
Nevarro	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 144
# text = Second Squadron Commander was a rank in the First Order Navy during the First Order/Resistance War.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31101
Second	O
Squadron	O
Commander	O
was	O
a	O
rank	O
in	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
Navy	I-ORG
during	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
/	O
Resistance	B-ORG
War	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 145
# text = Due to her role in defending the bridge of Commander Pyre's Resurgent-class Star Destroyer during the Escape from Aeos Prime, First Order TIE Fighter Pilot cadet Tamara Ryvora was promoted to the position of Second Squadron Commander.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 98900
Due	O
to	O
her	O
role	O
in	O
defending	O
the	O
bridge	O
of	O
Commander	O
Pyre	B-PER
'	O
s	O
Resurgent-class	O
Star	O
Destroyer	O
during	O
the	O
Escape	O
from	O
Aeos	B-LOC
Prime	I-LOC
,	O
First	O
Order	O
TIE	O
Fighter	O
Pilot	O
cadet	O
Tamara	B-PER
Ryvora	I-PER
was	O
promoted	O
to	O
the	O
position	O
of	O
Second	O
Squadron	O
Commander	O
.	O

# sent_id = 146
# text = Second weapons officer was a position within the starfleet of the Galactic Empire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 10136
Second	O
weapons	O
officer	O
was	O
a	O
position	O
within	O
the	O
starfleet	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 147
# text = Upon gaining the rank of junior lieutenant, Thrawn was assigned as the second weapons officer aboard the Gozanti-class cruiser Blood Crow.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 30599
Upon	O
gaining	O
the	O
rank	O
of	O
junior	O
lieutenant	O
,	O
Thrawn	B-PER
was	O
assigned	O
as	O
the	O
second	O
weapons	O
officer	O
aboard	O
the	O
Gozanti-class	O
cruiser	O
Blood	B-MISC
Crow	I-MISC
.	O

# sent_id = 148
# text = Long after the Galactic Civil War, a Whill talked to another Whill about recording the history of the galaxy.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 1082600
Long	O
after	O
the	O
Galactic	O
Civil	O
War	O
,	O
a	O
Whill	B-PER
talked	O
to	O
another	O
Whill	B-PER
about	O
recording	O
the	O
history	O
of	O
the	O
galaxy	O
.	O

# sent_id = 149
# text = Second-wave was a term used by the original settlers of the planet Jelucan to describe the settlers that arrived 350 years after the initial settlement of the planet.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 15842
Second-wave	O
was	O
a	O
term	O
used	O
by	O
the	O
original	O
settlers	O
of	O
the	O
planet	O
Jelucan	B-LOC
to	O
describe	O
the	O
settlers	O
that	O
arrived	O
350	O
years	O
after	O
the	O
initial	O
settlement	O
of	O
the	O
planet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 150
# text = Secondary sensor officer was a position within the starfleet of the Galactic Empire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 27355
Secondary	O
sensor	O
officer	O
was	O
a	O
position	O
within	O
the	O
starfleet	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 151
# text = He or she was subordinate to the chief sensor officer.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 5870
He	O
or	O
she	O
was	O
subordinate	O
to	O
the	O
chief	O
sensor	O
officer	O
.	O

# sent_id = 152
# text = Secret agents were operatives who belonged to the Noble Court-in-exile of the Anoat sector.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 34677
Secret	O
agents	O
were	O
operatives	O
who	O
belonged	O
to	O
the	O
Noble	O
Court-in	O
-	O
exile	O
of	O
the	O
Anoat	B-LOC
sector	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 153
# text = Although the Nobles frowned upon calling them assassins, those agents were trained to infiltrate Imperial bases, and they were just as deadly with a blaster than any gun-for-hire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 25214
Although	O
the	O
Nobles	O
frowned	O
upon	O
calling	O
them	O
assassins	O
,	O
those	O
agents	O
were	O
trained	O
to	O
infiltrate	O
Imperial	O
bases	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
were	O
just	O
as	O
deadly	O
with	O
a	O
blaster	O
than	O
any	O
gun-for	O
-	O
hire	O
.	O

# sent_id = 154
# text = The secret mission to Geonosis was carried out by the Sith Lord Darth Vader not long after the Battle of Yavin.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 18270
The	O
secret	O
mission	O
to	O
Geonosis	B-LOC
was	O
carried	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
Sith	B-PER
Lord	I-PER
Darth	I-PER
Vader	I-PER
not	O
long	O
after	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Yavin	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 155
# text = Having fallen out of favor with Emperor Palpatine, Vader had recruited the rogue archaeologist Doctor Chelli Aphra and the assassin droids BT-1 and 0-0-0 to assist him in building an army of unquestionably loyal battle droids.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 31305
Having	O
fallen	O
out	O
of	O
favor	O
with	O
Emperor	B-PER
Palpatine	I-PER
,	O
Vader	B-PER
had	O
recruited	O
the	O
rogue	O
archaeologist	O
Doctor	O
Chelli	B-PER
Aphra	I-PER
and	O
the	O
assassin	O
droids	O
BT-1	B-PER
and	O
0-0	B-PER
-	I-PER
0	I-PER
to	O
assist	O
him	O
in	O
building	O
an	O
army	O
of	O
unquestionably	O
loyal	O
battle	O
droids	O
.	O

# sent_id = 156
# text = Vader soon arrived on the planet Geonosis and his team infiltrated the lair of Karina, a Geonosian queen who had utilized a droid factory to produce battle droids as her children after she was injured and left unable to produce offspring during the sterilization of Geonosis.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 33213
Vader	B-PER
soon	O
arrived	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Geonosis	B-LOC
and	O
his	O
team	O
infiltrated	O
the	O
lair	O
of	O
Karina	B-PER
,	O
a	O
Geonosian	O
queen	O
who	O
had	O
utilized	O
a	O
droid	O
factory	O
to	O
produce	O
battle	O
droids	O
as	O
her	O
children	O
after	O
she	O
was	O
injured	O
and	O
left	O
unable	O
to	O
produce	O
offspring	O
during	O
the	O
sterilization	O
of	O
Geonosis	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 157
# text = While BT-1 fired on the queen's B1-series battle droids, Vader and Aphra severed the queen from her factory, and Aphra used her starship, the Ark Angel, to blow a large hole in the roof of the lair so that Vader's own starship could then extract both the factory and Vader's team with a large crane.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 40099
While	O
BT-1	B-MISC
fired	O
on	O
the	O
queen	O
'	O
s	O
B1-series	O
battle	O
droids	O
,	O
Vader	B-PER
and	O
Aphra	B-PER
severed	O
the	O
queen	O
from	O
her	O
factory	O
,	O
and	O
Aphra	B-PER
used	O
her	O
starship	O
,	O
the	O
Ark	B-MISC
Angel	I-MISC
,	O
to	O
blow	O
a	O
large	O
hole	O
in	O
the	O
roof	O
of	O
the	O
lair	O
so	O
that	O
Vader	B-PER
'	O
s	O
own	O
starship	O
could	O
then	O
extract	O
both	O
the	O
factory	O
and	O
Vader	B-PER
'	O
s	O
team	O
with	O
a	O
large	O
crane	O
.	O

# sent_id = 158
# text = The captured droid factory began producing BX-series droid commandos for Vader, which he used to assault the research base of a rival Imperial operative named Cylo.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 88462
The	O
captured	O
droid	O
factory	O
began	O
producing	O
BX-series	B-MISC
droid	O
commandos	O
for	O
Vader	B-PER
,	O
which	O
he	O
used	O
to	O
assault	O
the	O
research	O
base	O
of	O
a	O
rival	O
Imperial	O
operative	O
named	O
Cylo	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 159
# text = The secret mission to rebuild the Jedi Order was carried out during the Great Jedi Purge by former Jedi Knight Cere Junda and Padawan Cal Kestis.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 22442
The	O
secret	O
mission	O
to	O
rebuild	O
the	O
Jedi	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
was	O
carried	O
out	O
during	O
the	O
Great	O
Jedi	O
Purge	O
by	O
former	O
Jedi	O
Knight	O
Cere	B-PER
Junda	I-PER
and	O
Padawan	O
Cal	B-PER
Kestis	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 160
# text = It was their efforts to restore the destroyed Jedi Order that brought them into conflict with the Inquisitorius of the Galactic Empire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 16845
It	O
was	O
their	O
efforts	O
to	O
restore	O
the	O
destroyed	O
Jedi	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
that	O
brought	O
them	O
into	O
conflict	O
with	O
the	O
Inquisitorius	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 161
# text = The secret mission to Tatooine was an operation undertaken in 0 BBY by the Alliance to Restore the Republic during the Galactic Civil War.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 15287
The	O
secret	O
mission	O
to	O
Tatooine	B-LOC
was	O
an	O
operation	O
undertaken	O
in	O
0	O
BBY	O
by	O
the	O
Alliance	B-ORG
to	O
Restore	O
the	O
Republic	O
during	O
the	O
Galactic	O
Civil	O
War	O
.	O

# sent_id = 162
# text = The mission followed the Rebellion's theft of the plans to the Death Star, the Galactic Empire's planet-destroying deep space mobile battle station from the planet Scarif.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 138235
The	O
mission	O
followed	O
the	O
Rebellion	B-ORG
'	O
s	O
theft	O
of	O
the	O
plans	O
to	O
the	O
Death	B-LOC
Star	I-LOC
,	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
planet-destroying	O
deep	O
space	O
mobile	O
battle	O
station	O
from	O
the	O
planet	O
Scarif	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 163
# text = Rebel spies Jyn Erso and Cassian Andor transmitted the plans to Admiral Raddus aboard his flagship.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 22977
Rebel	O
spies	O
Jyn	B-PER
Erso	I-PER
and	O
Cassian	B-PER
Andor	I-PER
transmitted	O
the	O
plans	O
to	O
Admiral	O
Raddus	B-PER
aboard	O
his	O
flagship	O
.	O

# sent_id = 164
# text = As the battle concluded, the plans were nearly reclaimed by Darth Vader, but were successfully transferred to Princess Leia Organa of Alderaan aboard the Tantive IV.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 29411
As	O
the	O
battle	O
concluded	O
,	O
the	O
plans	O
were	O
nearly	O
reclaimed	O
by	O
Darth	B-PER
Vader	I-PER
,	O
but	O
were	O
successfully	O
transferred	O
to	O
Princess	O
Leia	B-PER
Organa	I-PER
of	O
Alderaan	B-LOC
aboard	O
the	O
Tantive	B-MISC
IV	I-MISC
.	O

# sent_id = 165
# text = The secret Phoenix Cell route was a secret hyperspace route created by the RA-7 protocol droid AP-5 when using both the Galactic Empire's databank and the data obtained by Phoenix Cell to reach Atollon.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 52554
The	O
secret	O
Phoenix	B-ORG
Cell	I-ORG
route	O
was	O
a	O
secret	O
hyperspace	O
route	O
created	O
by	O
the	O
RA-7	O
protocol	O
droid	O
AP-5	B-MISC
when	O
using	O
both	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
databank	O
and	O
the	O
data	O
obtained	O
by	O
Phoenix	B-ORG
Cell	I-ORG
to	O
reach	O
Atollon	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 166
# text = The hyperspace route became a closely guarded secret and the rebels established Chopper Base on Atollon's surface.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 103649
The	O
hyperspace	O
route	O
became	O
a	O
closely	O
guarded	O
secret	O
and	O
the	O
rebels	O
established	O
Chopper	B-MISC
Base	O
on	O
Atollon	B-LOC
'	O
s	O
surface	O
.	O

# sent_id = 167
# text = A secretary droid was a type of droid used to perform basic clerical work.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 9644
A	O
secretary	O
droid	O
was	O
a	O
type	O
of	O
droid	O
used	O
to	O
perform	O
basic	O
clerical	O
work	O
.	O

# sent_id = 168
# text = The CZ-series secretary/business communications droid was an example of this type of droid.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 4361
The	O
CZ-series	O
secretary	O
/	O
business	O
communications	O
droid	O
was	O
an	O
example	O
of	O
this	O
type	O
of	O
droid	O
.	O

# sent_id = 169
# text = One of the most notable secretary droid was CZ-1G5, a CZ unit who was located at Niima Outpost for over three hundred years and helped the Kubaz banker Rikard Lovas carry out a devilish plan to help him make money.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 30513
One	O
of	O
the	O
most	O
notable	O
secretary	O
droid	O
was	O
CZ-1G5	B-MISC
,	O
a	O
CZ	O
unit	O
who	O
was	O
located	O
at	O
Niima	B-LOC
Outpost	I-LOC
for	O
over	O
three	O
hundred	O
years	O
and	O
helped	O
the	O
Kubaz	O
banker	O
Rikard	B-PER
Lovas	I-PER
carry	O
out	O
a	O
devilish	O
plan	O
to	O
help	O
him	O
make	O
money	O
.	O

# sent_id = 170
# text = The Secretary of the Cabinet was an individual who led the Alliance Cabinet and its ministers, who were part of the civilian body of the Alliance to Restore the Republic, the Alliance Civil Government.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 126470
The	O
Secretary	O
of	O
the	O
Cabinet	O
was	O
an	O
individual	O
who	O
led	O
the	O
Alliance	B-ORG
Cabinet	I-ORG
and	O
its	O
ministers	O
,	O
who	O
were	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
civilian	O
body	O
of	O
the	O
Alliance	B-ORG
to	O
Restore	O
the	O
Republic	B-ORG
,	O
the	O
Alliance	B-ORG
Civil	I-ORG
Government	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 171
# text = Viceroy and former Senator Bail Organa served as Secretary of the Cabinet until his death in 0 BBY.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 17028
Viceroy	B-PER
and	O
former	O
Senator	O
Bail	B-PER
Organa	I-PER
served	O
as	O
Secretary	O
of	O
the	O
Cabinet	B-ORG
until	O
his	O
death	O
in	O
0	O
BBY	O
.	O

# sent_id = 172
# text = The Secretary of Transportation was the leader of the Republic Transport Bureau and was responsible for maintaining safe and reliable travel across the Galactic Republic and reported directly to the incumbent Supreme Chancellor.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 28358
The	O
Secretary	O
of	O
Transportation	O
was	O
the	O
leader	O
of	O
the	O
Republic	B-ORG
Transport	I-ORG
Bureau	I-ORG
and	O
was	O
responsible	O
for	O
maintaining	O
safe	O
and	O
reliable	O
travel	O
across	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
and	O
reported	O
directly	O
to	O
the	O
incumbent	O
Supreme	O
Chancellor	O
.	O

# sent_id = 173
# text = The position was held by a Muun male named Jeffo Lorillia in 232 BBY, who worked under Chancellor Lina Soh.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 478670
The	O
position	O
was	O
held	O
by	O
a	O
Muun	O
male	O
named	O
Jeffo	B-PER
Lorillia	I-PER
in	O
232	O
BBY	O
,	O
who	O
worked	O
under	O
Chancellor	O
Lina	B-PER
Soh	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 174
# text = Section A-five was a location on the space station Lansend Twenty-Six.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 33599
Section	B-LOC
A-five	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
on	O
the	O
space	O
station	O
Lansend	B-LOC
Twenty-Six	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 175
# text = Section A-four was a location on the space station Lansend Twenty-Six.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 16763
Section	B-LOC
A-four	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
on	O
the	O
space	O
station	O
Lansend	B-LOC
Twenty-Six	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 176
# text = Section B-eight was a location on the space station Lansend Twenty-Six, a facility the Galactic Empire used to hold slaves.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 16092
Section	B-LOC
B-eight	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
on	O
the	O
space	O
station	O
Lansend	B-LOC
Twenty-Six	I-LOC
,	O
a	O
facility	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
used	O
to	O
hold	O
slaves	O
.	O

# sent_id = 177
# text = Section B-five was a location on the space station Lansend Twenty-Six.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 107935
Section	B-LOC
B-five	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
on	O
the	O
space	O
station	O
Lansend	B-LOC
Twenty-Six	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 178
# text = Section C-6 was a location in Tipoca City Military Complex on the planet Kamino.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 15737
Section	B-LOC
C-6	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
in	O
Tipoca	B-LOC
City	I-LOC
Military	I-LOC
Complex	I-LOC
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Kamino	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 179
# text = Section IG44 was an area of the planet Coruscant.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 8191
Section	B-LOC
IG44	I-LOC
was	O
an	O
area	O
of	O
the	O
planet	O
Coruscant	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 180
# text = Coruscant Guard riot troopers believed Duchess Satine Kryze fled toward that section after the police identified her as a suspect in the murder of Davu Golec.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 28977
Coruscant	B-ORG
Guard	I-ORG
riot	O
troopers	O
believed	O
Duchess	O
Satine	B-PER
Kryze	I-PER
fled	O
toward	O
that	O
section	O
after	O
the	O
police	O
identified	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
suspect	O
in	O
the	O
murder	O
of	O
Davu	B-PER
Golec	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 181
# text = A sector was an area of space or land framed by an artificial, conventional boundary.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11037
A	O
sector	O
was	O
an	O
area	O
of	O
space	O
or	O
land	O
framed	O
by	O
an	O
artificial	O
,	O
conventional	O
boundary	O
.	O

# sent_id = 182
# text = Sector 11 was a location within the city of Sundari on the planet Mandalore.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 13875
Sector	B-LOC
11	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
within	O
the	O
city	O
of	O
Sundari	B-LOC
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Mandalore	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 183
# text = Some time into the Galactic Republic's siege against the forces of Maul, the assistance of the Republic clone troopers was able to keep most of the city under control, though fighting still occurred within sector 11.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 46002
Some	O
time	O
into	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
siege	O
against	O
the	O
forces	O
of	O
Maul	B-PER
,	O
the	O
assistance	O
of	O
the	O
Republic	O
clone	O
troopers	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
keep	O
most	O
of	O
the	O
city	O
under	O
control	O
,	O
though	O
fighting	O
still	O
occurred	O
within	O
sector	B-LOC
11	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 184
# text = Sector 11 was the designation for an area on the planet Rugosa.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 26883
Sector	B-LOC
11	I-LOC
was	O
the	O
designation	O
for	O
an	O
area	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Rugosa	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 185
# text = When a group of battle droids were searching for Jedi Master Yoda during the Ambush on Rugosa in 22 BBY, a OOM command battle droid noticed the Jedi in sector 11 and ordered his troops to fire at the area.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 34234
When	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
battle	O
droids	O
were	O
searching	O
for	O
Jedi	B-PER
Master	I-PER
Yoda	I-PER
during	O
the	O
Ambush	O
on	O
Rugosa	B-LOC
in	O
22	O
BBY	O
,	O
a	O
OOM	O
command	O
battle	O
droid	O
noticed	O
the	O
Jedi	O
in	O
sector	B-LOC
11	I-LOC
and	O
ordered	O
his	O
troops	O
to	O
fire	O
at	O
the	O
area	O
.	O

# sent_id = 186
# text = Sector 11374265 was the designation of an area of the planet Teth, outside the B'omarr Order Monastery.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 63942
Sector	B-LOC
11374265	I-LOC
was	O
the	O
designation	O
of	O
an	O
area	O
of	O
the	O
planet	O
Teth	B-LOC
,	O
outside	O
the	O
B	B-ORG
'	I-ORG
omarr	I-ORG
Order	I-ORG
Monastery	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 187
# text = During the Battle of Teth, when Galactic Republic forces approached the Confederacy of Independent Systems–controlled monastery, an OOM command battle droid ordered a B1 battle droid sergeant to fire on Sector 11374265.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 133127
During	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Teth	B-LOC
,	O
when	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
forces	O
approached	O
the	O
Confederacy	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Independent	I-ORG
Systems	I-ORG
–	O
controlled	O
monastery	O
,	O
an	O
OOM	O
command	O
battle	O
droid	O
ordered	O
a	O
B1	O
battle	O
droid	O
sergeant	O
to	O
fire	O
on	O
Sector	B-LOC
11374265	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 188
# text = The sergeant was unsure where his commanding officer had ordered him to fire, leading the irate OOM command battle droid to point out the location.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 7975
The	O
sergeant	O
was	O
unsure	O
where	O
his	O
commanding	O
officer	O
had	O
ordered	O
him	O
to	O
fire	O
,	O
leading	O
the	O
irate	O
OOM	O
command	O
battle	O
droid	O
to	O
point	O
out	O
the	O
location	O
.	O

# sent_id = 189
# text = Sector 3263827 was a location that received refuse from Black Spire Outpost, a remote settlement on the planet Batuu in the Outer Rim Territories.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 82400
Sector	B-LOC
3263827	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
that	O
received	O
refuse	O
from	O
Black	B-LOC
Spire	I-LOC
Outpost	I-LOC
,	O
a	O
remote	O
settlement	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Batuu	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
Outer	B-LOC
Rim	I-LOC
Territories	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 190
# text = Garbage receptacles in the outpost were stamped with orders, written in Aurebesh, to transport trash to the sector.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 9631
Garbage	O
receptacles	O
in	O
the	O
outpost	O
were	O
stamped	O
with	O
orders	O
,	O
written	O
in	O
Aurebesh	O
,	O
to	O
transport	O
trash	O
to	O
the	O
sector	O
.	O

# sent_id = 191
# text = B-881 was a subsector located in the Lothal sector of the galaxy's Outer Rim Territories.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 137541
B-881	B-LOC
was	O
a	O
subsector	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	I-LOC
of	O
the	O
galaxy	O
'	O
s	O
Outer	B-LOC
Rim	I-LOC
Territories	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 192
# text = During the age of the Galactic Empire, the Lothal sector, including Sector 33.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 25055
During	O
the	O
age	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	I-LOC
,	O
including	O
Sector	B-LOC
33	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 193
# text = B-881, was ruled by the Empire and governed by Arihnda Pryce, a human female, a Lothal native, as well as Moff Stattata.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 29336
B-881	B-LOC
,	O
was	O
ruled	O
by	O
the	O
Empire	B-ORG
and	O
governed	O
by	O
Arihnda	B-PER
Pryce	I-PER
,	O
a	O
human	O
female	O
,	O
a	O
Lothal	O
native	O
,	O
as	O
well	O
as	O
Moff	B-PER
Stattata	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 194
# text = Sector 33G. 925 was a subsector located in the Lothal sector of the galaxy's Outer Rim Territories.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 40392
Sector	B-LOC
33G	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
925	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
subsector	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	I-LOC
of	O
the	O
galaxy	O
'	O
s	O
Outer	B-LOC
Rim	I-LOC
Territories	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 195
# text = During the rule of the Galactic Empire, the Lothal sector and its subsectors, including Sector 33G. 925, was ruled by the Empire and controlled by Governor Arihnda Pryce, a human female from the planet Lothal, and Moff Stattata.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 44651
During	O
the	O
rule	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	I-LOC
and	O
its	O
subsectors	O
,	O
including	O
Sector	B-LOC
33G	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
925	I-LOC
,	O
was	O
ruled	O
by	O
the	O
Empire	B-ORG
and	O
controlled	O
by	O
Governor	O
Arihnda	B-PER
Pryce	I-PER
,	O
a	O
human	O
female	O
from	O
the	O
planet	O
Lothal	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
Moff	B-PER
Stattata	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 196
# text = Sector 47 was an area of space above the Forest Moon of Endor.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 99731
Sector	B-LOC
47	I-LOC
was	O
an	O
area	O
of	O
space	O
above	O
the	O
Forest	O
Moon	O
of	O
Endor	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 197
# text = During the Battle of Endor in the Galactic Civil War, the Galactic Empire's Star Destroyers were located in Sector 47 and ambushed the Alliance Fleet.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 80104
During	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Endor	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
Galactic	O
Civil	O
War	O
,	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
Star	O
Destroyers	O
were	O
located	O
in	O
Sector	B-LOC
47	I-LOC
and	O
ambushed	O
the	O
Alliance	O
Fleet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 198
# text = A Rebel Alliance Mon Calamari controller informed Admiral Gial Ackbar about the location of the Imperial vessels.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 459191
A	O
Rebel	O
Alliance	O
Mon	O
Calamari	O
controller	O
informed	O
Admiral	O
Gial	B-PER
Ackbar	I-PER
about	O
the	O
location	O
of	O
the	O
Imperial	O
vessels	O
.	O

# sent_id = 199
# text = Sector 5-1-5 was a sector in Capital City on the planet Lothal.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11474
Sector	B-LOC
5-1	I-LOC
-	I-LOC
5	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
sector	O
in	O
Capital	O
City	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Lothal	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 200
# text = Sector 5-1-5 was a sector on the desert planet of Geonosis.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 12861
Sector	B-LOC
5-1	I-LOC
-	I-LOC
5	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
sector	O
on	O
the	O
desert	O
planet	O
of	O
Geonosis	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 201
# text = During the First Battle of Geonosis, after Jedi Grand Master Yoda ordered all fire be focused on the nearest starship, a Clone Captain in the forward command center ordered all quadrants to the sector, allowing for the Republic's Self-Propelled Heavy Artillery Turbolasers to take down a core ship.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 36838
During	O
the	O
First	O
Battle	O
of	O
Geonosis	B-LOC
,	O
after	O
Jedi	B-PER
Grand	I-PER
Master	I-PER
Yoda	I-PER
ordered	O
all	O
fire	O
be	O
focused	O
on	O
the	O
nearest	O
starship	O
,	O
a	O
Clone	O
Captain	O
in	O
the	O
forward	O
command	O
center	O
ordered	O
all	O
quadrants	O
to	O
the	O
sector	O
,	O
allowing	O
for	O
the	O
Republic	O
'	O
s	O
Self-Propelled	O
Heavy	O
Artillery	O
Turbolasers	O
to	O
take	O
down	O
a	O
core	O
ship	O
.	O

# sent_id = 202
# text = After the ship fell to the battlefield below, the battle continued and was ultimately won by the Republic.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11190
After	O
the	O
ship	O
fell	O
to	O
the	O
battlefield	O
below	O
,	O
the	O
battle	O
continued	O
and	O
was	O
ultimately	O
won	O
by	O
the	O
Republic	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 203
# text = X48 was a subsector located in the Lothal sector of the galaxy's Outer Rim Territories.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 18402
X48	B-LOC
was	O
a	O
subsector	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	O
of	O
the	O
galaxy	O
'	O
s	O
Outer	B-LOC
Rim	I-LOC
Territories	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 204
# text = Following the establishment of the Galactic Empire, the Lothal sector and its subsectors, including Sector 6472.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 23175
Following	O
the	O
establishment	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	O
and	O
its	O
subsectors	O
,	O
including	O
Sector	B-LOC
6472	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 205
# text = X48, was ruled by the Empire and controlled by Governor Arihnda Pryce, a human female, from the planet Lothal, and Moff Stattata.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 37009
X48	B-LOC
,	O
was	O
ruled	O
by	O
the	O
Empire	B-ORG
and	O
controlled	O
by	O
Governor	O
Arihnda	B-PER
Pryce	I-PER
,	O
a	O
human	O
female	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
planet	O
Lothal	B-LOC
,	O
and	O
Moff	B-PER
Stattata	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 206
# text = Sector 7-E was a location on the Colossus the station's residents were prohibited from entering.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 23566
Sector	B-LOC
7-E	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
location	O
on	O
the	O
Colossus	B-LOC
the	O
station	O
'	O
s	O
residents	O
were	O
prohibited	O
from	O
entering	O
.	O

# sent_id = 207
# text = Kazuda Xiono and BB-8 encountered several pirates in sector 7-E, and managed to prevent them from stealing several crates of blasters.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 76175
Kazuda	B-PER
Xiono	I-PER
and	O
BB-8	B-MISC
encountered	O
several	O
pirates	O
in	O
sector	B-LOC
7-E	I-LOC
,	O
and	O
managed	O
to	O
prevent	O
them	O
from	O
stealing	O
several	O
crates	O
of	O
blasters	O
.	O

# sent_id = 208
# text = Sector 7732. 00122 was a subsector located in the Lothal sector of the galaxy's Outer Rim Territories.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 30977
Sector	B-LOC
7732	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
00122	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
subsector	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	O
of	O
the	O
galaxy	O
'	O
s	O
Outer	B-LOC
Rim	I-LOC
Territories	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 209
# text = During the rule of the Galactic Empire, the Lothal sector and its subsectors, including Sector 7732. 00122, was ruled by the Empire and controlled by Moff Stattata and Governor Arihnda Pryce, a human female, from the planet Lothal.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 37512
During	O
the	O
rule	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	I-LOC
and	O
its	O
subsectors	O
,	O
including	O
Sector	B-LOC
7732	I-LOC
.	I-LOC
00122	I-LOC
,	O
was	O
ruled	O
by	O
the	O
Empire	B-ORG
and	O
controlled	O
by	O
Moff	B-PER
Stattata	I-PER
and	O
Governor	O
Arihnda	B-PER
Pryce	I-PER
,	O
a	O
human	O
female	O
,	O
from	O
the	O
planet	O
Lothal	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 210
# text = 2J99 was a subsector located in the Lothal sector of the galaxy's Outer Rim Territories.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 19170
2J99	B-LOC
was	O
a	O
subsector	O
located	O
in	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	O
of	O
the	O
galaxy	O
'	O
s	O
Outer	B-LOC
Rim	I-LOC
Territories	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 211
# text = During the rule of the Galactic Empire, the Lothal sector and its subsectors, including Sector 885.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 108467
During	O
the	O
rule	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
,	O
the	O
Lothal	B-LOC
sector	O
and	O
its	O
subsectors	O
,	O
including	O
Sector	B-LOC
885	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 212
# text = 2J99, were ruled by the Empire and controlled by Moff Stattata and Governor Arihnda Pryce, a human female from the planet Lothal.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 62294
2J99	B-LOC
,	O
were	O
ruled	O
by	O
the	O
Empire	B-ORG
and	O
controlled	O
by	O
Moff	B-PER
Stattata	I-PER
and	O
Governor	B-PER
Arihnda	I-PER
Pryce	I-PER
,	O
a	O
human	O
female	O
from	O
the	O
planet	O
Lothal	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 213
# text = RMS droids were a type of droid that had cylindrical bodies with two legs at the bottom and a domed top.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 7577
RMS	O
droids	O
were	O
a	O
type	O
of	O
droid	O
that	O
had	O
cylindrical	O
bodies	O
with	O
two	O
legs	O
at	O
the	O
bottom	O
and	O
a	O
domed	O
top	O
.	O

# sent_id = 214
# text = A tube ran from the top of the droid down one side of its body, and an antenna protruded from the top of the droid on the same side as the tube.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 68791
A	O
tube	O
ran	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
droid	O
down	O
one	O
side	O
of	O
its	O
body	O
,	O
and	O
an	O
antenna	O
protruded	O
from	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
droid	O
on	O
the	O
same	O
side	O
as	O
the	O
tube	O
.	O

# sent_id = 215
# text = RMS droids could have gray plating with a single band of red near the top of the droids body.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 8491
RMS	B-MISC
droids	O
could	O
have	O
gray	O
plating	O
with	O
a	O
single	O
band	O
of	O
red	O
near	O
the	O
top	O
of	O
the	O
droids	O
body	O
.	O

# sent_id = 216
# text = RN-18 was an Imperial mining droid who was stolen by the pirate Fortombro and reprogrammed with numerous combat protocols.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 14660
RN-18	B-MISC
was	O
an	O
Imperial	O
mining	O
droid	O
who	O
was	O
stolen	O
by	O
the	O
pirate	O
Fortombro	B-PER
and	O
reprogrammed	O
with	O
numerous	O
combat	O
protocols	O
.	O

# sent_id = 217
# text = During the Galactic Empire's Iron Blockade of the Anoat sector following the Imperial defeat at the Battle of Endor, Fortombro rented RN-18 to various customers, including a young smuggler, who sent the droid on various missions.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 83278
During	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
Iron	O
Blockade	O
of	O
the	O
Anoat	B-LOC
sector	I-LOC
following	O
the	O
Imperial	O
defeat	O
at	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Endor	B-LOC
,	O
Fortombro	B-PER
rented	O
RN-18	B-MISC
to	O
various	O
customers	O
,	O
including	O
a	O
young	O
smuggler	O
,	O
who	O
sent	O
the	O
droid	O
on	O
various	O
missions	O
.	O

# sent_id = 218
# text = Ro was an officer in the starfleet of the Galactic Empire who fought in the Galactic Civil War.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 13398
Ro	B-PER
was	O
an	O
officer	O
in	O
the	O
starfleet	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Empire	I-ORG
who	O
fought	O
in	O
the	O
Galactic	O
Civil	O
War	O
.	O

# sent_id = 219
# text = By the time of the First Order, Ro's prowesses had passed into history, and the commemorative armbands worn by sergeants of the First Order's military bore the officer's name in Aurebesh.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 23214
By	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
,	O
Ro	B-PER
'	O
s	O
prowesses	O
had	O
passed	O
into	O
history	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
commemorative	O
armbands	O
worn	O
by	O
sergeants	O
of	O
the	O
First	B-ORG
Order	I-ORG
'	O
s	O
military	O
bore	O
the	O
officer	O
'	O
s	O
name	O
in	O
Aurebesh	O
.	O

# sent_id = 220
# text = General Hux's monitor wore a uniform with the officer's name on it, designating her as a sergeant.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 22701
General	O
Hux	B-PER
'	O
s	O
monitor	O
wore	O
a	O
uniform	O
with	O
the	O
officer	O
'	O
s	O
name	O
on	O
it	O
,	O
designating	O
her	O
as	O
a	O
sergeant	O
.	O

# sent_id = 221
# text = The Ro family was a family of a humanoid species, members of which included the Eyes of the Nihil Asgar Ro and his son Marchion Ro.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 26618
The	O
Ro	B-PER
family	O
was	O
a	O
family	O
of	O
a	O
humanoid	O
species	O
,	O
members	O
of	O
which	O
included	O
the	O
Eyes	O
of	O
the	O
Nihil	B-PER
Asgar	I-PER
Ro	I-PER
and	O
his	O
son	O
Marchion	B-PER
Ro	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 222
# text = Hailing from a homeworld, the family had a history entwined with the Jedi and a mysterious artifact, both of which Marchion believed to be connected to bad things which had befallen his ancestors.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 16680
Hailing	O
from	O
a	O
homeworld	O
,	O
the	O
family	O
had	O
a	O
history	O
entwined	O
with	O
the	O
Jedi	O
and	O
a	O
mysterious	O
artifact	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
which	O
Marchion	B-PER
believed	O
to	O
be	O
connected	O
to	O
bad	O
things	O
which	O
had	O
befallen	O
his	O
ancestors	O
.	O

# sent_id = 223
# text = Several generations of the family had also held the hyperspace prospector Mari San Tekka prisoner to utilize her ability to discover the Paths, difficult-to-traverse hyperspace routes.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 56162
Several	O
generations	O
of	O
the	O
family	O
had	O
also	O
held	O
the	O
hyperspace	O
prospector	O
Mari	B-PER
San	I-PER
Tekka	I-PER
prisoner	O
to	O
utilize	O
her	O
ability	O
to	O
discover	O
the	O
Paths	O
,	O
difficult-to	O
-	O
traverse	O
hyperspace	O
routes	O
.	O

# sent_id = 224
# text = Asgar and Marchion Ro hailed from a homeworld which they abandoned long before the Great Disaster, eventually joining the Nihil pirates.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 71603
Asgar	B-PER
and	O
Marchion	B-PER
Ro	I-PER
hailed	O
from	O
a	O
homeworld	O
which	O
they	O
abandoned	O
long	O
before	O
the	O
Great	O
Disaster	O
,	O
eventually	O
joining	O
the	O
Nihil	B-ORG
pirates	O
.	O

# sent_id = 225
# text = After leaving his homeworld, the closest thing Marchion had to a home was his flagship, the Gaze Electric.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 18297
After	O
leaving	O
his	O
homeworld	O
,	O
the	O
closest	O
thing	O
Marchion	B-PER
had	O
to	O
a	O
home	O
was	O
his	O
flagship	O
,	O
the	O
Gaze	B-MISC
Electric	I-MISC
.	O

# sent_id = 226
# text = The ro hypa was a serpentine creature native to the desert planet Mataou in the Anoat sector.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 50554
The	O
ro	O
hypa	O
was	O
a	O
serpentine	O
creature	O
native	O
to	O
the	O
desert	O
planet	O
Mataou	B-LOC
in	O
the	O
Anoat	B-LOC
sector	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 227
# text = They were red and purple in appearance and were highly venomous, capable of spewing potent poison at their prey.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 5401
They	O
were	O
red	O
and	O
purple	O
in	O
appearance	O
and	O
were	O
highly	O
venomous	O
,	O
capable	O
of	O
spewing	O
potent	O
poison	O
at	O
their	O
prey	O
.	O

# sent_id = 228
# text = Ro Thran was a Gran male who worked as a hunter for hire.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 8486
Ro	B-PER
Thran	I-PER
was	O
a	O
Gran	O
male	O
who	O
worked	O
as	O
a	O
hunter	O
for	O
hire	O
.	O

# sent_id = 229
# text = At one point, he captured a bull krykna for the Tyn Syndicate.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 11149
At	O
one	O
point	O
,	O
he	O
captured	O
a	O
bull	O
krykna	O
for	O
the	O
Tyn	B-ORG
Syndicate	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 230
# text = He was later one of several hunters hired by the archeologist Doctor Chelli Aphra, who had been swallowed alive by the Shadowfang Beast guarding a temple on the world of X3-299-11.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 95473
He	O
was	O
later	O
one	O
of	O
several	O
hunters	O
hired	O
by	O
the	O
archeologist	O
Doctor	O
Chelli	B-PER
Aphra	I-PER
,	O
who	O
had	O
been	O
swallowed	O
alive	O
by	O
the	O
Shadowfang	O
Beast	O
guarding	O
a	O
temple	O
on	O
the	O
world	O
of	O
X3-299	B-LOC
-	I-LOC
11	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 231
# text = Aphra wanted a hunter to subdue the beast then kill it so she could escape its stomach; however, Thran was killed when he activated one of the temple's traps that launched several spears into the Gran and pinned him to a wall.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 63759
Aphra	B-PER
wanted	O
a	O
hunter	O
to	O
subdue	O
the	O
beast	O
then	O
kill	O
it	O
so	O
she	O
could	O
escape	O
its	O
stomach	O
;	O
however	O
,	O
Thran	B-PER
was	O
killed	O
when	O
he	O
activated	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
temple	O
'	O
s	O
traps	O
that	O
launched	O
several	O
spears	O
into	O
the	O
Gran	B-PER
and	O
pinned	O
him	O
to	O
a	O
wall	O
.	O

# sent_id = 232
# text = The hunters Nokk and Winloss later discovered Thran's body, but Aphra claimed he must have been hired by someone else to capture the beast.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 34133
The	O
hunters	O
Nokk	B-PER
and	O
Winloss	B-PER
later	O
discovered	O
Thran	B-PER
'	O
s	O
body	O
,	O
but	O
Aphra	B-PER
claimed	O
he	O
must	O
have	O
been	O
hired	O
by	O
someone	O
else	O
to	O
capture	O
the	O
beast	O
.	O

# sent_id = 233
# text = Thran had black eyes and pink skin.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 6043
Thran	B-PER
had	O
black	O
eyes	O
and	O
pink	O
skin	O
.	O

# sent_id = 234
# text = He wore red armor over a black shirt and blue pants at the time of his death.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 5634
He	O
wore	O
red	O
armor	O
over	O
a	O
black	O
shirt	O
and	O
blue	O
pants	O
at	O
the	O
time	O
of	O
his	O
death	O
.	O

# sent_id = 235
# text = The Ro-Loo Triangle was a nebula that portions of the Imperial fleet hid away in after the Battle of Endor.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 70451
The	O
Ro-Loo	B-LOC
Triangle	I-LOC
was	O
a	O
nebula	O
that	O
portions	O
of	O
the	O
Imperial	O
fleet	O
hid	O
away	O
in	O
after	O
the	O
Battle	O
of	O
Endor	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 236
# text = The fleet there was not as big as the one residing in the Vulpinus Nebula, however there were still hundreds of Star Destroyers and thousands of smaller craft.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 41206
The	O
fleet	O
there	O
was	O
not	O
as	O
big	O
as	O
the	O
one	O
residing	O
in	O
the	O
Vulpinus	B-LOC
Nebula	I-LOC
,	O
however	O
there	O
were	O
still	O
hundreds	O
of	O
Star	O
Destroyers	O
and	O
thousands	O
of	O
smaller	O
craft	O
.	O

# sent_id = 237
# text = Ro-roos were creatures that existed in the galaxy.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 9116
Ro-roos	O
were	O
creatures	O
that	O
existed	O
in	O
the	O
galaxy	O
.	O

# sent_id = 238
# text = The RO-series childcare and nanny droid was a model of nanny droid manufactured by a partnership of GoCorp and Utilitech.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 15562
The	O
RO-series	B-MISC
childcare	O
and	O
nanny	O
droid	O
was	O
a	O
model	O
of	O
nanny	O
droid	O
manufactured	O
by	O
a	O
partnership	O
of	O
GoCorp	B-ORG
and	O
Utilitech	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 239
# text = The uni-wheel drive and chassis of the WA-7 waitress droid served as the basis for the model, which was equipped with soft glowing eyes, a soothing voice and many padded limbs to aid in caring for their infant charges.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 78428
The	O
uni-wheel	O
drive	O
and	O
chassis	O
of	O
the	O
WA-7	B-MISC
waitress	O
droid	O
served	O
as	O
the	O
basis	O
for	O
the	O
model	O
,	O
which	O
was	O
equipped	O
with	O
soft	O
glowing	O
eyes	O
,	O
a	O
soothing	O
voice	O
and	O
many	O
padded	O
limbs	O
to	O
aid	O
in	O
caring	O
for	O
their	O
infant	O
charges	O
.	O

# sent_id = 240
# text = The droids were equipped with a database detailing the species of the child in their care and could perform minor medical operations in emergencies while also contacting the authorities.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 7202
The	O
droids	O
were	O
equipped	O
with	O
a	O
database	O
detailing	O
the	O
species	O
of	O
the	O
child	O
in	O
their	O
care	O
and	O
could	O
perform	O
minor	O
medical	O
operations	O
in	O
emergencies	O
while	O
also	O
contacting	O
the	O
authorities	O
.	O

# sent_id = 241
# text = The Ro-ti-Mundi was a Venator-class Star Destroyer of the Open Circle Fleet, a major space fleet of the Republic Navy during the Clone Wars.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 53061
The	O
Ro-ti	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
Mundi	I-MISC
was	O
a	O
Venator-class	O
Star	O
Destroyer	O
of	O
the	O
Open	O
Circle	O
Fleet	O
,	O
a	O
major	O
space	O
fleet	O
of	O
the	O
Republic	B-ORG
Navy	I-ORG
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
.	O

# sent_id = 242
# text = The Star Destroyer was notably involved in the defense of Coruscant, capital of the Galactic Republic, against the naval forces of the Confederacy of Independent Systems.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 74370
The	O
Star	O
Destroyer	O
was	O
notably	O
involved	O
in	O
the	O
defense	O
of	O
Coruscant	B-LOC
,	O
capital	O
of	O
the	O
Galactic	B-ORG
Republic	I-ORG
,	O
against	O
the	O
naval	O
forces	O
of	O
the	O
Confederacy	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Independent	I-ORG
Systems	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 243
# text = During the battle, the Ro-ti-Mundi served as a carrier for Clone Flight Squad Seven—a starfighter squadron led by Clone Commander CC-2237.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 30754
During	O
the	O
battle	O
,	O
the	O
Ro-ti	B-MISC
-	I-MISC
Mundi	I-MISC
served	O
as	O
a	O
carrier	O
for	O
Clone	O
Flight	O
Squad	O
Seven	O
—	O
a	O
starfighter	O
squadron	O
led	O
by	O
Clone	O
Commander	B-PER
CC-2237	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 244
# text = RO-Z67 was a heavily modified RO-series childcare and nanny droid employed by Darth Sidious, Dark Lord of the Sith, during the Clone Wars.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 22577
RO-Z67	B-MISC
was	O
a	O
heavily	O
modified	O
RO-series	B-MISC
childcare	O
and	O
nanny	O
droid	O
employed	O
by	O
Darth	B-PER
Sidious	I-PER
,	O
Dark	O
Lord	O
of	O
the	O
Sith	O
,	O
during	O
the	O
Clone	O
Wars	O
.	O

# sent_id = 245
# text = Stationed at a secret facility on the planet Mustafar, RO-Z67 worked with several Force-sensitive children that were kidnapped by the bounty hunter Cad Bane on behalf of Sidious.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 22549
Stationed	O
at	O
a	O
secret	O
facility	O
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Mustafar	B-LOC
,	O
RO-Z67	B-MISC
worked	O
with	O
several	O
Force-sensitive	O
children	O
that	O
were	O
kidnapped	O
by	O
the	O
bounty	O
hunter	O
Cad	B-PER
Bane	I-PER
on	O
behalf	O
of	O
Sidious	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 246
# text = Sidious planned to train the children to become dark side spies, but RO-Z67 was destroyed when Jedi Knight Anakin Skywalker and his Padawan apprentice Ahsoka Tano rescued the children.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 25517
Sidious	B-PER
planned	O
to	O
train	O
the	O
children	O
to	O
become	O
dark	O
side	O
spies	O
,	O
but	O
RO-Z67	B-MISC
was	O
destroyed	O
when	O
Jedi	O
Knight	O
Anakin	B-PER
Skywalker	I-PER
and	O
his	O
Padawan	O
apprentice	O
Ahsoka	B-PER
Tano	I-PER
rescued	O
the	O
children	O
.	O

# sent_id = 247
# text = Roach was a human female and a member of the Alliance to Restore the Republic's 61st Mobile Infantry, better known as Twilight Company.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 33892
Roach	B-PER
was	O
a	O
human	O
female	O
and	O
a	O
member	O
of	O
the	O
Alliance	B-ORG
to	O
Restore	O
the	O
Republic	O
'	O
s	O
61st	O
Mobile	O
Infantry	O
,	O
better	O
known	O
as	O
Twilight	O
Company	O
.	O

# sent_id = 248
# text = She was recruited by First Sergeant Hazram Namir and Quartermaster Hober on her home planet of Haidoral Prime in 3 ABY.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 18699
She	O
was	O
recruited	O
by	O
First	O
Sergeant	O
Hazram	B-PER
Namir	I-PER
and	O
Quartermaster	O
Hober	B-PER
on	O
her	O
home	O
planet	O
of	O
Haidoral	B-LOC
Prime	I-LOC
in	O
3	O
ABY	O
.	O

# sent_id = 249
# text = Namir took a liking to her when she became part of the company and also was able to determine that Roach was a recovering spice addict.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 41993
Namir	B-PER
took	O
a	O
liking	O
to	O
her	O
when	O
she	O
became	O
part	O
of	O
the	O
company	O
and	O
also	O
was	O
able	O
to	O
determine	O
that	O
Roach	B-PER
was	O
a	O
recovering	O
spice	O
addict	O
.	O

# sent_id = 250
# text = She was ultimately killed during the Siege of Inyusu Tor on the planet Sullust.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 14679
She	O
was	O
ultimately	O
killed	O
during	O
the	O
Siege	O
of	O
Inyusu	B-LOC
Tor	I-LOC
on	O
the	O
planet	O
Sullust	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 251
# text = A roach-rat was a type of rat.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 5317
A	O
roach-rat	O
was	O
a	O
type	O
of	O
rat	O
.	O

# sent_id = 252
# text = They were known to hide and scuttle around in darkness.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 4527
They	O
were	O
known	O
to	O
hide	O
and	O
scuttle	O
around	O
in	O
darkness	O
.	O

# sent_id = 253
# text = Roachrats were a type of creature that scattered when they were exposed to sunlight.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 4312
Roachrats	O
were	O
a	O
type	O
of	O
creature	O
that	O
scattered	O
when	O
they	O
were	O
exposed	O
to	O
sunlight	O
.	O

# sent_id = 254
# text = The Roamer-6 breath mask was a model of breath mask produced by Gandorthral Atmospherics.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 15320
The	O
Roamer-6	B-MISC
breath	O
mask	O
was	O
a	O
model	O
of	O
breath	O
mask	O
produced	O
by	O
Gandorthral	O
Atmospherics	O
.	O

# sent_id = 255
# text = Roast nuna was a cooked meal made of roast nuna meat.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 25528
Roast	O
nuna	O
was	O
a	O
cooked	O
meal	O
made	O
of	O
roast	O
nuna	O
meat	O
.	O

# sent_id = 256
# text = It could be found in a bar.
# status = {"0":"accepted"}
# time (ms) = 14168
It	O
could	O
be	O
found	O
in	O
a	O
bar	O
.	O
