-DOCSTART- -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
4XB -X- -X- B-MISC
programming -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
programming -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

One -X- -X- O
4XB -X- -X- B-MISC
programming -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
DA1-4XB -X- -X- B-MISC
, -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Pyke -X- -X- B-ORG
Syndicate -X- -X- I-ORG
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
spice -X- -X- O
mines -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Kessel -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

5-L -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
MSE-6 -X- -X- B-MISC
series -X- -X- O
repair -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
during -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

500 -X- -X- B-LOC
Republica -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
prestigious -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
exclusive -X- -X- O
residential -X- -X- O
tower -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Senate -X- -X- B-LOC
District -X- -X- I-LOC
of -X- -X- I-LOC
Galactic -X- -X- I-LOC
City -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Coruscant -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
here -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Supreme -X- -X- B-PER
Chancellor -X- -X- I-PER
Sheev -X- -X- I-PER
Palpatine -X- -X- I-PER
maintained -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
expansive -X- -X- O
apartment -X- -X- O
suite -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
building -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
upper -X- -X- O
levels -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
wired -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
discreet -X- -X- O
security -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
surveillance -X- -X- O
equipment -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Queen -X- -X- B-PER
PadmĂ© -X- -X- I-PER
Amidala -X- -X- I-PER
of -X- -X- I-PER
Naboo -X- -X- I-PER
stayed -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
500 -X- -X- B-LOC
Republica -X- -X- I-LOC
as -X- -X- O
Palpatine -X- -X- B-PER
's -X- -X- O
guest -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Invasion -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- O-MISC
Naboo -X- -X- O-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Futures -X- -X- B-PER
Program -X- -X- I-PER
graduate -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
former -X- -X- O
Senator -X- -X- B-PER
who -X- -X- O
organized -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Futures -X- -X- B-MISC
Program -X- -X- I-MISC
reunion -X- -X- I-MISC
Galen -X- -X- B-PER
Erso -X- -X- I-PER
attended -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
apartment -X- -X- O
suite -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
tower -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
501st -X- -X- B-ORG
Legion -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
referred -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
501st -X- -X- B-ORG
Battalion -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
501st -X- -X- B-ORG
clone -X- -X- I-ORG
battalion -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
later -X- -X- O
nicknamed -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Vader -X- -X- B-ORG
's -X- -X- I-ORG
Fist -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
elite -X- -X- O
stormtrooper -X- -X- O
legion -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
command -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Dark -X- -X- B-PER
Lord -X- -X- I-PER
of -X- -X- I-PER
the -X- -X- I-PER
Sith -X- -X- I-PER
Darth -X- -X- I-PER
Vader -X- -X- I-PER
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-MISC
Era -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Under -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
leadership -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
General -X- -X- I-PER
Anakin -X- -X- I-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Commander -X- -X- I-PER
Ahsoka -X- -X- I-PER
Tano -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- B-PER
Commander -X- -X- I-PER
CT-7567 -X- -X- I-PER
" -X- -X- O
Rex -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
501st -X- -X- B-ORG
fought -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-ORG
Droid -X- -X- I-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
the -X- -X- I-ORG
Confederacy -X- -X- I-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
Independent -X- -X- I-ORG
Systems -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

5251977 -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
small -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
obscure -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
given -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
besides -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
numerical -X- -X- O
designation -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Because -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
slow -X- -X- O
rotation -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
5251977 -X- -X- B-LOC
had -X- -X- O
days -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
nights -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
lasted -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
equivalent -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
weeks -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
most -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
planets -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
53 -X- -X- B-PER
" -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
individual -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
aboard -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
Death -X- -X- B-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
planet-killing -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
station -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

5387 -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
fellow -X- -X- O
stormtrooper -X- -X- O
5389 -X- -X- B-PER
were -X- -X- O
called -X- -X- O
upon -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
stormtrooper -X- -X- O
comrades -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
follow -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
trooper -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Around -X- -X- O
9 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
group -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
infiltrators -X- -X- O
sabotaged -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
base -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
cooling -X- -X- O
system -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
prevented -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
control -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Nevarro -X- -X- B-LOC
's -X- -X- O
lava -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
55VH -X- -X- B-MISC
Vocabulator -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
vocabulator -X- -X- O
owned -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
G2-1B7 -X- -X- B-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
5L5 -X- -X- B-MISC
fusial -X- -X- O
thrust -X- -X- O
engine -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
engine -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
T-70 -X- -X- B-MISC
X-wing -X- -X- I-MISC
starfighter -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
614-AvA -X- -X- B-MISC
speeder -X- -X- O
bike -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Lothal -X- -X- B-MISC
Speeder -X- -X- I-MISC
Bike -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-ORG
Military -X- -X- I-ORG
speeder -X- -X- O
bike -X- -X- O
model -X- -X- O
manufactured -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Aratech -X- -X- B-ORG
Repulsor -X- -X- I-ORG
Company -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
61st -X- -X- B-ORG
Mobile -X- -X- I-ORG
Infantry -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
referred -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
61st -X- -X- B-ORG
or -X- -X- O
Twilight -X- -X- B-ORG
Company -X- -X- I-ORG
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
unit -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- B-ORG
to -X- -X- I-ORG
Restore -X- -X- I-ORG
the -X- -X- I-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
under -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
command -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Captain -X- -X- B-PER
Micha -X- -X- I-PER
Evon -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
Howl -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-MISC
Civil -X- -X- I-MISC
War -X- -X- I-MISC
against -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
631 -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
model -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
B1-series -X- -X- B-MISC
battle -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-ORG
Droid -X- -X- I-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- B-MISC
Wars -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
67e -X- -X- B-MISC
fusion -X- -X- O
core -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
fusion -X- -X- O
generator -X- -X- O
manufactured -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Klyd-Marro -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

These -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
K-88 -X- -X- B-MISC
" -X- -X- I-MISC
Event -X- -X- I-MISC
Horizon -X- -X- I-MISC
" -X- -X- I-MISC
sublight -X- -X- O
engines -X- -X- O
commonly -X- -X- O
installed -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
RZ-2 -X- -X- B-MISC
A-wing -X- -X- I-MISC
interceptors -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
68th -X- -X- B-ORG
Legion -X- -X- I-ORG
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
legion -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
's -X- -X- I-ORG
Imperial -X- -X- I-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
Verpine -X- -X- B-MISC
smuggler -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Abednedo -X- -X- B-LOC
owned -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
hold -X- -X- O
captured -X- -X- O
stormtroopers -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

6C -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
room -X- -X- O
number -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
small -X- -X- O
apartment -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Pons -X- -X- B-LOC
Ora -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
small -X- -X- O
settlement -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
remote -X- -X- O
desert -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Abafar -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

6G-66 -X- -X- B-MISC
, -X- -X- O
nicknamed -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Sixer -X- -X- B-MISC
, -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
astromech -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
service -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- B-ORG
during -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

6L-CH -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
overstressed -X- -X- O
green-plated -X- -X- O
BB-series -X- -X- O
astromech -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
service -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
709th -X- -X- B-ORG
Legion -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Red -X- -X- B-ORG
Fury -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
elite -X- -X- O
stormtrooper -X- -X- O
legion -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
under -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
command -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Supreme -X- -X- B-PER
Leader -X- -X- I-PER
Kylo -X- -X- I-PER
Ren -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

Lieutenant -X- -X- B-PER
Agnon -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
stormtrooper -X- -X- O
sergeant -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
staff -X- -X- O
officers -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
709th -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

7169 -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
B1-series -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
's -X- -X- O
Droid -X- -X- B-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
32 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
deployed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- B-LOC
of -X- -X- I-LOC
Theed -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Naboo -X- -X- B-LOC
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Federation -X- -X- B-ORG
during -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
invasion -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

7173 -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
designation -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
member -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Stormtrooper -X- -X- B-ORG
Corps -X- -X- I-ORG
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
71st -X- -X- B-MISC
GAV -X- -X- I-MISC
Battalion -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
battalion -X- -X- O
composed -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
tank -X- -X- O
drivers -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
stormtroopers -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
72 -X- -X- B-MISC
twin -X- -X- I-MISC
auto-blaster -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
auto-blaster -X- -X- O
manufactured -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Gyrhil -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

7276 -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
B1-series -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
Droid -X- -X- I-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
closing -X- -X- O
phases -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Naboo -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
approached -X- -X- O
Bombad -X- -X- B-PER
General -X- -X- I-PER
Jar -X- -X- I-PER
Jar -X- -X- I-PER
Binks -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
told -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
surrender -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Gungan -X- -X- B-PER
quickly -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

7276 -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
deactivated -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
like -X- -X- O
all -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
Federation -X- -X- B-ORG
droids -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Droid -X- -X- B-MISC
Control -X- -X- I-MISC
Ship -X- -X- I-MISC
orbiting -X- -X- O
Naboo -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
destroyed -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
74-Y -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
popular -X- -X- O
model -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
civilian -X- -X- O
speeder -X- -X- O
bike -X- -X- O
manufactured -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Aratech -X- -X- B-ORG
Repulsor -X- -X- I-ORG
Company -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

All -X- -X- O
machinery -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Empire -X- -X- B-ORG
deemed -X- -X- O
unnecessary -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
stripped -X- -X- O
off -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
maximize -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
speeder -X- -X- O
bike -X- -X- O
's -X- -X- O
speed -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

77 -X- -X- B-MISC
Squadron -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
starfighter -X- -X- O
squadron -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
New -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
's -X- -X- O
starfighter -X- -X- O
corps -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-MISC
Civil -X- -X- I-MISC
War -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

ARC -X- -X- B-ORG
trooper -X- -X- O
Fives -X- -X- B-PER
had -X- -X- O
taxi -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
Jay -X- -X- B-PER
Igno -X- -X- I-PER
take -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
79 -X- -X- B-MISC
's -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
met -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
friend -X- -X- O
Kix -X- -X- B-PER
to -X- -X- O
ask -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
help -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
Fives -X- -X- B-PER
discovered -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Order -X- -X- B-ORG
66 -X- -X- I-ORG
conspiracy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
7G -X- -X- B-LOC
sector -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sector -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
space -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Unknown -X- -X- B-LOC
Regions -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
7th -X- -X- B-MISC
Fleet -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
Seventh -X- -X- B-MISC
Fleet -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
fleet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-ORG
Navy -X- -X- I-ORG
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
reign -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
unsuccessful -X- -X- O
bid -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
prison -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Toren -X- -X- B-PER
agreed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
help -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
Agent -X- -X- B-PER
Terex -X- -X- I-PER
kill -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- B-ORG
pilot -X- -X- O
Poe -X- -X- B-PER
Dameron -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
Black -X- -X- B-PER
Squadron -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
storm -X- -X- O
Grakkus -X- -X- B-PER
the -X- -X- O
Hutt -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
fortress -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

This -X- -X- O
plot -X- -X- O
failed -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Terex -X- -X- B-PER
abandoned -X- -X- O
Toren -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
fellow -X- -X- O
gangsters -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
die -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weight -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Megalox -X- -X- B-LOC
Beta -X- -X- I-LOC
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
heavy -X- -X- O
atmosphere -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torge -X- -X- B-PER
Gommer -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- B-ORG
to -X- -X- I-ORG
Restore -X- -X- I-ORG
the -X- -X- I-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-MISC
Civil -X- -X- I-MISC
War -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Gommer -X- -X- B-PER
served -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-MISC
Alliance -X- -X- I-MISC
Starfighter -X- -X- I-MISC
Corps -X- -X- I-MISC
in -X- -X- O
Green -X- -X- B-ORG
Squadron -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
callsign -X- -X- O
Green -X- -X- B-MISC
Two -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Shortly -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Yavin -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
participated -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Scarif -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Toria-vic -X- -X- B-LOC
Nebula -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
nebula -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
contained -X- -X- O
Planetoid -X- -X- B-MISC
A -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- I-MISC
17 -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Torjeka -X- -X- B-ORG
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
company -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
manufactured -X- -X- O
scanner -X- -X- O
goggles -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
Denic -X- -X- B-PER
always -X- -X- O
wore -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
pair -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Torjeka -X- -X- B-ORG
scanner -X- -X- O
goggles -X- -X- O
while -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
lived -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
moon -X- -X- O
Jedha -X- -X- B-LOC
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
reign -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Torment -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-MISC
II-class -X- -X- I-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
Destroyer -X- -X- I-MISC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
naval -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
that -X- -X- O
participated -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Theed -X- -X- I-MISC
during -X- -X- O
Operation -X- -X- B-MISC
: -X- -X- I-MISC
Cinder -X- -X- I-MISC
and -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
helmed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Captain -X- -X- B-PER
Lerr -X- -X- I-PER
Duvat -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Tormentor -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-MISC
II-class -X- -X- I-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
Destroyer -X- -X- I-MISC
that -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
flagship -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Captain -X- -X- B-PER
Amos -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
fleet -X- -X- O
following -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Endor -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
destroyed -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
above -X- -X- O
Desevro -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Tormo -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Twi -X- -X- B-MISC
' -X- -X- I-MISC
lek -X- -X- I-MISC
male -X- -X- O
bomb -X- -X- O
expert -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
member -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rebel -X- -X- O
group -X- -X- O
led -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Yendor -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
year -X- -X- O
5 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Yendor -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
team -X- -X- O
went -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
relief -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Ryloth -X- -X- B-LOC
but -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
only -X- -X- O
found -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
abandoned -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-ORG
station -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
injured -X- -X- O
stormtrooper -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Toro -X- -X- B-PER
Calican -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
bounty -X- -X- O
hunter -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
New -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Looking -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
get -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Bounty -X- -X- B-MISC
Hunters -X- -X- I-MISC
' -X- -X- I-MISC
Guild -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
Calican -X- -X- B-PER
took -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
job -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
find -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
assassin -X- -X- O
Fennec -X- -X- B-PER
Shand -X- -X- I-PER
on -X- -X- O
Tatooine -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
encountered -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bounty -X- -X- O
hunter -X- -X- O
Din -X- -X- B-PER
Djarin -X- -X- I-PER
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mos -X- -X- B-LOC
Eisley -X- -X- I-LOC
Cantina -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
seeking -X- -X- O
assistance -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
job -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
managed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
capture -X- -X- O
Shand -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
informed -X- -X- O
Calican -X- -X- B-PER
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mandalorian -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
target -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Guild -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Calican -X- -X- B-PER
shot -X- -X- O
Shand -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
instead -X- -X- O
sought -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
turn -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mandalorian -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

Returning -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mandalorian -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
starship -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Razor -X- -X- B-MISC
Crest -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
Calican -X- -X- B-PER
captured -X- -X- O
Grogu -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
whom -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Mandalorian -X- -X- B-PER
had -X- -X- O
rescued -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Guild -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Mandalorian -X- -X- B-PER
killed -X- -X- O
Calican -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
left -X- -X- O
Tatooine -X- -X- B-LOC
with -X- -X- O
Grogu -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
ending -X- -X- O
Calican -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
bounty -X- -X- O
hunting -X- -X- O
career -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
even -X- -X- O
begun -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torost -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
terrestrial -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
galaxy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
By -X- -X- O
35 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Torost -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
entirely -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
control -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- B-ORG
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
such -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
contested -X- -X- O
locations -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
deployed -X- -X- O
ground -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
under -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
direction -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
General -X- -X- B-PER
Bellava -X- -X- I-PER
Parnadee -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
torpedo -X- -X- O
siege -X- -X- O
platform -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
proposed -X- -X- O
design -X- -X- O
developed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Special -X- -X- B-ORG
Weapons -X- -X- I-ORG
Group -X- -X- I-ORG
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
aftermath -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Naboo -X- -X- B-MISC
Crisis -X- -X- I-MISC
of -X- -X- O
32 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
However -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
because -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
pacifistic -X- -X- O
leanings -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
consequent -X- -X- O
lack -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
funding -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
project -X- -X- O
never -X- -X- O
made -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
past -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planning -X- -X- O
stage -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torpedo -X- -X- B-MISC
Spheres -X- -X- I-MISC
were -X- -X- O
allegedly -X- -X- O
large -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
disk-shaped -X- -X- O
siege -X- -X- O
platforms -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
that -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
armed -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
hundreds -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
proton -X- -X- O
torpedo -X- -X- O
launchers -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Given -X- -X- O
enough -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
stations -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
crack -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
any -X- -X- O
planetary -X- -X- O
shield -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Torpedo -X- -X- B-MISC
Sphere -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
featured -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
report -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-ORG
weapons -X- -X- O
projects -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
Colonel -X- -X- I-ORG
Haxen -X- -X- I-ORG
Delto -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
later -X- -X- O
integrated -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-MISC
Files -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
archive -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
sensitive -X- -X- O
information -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
rediscovered -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- B-ORG
decades -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-MISC
Civil -X- -X- I-MISC
War -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
Torphlus -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
galaxy -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
homeworld -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Torphlusian -X- -X- B-MISC
senator -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
represented -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Senate -X- -X- I-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
the -X- -X- I-ORG
New -X- -X- I-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Torphlusian -X- -X- B-MISC
were -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tentacled -X- -X- O
sentient -X- -X- O
species -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
lived -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
galaxy -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
5 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
One -X- -X- O
such -X- -X- O
Torphlusian -X- -X- B-PER
represented -X- -X- O
Torphlus -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Senate -X- -X- I-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
the -X- -X- I-ORG
New -X- -X- I-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Torplex -X- -X- B-ORG
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
company -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
notably -X- -X- O
manufactured -X- -X- O
deflector -X- -X- O
shield -X- -X- O
projectors -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
flight -X- -X- O
computers -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Models -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
latter -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
Navy -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
TIE -X- -X- B-MISC
/ -X- -X- I-MISC
fo -X- -X- I-MISC
and -X- -X- O
TIE -X- -X- B-MISC
/ -X- -X- I-MISC
sfs -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
An -X- -X- O
experimental -X- -X- O
flight -X- -X- O
computer -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Elrik -X- -X- B-PER
Vonreg -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
TIE -X- -X- B-MISC
Baron -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
modified -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
TIE -X- -X- B-MISC
/ -X- -X- I-MISC
IN -X- -X- I-MISC
interceptor -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
Torplex -X- -X- B-ORG
flight -X- -X- O
computer -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sophisticated -X- -X- O
model -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
flight -X- -X- O
computer -X- -X- O
produced -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Torplex -X- -X- B-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Such -X- -X- O
computers -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
installed -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
TIE -X- -X- B-MISC
fighters -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
computer -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
movements -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
control -X- -X- O
columns -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
adjust -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
fighter -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Ion -X- -X- O
engines -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torra -X- -X- B-PER
Doza -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
lived -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Colossus -X- -X- B-MISC
, -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
aircraft -X- -X- O
refueling -X- -X- O
station -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Outer -X- -X- B-LOC
Rim -X- -X- I-LOC
world -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Castilon -X- -X- B-MISC
, -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
era -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
New -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
daughter -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Venisa -X- -X- B-PER
Doza -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
former -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alliance -X- -X- B-ORG
to -X- -X- I-ORG
Restore -X- -X- I-ORG
the -X- -X- I-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
mother -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
exploits -X- -X- O
helped -X- -X- O
inspire -X- -X- O
Doza -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
own -X- -X- O
love -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
flying -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
She -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
resident -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
facility -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
upper -X- -X- O
levels -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
owing -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
father -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Captain -X- -X- B-PER
Imanuel -X- -X- I-PER
Doza -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
station -X- -X- O
operator -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torra -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
quarters -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
Torra -X- -X- B-PER
Doza -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
room -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Doza -X- -X- B-LOC
Tower -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Torreb -X- -X- B-PER
Savato -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
arrested -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Canto -X- -X- B-ORG
Bight -X- -X- I-ORG
Police -X- -X- I-ORG
Department -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
locked -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
cells -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Canto -X- -X- B-ORG
Bight -X- -X- I-ORG
police -X- -X- I-ORG
headquarters -X- -X- I-ORG
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Cantonica -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
year -X- -X- O
34 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
criminal -X- -X- O
DJ -X- -X- B-PER
escaped -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
nearby -X- -X- O
cell -X- -X- O
using -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
skeleton -X- -X- O
key -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Savato -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
prisoners -X- -X- O
reached -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bars -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
cell -X- -X- O
toward -X- -X- O
DJ -X- -X- B-PER
; -X- -X- O
however -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
left -X- -X- O
without -X- -X- O
freeing -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

While -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
cell -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
wore -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mottled -X- -X- O
brown -X- -X- O
jerkin -X- -X- O
along -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
pair -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
gray -X- -X- O
pants -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
brown -X- -X- O
boots -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

They -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
led -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- B-PER
Captain -X- -X- I-PER
CT-7567 -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Rex -X- -X- B-PER
", -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
first-in -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
command -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
General -X- -X- I-PER
Anakin -X- -X- I-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

Tophen -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Christophsis -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
hometown -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
prime -X- -X- O
minister -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
After -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
prime -X- -X- O
minister -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
executed -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
3 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
treason -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
during -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
series -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
arrests -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Tophen -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
"" -X- -X- O
pacified -X- -X- O
"" -X- -X- O
due -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
center -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
insurgency -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tophid -X- -X- B-PER
Bruster -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
designated -X- -X- O
DT-4431 -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
lieutenant -X- -X- O
TIE -X- -X- B-MISC
fighter -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Starfighter -X- -X- B-ORG
Corps -X- -X- I-ORG
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
35 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Bruster -X- -X- B-PER
piloted -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
TIE -X- -X- B-MISC
/ -X- -X- I-MISC
fo -X- -X- I-MISC
space -X- -X- O
superiority -X- -X- O
fighter -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
group -X- -X- O
sent -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
destroy -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
YT-1300 -X- -X- B-MISC
light -X- -X- O
freighter -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Millennium -X- -X- B-MISC
Falcon -X- -X- I-MISC
while -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Sinta -X- -X- B-LOC
Glacier -X- -X- I-LOC
Colony -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
Bruster -X- -X- B-PER
engaged -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
freighter -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
ultimately -X- -X- O
escaped -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tophin -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
resident -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
farming -X- -X- O
community -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
outskirts -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Black -X- -X- B-LOC
Spire -X- -X- I-LOC
Outpost -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
Batuu -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
cousin -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Dolin -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
When -X- -X- O
Tophin -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
killed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
stormtroopers -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
farmers -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
community -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
made -X- -X- O
aware -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
tyranny -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
attempted -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
fight -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Topple -X- -X- B-ORG
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
establishment -X- -X- O
where -X- -X- O
Walt -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
friend -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Juahir -X- -X- B-PER
Madras -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
They -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
clientele -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
hire -X- -X- O
due -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
malfunctioning -X- -X- O
server -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
connected -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
locations -X- -X- O
Feriae -X- -X- B-LOC
Junction -X- -X- I-LOC
and -X- -X- O
Pho -X- -X- B-LOC
Ph -X- -X- I-LOC
' -X- -X- I-LOC
eah -X- -X- I-LOC
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Hydian -X- -X- B-MISC
Way -X- -X- I-MISC
hyperspace -X- -X- O
route -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Topside -X- -X- B-LOC
Dome -X- -X- I-LOC
was -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Polis -X- -X- B-LOC
Massa -X- -X- I-LOC
Base -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
facility -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
provided -X- -X- O
food -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
rest -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
base -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
archaeologists -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
included -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
equipment -X- -X- O
store -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
artifact -X- -X- O
documentation -X- -X- O
facilities -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
basic -X- -X- O
laboratory -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
analysis -X- -X- O
center -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
When -X- -X- O
Wyl -X- -X- B-PER
Lark -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
another -X- -X- O
Polynean -X- -X- B-PER
who -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
left -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
part -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Hundred -X- -X- B-ORG
and -X- -X- O
Twenty -X- -X- B-ORG
, -X- -X- O
spoke -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Elder -X- -X- B-PER
Zephyr -X- -X- I-PER
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
skirmish -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Circus -X- -X- B-LOC
of -X- -X- I-LOC
Mortal -X- -X- I-LOC
Appetites -X- -X- I-LOC
about -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
desire -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
return -X- -X- O
home -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Elder -X- -X- B-PER
informed -X- -X- O
Lark -X- -X- B-PER
that -X- -X- O
Groundling -X- -X- B-PER
had -X- -X- O
arrived -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Tor -X- -X- B-LOC
the -X- -X- O
day -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torban -X- -X- B-PER
Buck -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
nicknamed -X- -X- O
" -X- -X- O
Buckets -X- -X- B-PER
of -X- -X- I-PER
Blood -X- -X- I-PER
," -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Chagrian -X- -X- B-PER
male -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Master -X- -X- I-PER
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
healer -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
High -X- -X- B-MISC
Republic -X- -X- I-MISC
Era -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Alongside -X- -X- O
Master -X- -X- B-PER
Yoda -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
Buck -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
stationed -X- -X- O
aboard -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-MISC
Padawan -X- -X- I-MISC
academic -X- -X- O
cruiser -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- B-MISC
Hopper -X- -X- I-MISC
when -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
cruiser -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
passengers -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
forced -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
respond -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
fallout -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Great -X- -X- B-MISC
Disaster -X- -X- I-MISC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Trymant -X- -X- B-LOC
system -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torben -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
member -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Scyre -X- -X- B-ORG
clan -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Parnassos -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
He -X- -X- O
accompanied -X- -X- O
Phasma -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
Siv -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
Gosta -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Carr -X- -X- B-PER
on -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
journey -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
return -X- -X- O
Brendol -X- -X- B-PER
Hux -X- -X- I-PER
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
back -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
crash -X- -X- O
landed -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torben -X- -X- B-PER
fought -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
killed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
brother -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
group -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Scyre -X- -X- B-ORG
led -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Keldo -X- -X- B-PER
caught -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
Phasma -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
Torben -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Siv -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
helping -X- -X- O
General -X- -X- B-PER
Brendol -X- -X- I-PER
Hux -X- -X- I-PER
get -X- -X- O
back -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
crash -X- -X- O
landing -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Parnassos -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
As -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
fell -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ground -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Siv -X- -X- B-PER
saw -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
small -X- -X- O
smile -X- -X- O
lit -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
face -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
thought -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
saw -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
lips -X- -X- O
form -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
words -X- -X- O
thank -X- -X- O
you -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

This -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
mother -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Torben -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
When -X- -X- O
Torben -X- -X- B-PER
told -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
mother -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
wanted -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
stay -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Nautilus -X- -X- B-MISC
forever -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
tell -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
normal -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bird -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
love -X- -X- O
captivity -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
until -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
longs -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
fly -X- -X- O
again -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
She -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
born -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
raised -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Siv -X- -X- B-PER
in -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Con -X- -X- B-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
Mining -X- -X- I-MISC
Corporation -X- -X- I-MISC
facility -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Calliope -X- -X- B-MISC
Station -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
first -X- -X- O
ten -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
life -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
shared -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Tusken -X- -X- B-PER
Raider -X- -X- I-PER
criminal -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
profile -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
registry -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Tusken -X- -X- B-PER
Raider -X- -X- I-PER
shared -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
name -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
criminal -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
profile -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
registry -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torch -X- -X- B-MISC
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
astromech -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
masculine -X- -X- O
programming -X- -X- O
owned -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Resistance -X- -X- B-ORG
pilot -X- -X- O
Venisa -X- -X- B-PER
Doza -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
accompanied -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
many -X- -X- O
missions -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
including -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Bakura -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
Lehon -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
When -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
captured -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Agent -X- -X- B-PER
Tierny -X- -X- I-PER
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
First -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
Torch -X- -X- B-PER
pretended -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
have -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
fried -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
rendered -X- -X- O
inoperable -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
order -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
assist -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Doza -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
agent -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Resurgent-class -X- -X- B-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
Destroyer -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
ultimately -X- -X- O
piloting -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
TIE -X- -X- B-MISC
/ -X- -X- I-MISC
fo -X- -X- I-MISC
space -X- -X- O
superiority -X- -X- O
fighter -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
capital -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
main -X- -X- O
hangar -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
diversion -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Torch -X- -X- B-LOC
Nebula -X- -X- I-LOC
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Torch -X- -X- B-LOC
sector -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
nebula -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Outer -X- -X- B-LOC
Rim -X- -X- I-LOC
Territories -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
The -X- -X- O
Spice -X- -X- B-MISC
Runners -X- -X- I-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Kijimi -X- -X- I-MISC
undertook -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
heist -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
nearby -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Guat -X- -X- B-LOC
' -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
subsequently -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Osako -X- -X- B-MISC
pirates -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Torch -X- -X- B-LOC
Nebula -X- -X- I-LOC
along -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Llanic -X- -X- B-MISC
Spice -X- -X- I-MISC
Run -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

" -X- -X- O
During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
High -X- -X- B-MISC
Republic -X- -X- I-MISC
Era -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
group -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Nihil -X- -X- B-LOC
raiders -X- -X- O
torched -X- -X- O
Nelgenam -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
company -X- -X- O
fought -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
engagements -X- -X- O
against -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Confederacy -X- -X- B-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
Independent -X- -X- I-ORG
Systems -X- -X- I-ORG
throughout -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
including -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Christophsis -X- -X- I-MISC
and -X- -X- I-PER
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Teth -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Torrent -X- -X- B-MISC
wisp -X- -X- O
trees -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
species -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
tree -X- -X- O
native -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Concordia -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
moon -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Mandalore -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Outer -X- -X- B-LOC
Rim -X- -X- I-LOC
Territories -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
tree -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
windswept -X- -X- O
appearance -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
leaves -X- -X- O
facing -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
direction -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
trunk -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
tree -X- -X- O
curved -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
same -X- -X- O
direction -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
torrent -X- -X- O
wisp -X- -X- O
trees -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
found -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
countryside -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Concordia -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
lined -X- -X- O
paths -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
region -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torret -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Pamarthen -X- -X- B-MISC
pilot -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
competed -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Gauntlet -X- -X- B-MISC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
starship -X- -X- O
race -X- -X- O
run -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Han -X- -X- B-PER
Solo -X- -X- I-PER
on -X- -X- O
Corellia -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Han -X- -X- B-PER
Solo -X- -X- I-PER
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
run-in -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
Torrian -X- -X- B-MISC
security -X- -X- O
guards -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Hosnian -X- -X- B-LOC
Prime -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Torro -X- -X- B-PER
Sbazzle -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Devaronian -X- -X- B-MISC
female -X- -X- O
Executive -X- -X- B-MISC
Chef -X- -X- I-MISC
who -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Baron -X- -X- B-MISC
Administrator -X- -X- I-MISC
Lando -X- -X- I-PER
Calrissian -X- -X- I-PER
of -X- -X- O
Cloud -X- -X- B-LOC
City -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Calrissian -X- -X- B-PER
requested -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
Sbazzle -X- -X- B-PER
cook -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Darth -X- -X- B-PER
Vader -X- -X- I-PER
when -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Sith -X- -X- B-PER
Lord -X- -X- I-PER
visited -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
city -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Torture -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
means -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
punishment -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
interrogation -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
causing -X- -X- O
physical -X- -X- O
pain -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Darth -X- -X- B-PER
Vader -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
adept -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
: -X- -X- O
even -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
Force -X- -X- B-MISC
choked -X- -X- O
Poggle -X- -X- B-PER
the -X- -X- I-PER
Lesser -X- -X- I-PER
to -X- -X- O
gain -X- -X- O
information -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
killing -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
brain -X- -X- O
worms -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
once -X- -X- O
tortured -X- -X- O
Han -X- -X- B-PER
Solo -X- -X- I-PER
so -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
pain -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
reverberate -X- -X- O
through -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Force -X- -X- B-MISC
and -X- -X- O
draw -X- -X- O
out -X- -X- O
Luke -X- -X- B-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
torture -X- -X- O
web -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
torture -X- -X- O
device -X- -X- O
use -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Vane -X- -X- B-PER
Ă© -X- -X- I-PER
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Mustafar -X- -X- B-LOC
to -X- -X- O
torture -X- -X- O
rebel -X- -X- O
Lieutenant -X- -X- B-MISC
Thom -X- -X- B-PER
Hudd -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
appear -X- -X- O
gruff -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
interacting -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
customers -X- -X- O
; -X- -X- O
however -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
ever -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
traded -X- -X- O
goods -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
parents -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Norra -X- -X- B-PER
Wexley -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
sister -X- -X- O
Esmelle -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
would -X- -X- O
always -X- -X- O
slip -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
children -X- -X- O
candy-swirl -X- -X- O
sticks -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

At -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
point -X- -X- O
prior -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
Wexley -X- -X- B-PER
leaving -X- -X- O
Akiva -X- -X- B-LOC
to -X- -X- O
fight -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-MISC
Civil -X- -X- I-MISC
War -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
Bolo -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
store -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
burned -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
rumor -X- -X- O
spread -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
arsonist -X- -X- O
responsible -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
someone -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
black -X- -X- O
market -X- -X- O
looking -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
make -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
profit -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
reducing -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
availability -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
certain -X- -X- O
items -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Toryn -X- -X- B-PER
Farr -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
communications -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-MISC
Civil -X- -X- I-MISC
War -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Toryn -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
sister -X- -X- O
Samoc -X- -X- B-PER
Farr -X- -X- I-PER
joined -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
rebellion -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
young -X- -X- O
age -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
became -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
best -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
areas -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Three -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Yavin -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
stationed -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Echo -X- -X- B-LOC
Base -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Hoth -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
tasked -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
monitoring -X- -X- O
anomalies -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
Hoth -X- -X- B-LOC
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
atmosphere -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

At -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
point -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Farr -X- -X- B-PER
noticed -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
signature -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
thought -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- B-MISC
Destroyer -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
passed -X- -X- O
right -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Hoth -X- -X- B-LOC
without -X- -X- O
deviating -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
flight -X- -X- O
path -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tosan -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Zygerrian -X- -X- B-MISC
female -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Master -X- -X- I-PER
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-ORG
Order -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
following -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Naboo -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

At -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
point -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
informed -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Knight -X- -X- I-PER
Obi-Wan -X- -X- I-PER
Kenobi -X- -X- I-PER
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-ORG
Council -X- -X- I-ORG
had -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
concerning -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-ORG
holocron -X- -X- O
discovered -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Dallenor -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Tenacious -X- -X- B-PER
by -X- -X- O
nature -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Tosan -X- -X- B-PER
used -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
yellow-colored -X- -X- O
double-bladed -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tosche -X- -X- B-MISC
Station -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
power -X- -X- O
station -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
repair -X- -X- O
shop -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
outskirts -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Anchorhead -X- -X- B-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
desert -X- -X- O
world -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Tatooine -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
owned -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Merl -X- -X- B-PER
Tosche -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
operated -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Laze -X- -X- B-PER
Loneozner -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
witnessing -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
skies -X- -X- O
over -X- -X- O
Tatooine -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Skywalker -X- -X- B-PER
told -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
friends -X- -X- O
about -X- -X- O
what -X- -X- O
he -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
seen -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
not -X- -X- O
believe -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Toscwons -X- -X- B-MISC
were -X- -X- O
creatures -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
lived -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Ithor -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

When -X- -X- O
hunting -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
molsumes -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
jungles -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Ithor -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Dowutin -X- -X- B-PER
Grummgar -X- -X- I-PER
informed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
Nysorly -X- -X- B-PER
that -X- -X- O
if -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
wanted -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
do -X- -X- O
more -X- -X- O
local -X- -X- O
hunting -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
wouldn -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
t -X- -X- O
need -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
change -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
camouflage -X- -X- O
provided -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
hadn -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
t -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
licked -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
death -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
toscwon -X- -X- O
beforehand -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Toshdor -X- -X- B-PER
Ni -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
Lorrdian -X- -X- B-PER
member -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Brotherhood -X- -X- B-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
the -X- -X- I-ORG
Beatific -X- -X- I-ORG
Countenance -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
pilgrim -X- -X- O
visiting -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Holy -X- -X- B-LOC
City -X- -X- I-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
moon -X- -X- O
Jedha -X- -X- B-LOC
shortly -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
destruction -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
test -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Death -X- -X- B-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
superlaser -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

To -X- -X- O
hide -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
naturally -X- -X- O
occurring -X- -X- O
odor -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
species -X- -X- O
produced -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Ni -X- -X- B-PER
wore -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
censer -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
dispensed -X- -X- O
Qatameric -X- -X- B-MISC
incense -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Toshma -X- -X- B-PER
Jefkin -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
soldier -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
military -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
guard -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Alderaanian -X- -X- B-MISC
consular -X- -X- O
security -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
serving -X- -X- O
aboard -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Tantive -X- -X- B-MISC
IV -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
second -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
0 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tosste -X- -X- B-LOC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
location -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
describing -X- -X- O
early -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- O
history -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
Strategy -X- -X- B-MISC
and -X- -X- I-MISC
Tactics -X- -X- I-MISC
class -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
academy -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Arkanis -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
Colonel -X- -X- B-PER
Julyan -X- -X- I-PER
taught -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
students -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Tosste -X- -X- B-LOC
that -X- -X- O
Admiral -X- -X- B-PER
Terrinald -X- -X- I-PER
Screed -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-ORG
Navy -X- -X- I-ORG
smashed -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Iska -X- -X- B-MISC
pirates -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
driven -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
Fanha -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Tost -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
individual -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
served -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
captain -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
InterGalactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Banking -X- -X- I-ORG
Clan -X- -X- I-ORG
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Iotran -X- -X- B-PER
Guard -X- -X- I-PER
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- B-MISC
Wars -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
galactic -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Confederacy -X- -X- B-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
Independent -X- -X- I-ORG
Systems -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
Tost -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Iotran -X- -X- B-PER
Guard -X- -X- I-PER
fought -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
side -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatists -X- -X- B-ORG
â€” -X- -X- O
along -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
support -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
IG-100 -X- -X- B-MISC
MagnaGuards -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
bodyguards -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Confederacy -X- -X- B-ORG
â€” -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
protected -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
collection -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
planets -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
vault -X- -X- O
worlds -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tosta -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
male -X- -X- O
Nikto -X- -X- B-PER
magistrate -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Bastatha -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
28 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tosta -X- -X- B-PER
worked -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
another -X- -X- O
magistrate -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Xun -X- -X- B-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Tosta -X- -X- B-PER
was -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
cahoots -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
elements -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
organized -X- -X- O
crime -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Bastatha -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
helped -X- -X- O
lead -X- -X- O
New -X- -X- B-PER
Republic -X- -X- I-PER
Senator -X- -X- I-PER
Leia -X- -X- I-PER
Organa -X- -X- I-PER
into -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
kidnapping -X- -X- O
plot -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
arrived -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Bastatha -X- -X- B-LOC
to -X- -X- O
investigate -X- -X- O
Rinnrivin -X- -X- B-PER
Di -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
criminal -X- -X- O
empire -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tostovin -X- -X- B-MISC
Munitions -X- -X- I-MISC
were -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
weapons -X- -X- O
manufacturing -X- -X- O
company -X- -X- O
active -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
reign -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
and -X- -X- O
still -X- -X- O
active -X- -X- O
around -X- -X- O
thirty -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Endor -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Hylobon -X- -X- B-MISC
guards -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Dryden -X- -X- B-PER
Vos -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
public -X- -X- O
face -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Crimson -X- -X- B-MISC
Dawn -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
carried -X- -X- O
JND-41 -X- -X- B-MISC
percussive -X- -X- O
cannons -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Totem -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Saglanost -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
religious -X- -X- O
artifact -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
gave -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Rekk -X- -X- B-MISC
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
time -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Touksingal -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
advisor -X- -X- O
lost -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
arm -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
group -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
bloodthirsty -X- -X- O
bat-like -X- -X- O
- -X- -X- O
predators -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
hunted -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
swarms -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
tour -X- -X- O
guide -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
individual -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
provided -X- -X- O
guidance -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
tourists -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

This -X- -X- O
occupation -X- -X- O
could -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
instances -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
performed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
tour -X- -X- O
guide -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

While -X- -X- O
searching -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Chelli -X- -X- B-PER
Lona -X- -X- I-PER
Aphra -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
droids -X- -X- O
0-0 -X- -X- B-MISC
- -X- -X- I-MISC
0 -X- -X- I-MISC
and -X- -X- O
BT-1 -X- -X- B-MISC
hijacked -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
touring -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
killing -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
crew -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
ejecting -X- -X- O
several -X- -X- O
Bith -X- -X- B-MISC
passengers -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
space -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
individual -X- -X- O
lived -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
galaxy -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Age -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
the -X- -X- I-MISC
Republic -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

She -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
mother -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Trace -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Rafa -X- -X- B-PER
Martez -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
taught -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
daughters -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
help -X- -X- O
others -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
need -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Trace -X- -X- B-PER
initially -X- -X- O
told -X- -X- O
Ahsoka -X- -X- B-PER
Tano -X- -X- I-PER
that -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
parents -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
"" -X- -X- O
split -X- -X- O
,"" -X- -X- O
leaving -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
family -X- -X- O
business -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
Rafa -X- -X- B-PER
later -X- -X- O
told -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
they -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
been -X- -X- O
killed -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Senate -X- -X- B-MISC
hostage -X- -X- O
crisis -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
when -X- -X- O
Cad -X- -X- B-PER
Bane -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
remembered -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
"" -X- -X- O
red-eyed -X- -X- O
alien -X- -X- O
,"" -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
shot -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
transport -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
Ziro -X- -X- B-PER
Desilijic -X- -X- I-PER
Tiure -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
pursuing -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
stopped -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
crashing -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
crowded -X- -X- O
platform -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
instead -X- -X- O
causing -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
accidentally -X- -X- O
crash -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Martez -X- -X- B-PER
family -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
quarters -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
killing -X- -X- O
both -X- -X- O
parents -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Trace -X- -X- B-PER
Martez -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
pilot -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
mechanic -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
along -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
older -X- -X- O
sister -X- -X- O
Rafa -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
lived -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Level -X- -X- B-MISC
1313 -X- -X- I-MISC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Coruscant -X- -X- B-LOC
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
waning -X- -X- O
days -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- B-MISC
Wars -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
Trace -X- -X- B-PER
met -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
former -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Padawan -X- -X- I-PER
Ahsoka -X- -X- I-PER
Tano -X- -X- I-PER
when -X- -X- O
Tano -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
having -X- -X- O
difficulties -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
broken-down -X- -X- O
Joben -X- -X- B-MISC
T-85 -X- -X- I-MISC
speeder -X- -X- O
bike -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
purchased -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
crash-landed -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
platform -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Trace -X- -X- B-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
repair -X- -X- O
shop -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

During -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- B-MISC
Wars -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
Trace -X- -X- B-PER
Martez -X- -X- I-PER
owned -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
repair -X- -X- O
shop -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Level -X- -X- B-MISC
1313 -X- -X- I-MISC
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Coruscant -X- -X- B-LOC
underworld -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

She -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
inherited -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
after -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
parents -X- -X- O
died -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Martez -X- -X- B-PER
kept -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
modified -X- -X- O
Nebula-class -X- -X- B-MISC
freighter -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
working -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
shop -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
named -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Silver -X- -X- B-MISC
Angel -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Martez -X- -X- B-PER
met -X- -X- O
former -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Padawan -X- -X- I-PER
Ahsoka -X- -X- I-PER
Tano -X- -X- I-PER
when -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Togruta -X- -X- B-PER
crashed -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
malfunctioning -X- -X- O
speeder -X- -X- O
bike -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
repair -X- -X- O
shop -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
landing -X- -X- O
pad -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tracene -X- -X- B-PER
Kane -X- -X- I-PER
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
female -X- -X- O
human -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
journalist -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Chandrila -X- -X- B-LOC
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-MISC
Civil -X- -X- I-MISC
War -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

She -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
close -X- -X- O
friends -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
cameraman -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Trandoshan -X- -X- B-MISC
named -X- -X- O
Lug -X- -X- B-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
perished -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
battle -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
Binjai-Tin -X- -X- B-LOC
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Nag -X- -X- B-LOC
Ubdur -X- -X- I-LOC
in -X- -X- O
5 -X- -X- O
ABY -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tracene -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
new -X- -X- O
Sullustan -X- -X- B-MISC
colleague -X- -X- O
Birt -X- -X- B-PER
later -X- -X- O
recorded -X- -X- O
Chancellor -X- -X- B-PER
Mon -X- -X- I-PER
Mothma -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
press -X- -X- O
statement -X- -X- O
regarding -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
discovery -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-ORG
forces -X- -X- I-ORG
on -X- -X- O
Jakku -X- -X- B-LOC
prior -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Battle -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Jakku -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Tracker -X- -X- B-PER
along -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
Threepwood -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
Boil -X- -X- B-PER
accompanied -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-PER
Obi-Wan -X- -X- I-PER
Kenobi -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
Anakin -X- -X- B-PER
Skywalker -X- -X- I-PER
during -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
mission -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
hunt -X- -X- O
down -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Sith -X- -X- B-MISC
fugitives -X- -X- O
Count -X- -X- B-PER
Dooku -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
Quinlan -X- -X- B-PER
Vos -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
escaped -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
custody -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
crash-landed -X- -X- O
their -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Banshee -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Christophsis -X- -X- B-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Tracker -X- -X- B-PER
found -X- -X- O
blood -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
crash -X- -X- O
site -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Jedi-Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
party -X- -X- O
deduced -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
fugitives -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
survived -X- -X- O
but -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
injured -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Shortly -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
forces -X- -X- O
launched -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
attack -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-ORG
base -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Christophsis -X- -X- B-LOC
, -X- -X- O
leading -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Second -X- -X- B-MISC
battle -X- -X- I-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Christophsis -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Tracker -X- -X- B-MISC
I -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
starfighter -X- -X- O
piloted -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-MISC
Hunter -X- -X- I-MISC
droid -X- -X- I-MISC
M-OC -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Emperor -X- -X- B-PER
Palpatine -X- -X- I-PER
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
secret -X- -X- O
project -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

He -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
this -X- -X- O
ship -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
ferry -X- -X- O
him -X- -X- O
across -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
galaxy -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
hunt -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
Rowan -X- -X- B-PER
Freemaker -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
who -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
stolen -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Kyber -X- -X- B-MISC
Saber -X- -X- I-MISC
from -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Emperor -X- -X- B-PER
. -X- -X- O

Upon -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
capture -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
delivery -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
said -X- -X- O
quarry -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Guild -X- -X- B-MISC
operative -X- -X- O
runs -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
sensor -X- -X- O
check -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bounty -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
body -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
compares -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
chain -X- -X- O
code -X- -X- O
data -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
fob -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
confirming -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
identification -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
acquisition -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tracking -X- -X- O
officer -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
tracking -X- -X- O
systems -X- -X- O
specialist -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
position -X- -X- O
within -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
starfleet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

His -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
duty -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
track -X- -X- O
enemy -X- -X- O
starships -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

In -X- -X- O
Star -X- -X- B-MISC
Destroyers -X- -X- I-MISC
, -X- -X- O
such -X- -X- O
officers -X- -X- O
worked -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
data -X- -X- O
pits -X- -X- O
located -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
either -X- -X- O
sides -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
bridge -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
platform -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tracking -X- -X- O
torpedoes -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
torpedo -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Admiral -X- -X- B-PER
Trench -X- -X- I-PER
to -X- -X- O
defeat -X- -X- O
stealth -X- -X- O
ships -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Such -X- -X- O
devices -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
employed -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
vessels -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
creating -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
energy -X- -X- O
field -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
allowed -X- -X- O
them -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
lock -X- -X- O
onto -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
move -X- -X- O
other -X- -X- O
vessels -X- -X- O
or -X- -X- O
objects -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Tractor -X- -X- B-MISC
Beam -X- -X- I-MISC
12 -X- -X- I-MISC
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
beam -X- -X- O
control -X- -X- O
unit -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
board -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Death -X- -X- B-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
beam -X- -X- O
projector -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
device -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
generated -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
beam -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Cantwell-class -X- -X- B-MISC
Arrestor -X- -X- I-MISC
Cruiser -X- -X- I-MISC
boasted -X- -X- O
three -X- -X- O
powerful -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
beam -X- -X- O
projectors -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
which -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
help -X- -X- O
steer -X- -X- O
traffic -X- -X- O
away -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
contruction -X- -X- O
zones -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Located -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
top -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
command -X- -X- O
tower -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
sat -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
two -X- -X- O
deflector -X- -X- O
shield -X- -X- O
projector -X- -X- O
globes -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Imperial -X- -X- B-MISC
II-class -X- -X- I-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
Destroyers -X- -X- I-MISC
replaced -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
array -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
communications -X- -X- O
tower -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
did -X- -X- O
upgraded -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-MISC
I-class -X- -X- I-MISC
Star -X- -X- I-MISC
Destroyers -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

A -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
envelope -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
form -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
gravity -X- -X- O
field -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
wrecked -X- -X- O
ships -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
made -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
body -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
prison -X- -X- O
Accresker -X- -X- B-LOC
Jail -X- -X- I-LOC
were -X- -X- O
held -X- -X- O
together -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
envelope -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
rifle -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
type -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
rifle -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
capable -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
projecting -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
beam -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
pulling -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
object -X- -X- O
such -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
lightsaber -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
report -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
individual -X- -X- O
using -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Force -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
escape -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bar -X- -X- O
fight -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Sith -X- -X- B-PER
Lord -X- -X- I-PER
Darth -X- -X- I-PER
Vader -X- -X- I-PER
traveled -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
bar -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Cabarria -X- -X- B-LOC
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Colonies -X- -X- B-LOC
region -X- -X- I-LOC
. -X- -X- O

Although -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
saber -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
stopped -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Vader -X- -X- B-PER
in -X- -X- O
mid-air -X- -X- O
thanks -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
Force -X- -X- B-MISC
abilities -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
weapon -X- -X- O
eventually -X- -X- O
snapped -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
half -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
red -X- -X- O
kyber -X- -X- O
crystal -X- -X- O
fell -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
ground -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

After -X- -X- O
being -X- -X- O
stranded -X- -X- O
on -X- -X- O
Accresker -X- -X- B-LOC
Jail -X- -X- I-LOC
with -X- -X- O
Chelli -X- -X- B-PER
Lona -X- -X- I-PER
Aphra -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
Sana -X- -X- B-PER
Starros -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Lopset -X- -X- B-PER
Yas -X- -X- I-PER
, -X- -X- O
Captain-Inspector -X- -X- B-PER
Magna -X- -X- I-PER
Tolvan -X- -X- I-PER
contacted -X- -X- O
Imperial -X- -X- B-MISC
Sector -X- -X- I-MISC
Control -X- -X- I-MISC
and -X- -X- O
ordered -X- -X- O
for -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
collision -X- -X- O
course -X- -X- O
between -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
jail -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
Tiferep -X- -X- B-LOC
Major -X- -X- I-LOC
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
aborted -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
dispatch -X- -X- O
tractor -X- -X- O
tugs -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
although -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
denied -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
she -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
believed -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
be -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
Rebel -X- -X- B-ORG
Alliance -X- -X- I-ORG
member -X- -X- O
impersonating -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
was -X- -X- O
an -X- -X- O
interstellar -X- -X- O
shipping -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
trade -X- -X- O
conglomerate -X- -X- O
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
waning -X- -X- O
years -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Republic -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
one -X- -X- O
so -X- -X- O
powerful -X- -X- O
that -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
had -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
own -X- -X- O
representatives -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Senate -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

Viceroy -X- -X- B-PER
Nute -X- -X- I-PER
Gunray -X- -X- I-PER
secretly -X- -X- O
allied -X- -X- O
with -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Sith -X- -X- B-PER
Lord -X- -X- I-PER
Darth -X- -X- I-PER
Sidious -X- -X- I-PER
to -X- -X- O
invade -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
peaceful -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
Naboo -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
cause -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
crisis -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
government -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
although -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
occupation -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
thwarted -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Queen -X- -X- B-PER
Padm -X- -X- I-PER
Ă© -X- -X- I-PER
Amidala -X- -X- I-PER
and -X- -X- O
her -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

Escaping -X- -X- O
imprisonment -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
Gunray -X- -X- B-PER
pledged -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
droid -X- -X- O
forces -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Confederacy -X- -X- B-ORG
of -X- -X- I-ORG
Independent -X- -X- I-ORG
Systems -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Federation -X- -X- B-ORG
fought -X- -X- O
Republic -X- -X- B-ORG
and -X- -X- O
Jedi -X- -X- B-ORG
armies -X- -X- O
throughout -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Clone -X- -X- B-MISC
Wars -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Gunray -X- -X- B-PER
and -X- -X- O
his -X- -X- O
fellow -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-ORG
Council -X- -X- I-ORG
members -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
killed -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
Darth -X- -X- B-PER
Vader -X- -X- I-PER
at -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
end -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
war -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
was -X- -X- O
nationalized -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
newly-formed -X- -X- O
Galactic -X- -X- B-ORG
Empire -X- -X- I-ORG
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
armaments -X- -X- O
committee -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
committee -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
that -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
formed -X- -X- O
at -X- -X- O
some -X- -X- O
point -X- -X- O
before -X- -X- O
32 -X- -X- O
BBY -X- -X- O
' -X- -X- O
s -X- -X- O
Capture -X- -X- B-MISC
of -X- -X- I-MISC
Theed -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

The -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
Droid -X- -X- I-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
also -X- -X- O
known -X- -X- O
as -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
army -X- -X- I-ORG
, -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
a -X- -X- O
private -X- -X- O
, -X- -X- O
automated -X- -X- O
defense -X- -X- O
force -X- -X- O
maintained -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
to -X- -X- O
protect -X- -X- O
its -X- -X- O
valuable -X- -X- O
shipments -X- -X- O
from -X- -X- O
piracy -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O

It -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
used -X- -X- O
by -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Trade -X- -X- B-ORG
Federation -X- -X- I-ORG
to -X- -X- O
invade -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
Naboo -X- -X- B-LOC
and -X- -X- O
was -X- -X- O
later -X- -X- O
incorporated -X- -X- O
into -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-ORG
Droid -X- -X- I-ORG
Army -X- -X- I-ORG
during -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
Separatist -X- -X- B-MISC
Crisis -X- -X- I-MISC
. -X- -X- O

Advertisements -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
form -X- -X- O
of -X- -X- O
billboards -X- -X- O
and -X- -X- O
poster -X- -X- O
were -X- -X- O
put -X- -X- O
up -X- -X- O
around -X- -X- O
the -X- -X- O
planet -X- -X- O
in -X- -X- O
order -X- -X- O
to -X- -X- O
promote -X- -X- O
it -X- -X- O
. -X- -X- O